{
	"description": "Japanese given names",
	"deck": [
	{ "question": "鈴木", "answers": [ "すずき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "山田", "answers": [ "やまだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "森", "answers": [ "しん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 3%" },
	{ "question": "石井", "answers": [ "いしい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 5%" },
	{ "question": "大輔", "answers": [ "だいすけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "一郎", "answers": [ "いちろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "誠", "answers": [ "まこと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%" },
	{ "question": "豊", "answers": [ "ゆたか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%" },
	{ "question": "徹", "answers": [ "とおる", "てつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 89%, 9%" },
	{ "question": "明", "answers": [ "あきら", "めい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "太郎", "answers": [ "たろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "剛", "answers": [ "つよし", "ごう", "たけし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 49%, 24%, 23%" },
	{ "question": "健", "answers": [ "けん", "たけし", "たける" ], "comment": "Frequency: 74%, 22%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "隆", "answers": [ "たかし", "りゅう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 91%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "茂", "answers": [ "しげる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "平", "answers": [ "たいら", "ぺい", "ひとし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 4%, 2%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "愛", "answers": [ "あい", "めぐみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 90%, 8%" },
	{ "question": "伊東", "answers": [ "いとう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 4%" },
	{ "question": "淳", "answers": [ "じゅん", "あつし", "きよし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 71%, 26%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "金", "answers": [ "きん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 5%" },
	{ "question": "清", "answers": [ "きよし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "勝", "answers": [ "まさる", "かつ", "しょう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 62%, 5%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "永井", "answers": [ "ながい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 4%" },
	{ "question": "武", "answers": [ "たけし", "ぶ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 62%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "宏", "answers": [ "ひろし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "直樹", "answers": [ "なおき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "南", "answers": [ "みなみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 6%" },
	{ "question": "健一", "answers": [ "けんいち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "実", "answers": [ "みのる", "まこと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 90%, 8%" },
	{ "question": "家康", "answers": [ "いえやす" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "三郎", "answers": [ "さぶろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "哲也", "answers": [ "てつや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "博", "answers": [ "ひろし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "進", "answers": [ "すすむ", "しん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "薫", "answers": [ "かおる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "陽子", "answers": [ "ようこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "桂", "answers": [ "けい", "かつら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 7%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "大介", "answers": [ "だいすけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "東", "answers": [ "あずま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 5%" },
	{ "question": "修", "answers": [ "おさむ", "しゅう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "優子", "answers": [ "ゆうこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "優", "answers": [ "ゆう", "まさる", "ゆたか", "すぐる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 70%, 25%, 2%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "浩", "answers": [ "ひろし", "ひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "秀樹", "answers": [ "ひでき", "ほつき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "久美子", "answers": [ "くみこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "弘", "answers": [ "ひろし", "ひろむ", "こう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 86%, 11%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "浩二", "answers": [ "こうじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "洋子", "answers": [ "ようこ", "ひろこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "裕子", "answers": [ "ゆうこ", "ひろこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 87%, 13%" },
	{ "question": "光", "answers": [ "ひかる", "ひかり", "こう", "あきら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 69%, 11%, 6%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "信長", "answers": [ "のぶなが" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "亮", "answers": [ "りょう", "あきら", "とおる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 86%, 9%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "純", "answers": [ "じゅん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "聡", "answers": [ "さとし", "さとる", "ただし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 79%, 16%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "康", "answers": [ "やすし", "こう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 72%, 11%" },
	{ "question": "正", "answers": [ "ただし", "せい", "まさし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 86%, 7%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "毅", "answers": [ "たけし", "つよし", "き", "こわし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 55%, 36%, 5%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "白石", "answers": [ "はくせき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 10%" },
	{ "question": "裕", "answers": [ "ゆたか", "ゆう", "ひろし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 42%, 36%, 22%" },
	{ "question": "潤", "answers": [ "じゅん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "秋山", "answers": [ "あきやま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 3%" },
	{ "question": "谷", "answers": [ "たに" ], "comment": "Frequency: 4%" },
	{ "question": "和彦", "answers": [ "かずひこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "仁", "answers": [ "じん", "ひとし", "まさし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 57%, 38%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "勉", "answers": [ "つとむ", "べん", "ミョン" ], "comment": "Frequency: 81%, 16%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "稔", "answers": [ "みのる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%" },
	{ "question": "聖子", "answers": [ "せいこ", "しょうこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 82%, 16%" },
	{ "question": "洋", "answers": [ "ひろし", "よう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 72%, 26%" },
	{ "question": "涼子", "answers": [ "りょうこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "泉", "answers": [ "いずみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 31%" },
	{ "question": "美穂", "answers": [ "みほ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "寛", "answers": [ "ひろし", "かん", "ゆたか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 50%, 41%, 10%" },
	{ "question": "達也", "answers": [ "たつや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "勇", "answers": [ "いさむ", "いさみ", "ゆう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 74%, 18%, 7%" },
	{ "question": "学", "answers": [ "まなぶ", "がく" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "博之", "answers": [ "ひろゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "俊彦", "answers": [ "としひこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "和夫", "answers": [ "かずお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "荒川", "answers": [ "あらかわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "昇", "answers": [ "のぼる", "しょう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 88%, 11%" },
	{ "question": "由美", "answers": [ "ゆみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 90%" },
	{ "question": "和也", "answers": [ "かずや", "かずなり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 89%, 11%" },
	{ "question": "晃", "answers": [ "あきら", "こう", "のぼる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 79%, 19%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "治", "answers": [ "おさむ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "健太郎", "answers": [ "けんたろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "悠", "answers": [ "ゆう", "はるか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "恵", "answers": [ "めぐみ", "けい", "めぐむ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 58%, 26%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "一夫", "answers": [ "かずお", "かづを" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "二郎", "answers": [ "じろう", "にろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "彰", "answers": [ "あきら", "しょう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "哲郎", "answers": [ "てつろう", "てつお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 92%, 8%" },
	{ "question": "勲", "answers": [ "いさお", "フン", "くん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 82%, 15%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "満", "answers": [ "みつる", "まん", "みちる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 86%, 9%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "理恵", "answers": [ "りえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "繁", "answers": [ "しげる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "直人", "answers": [ "なおと", "なおひと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 86%, 14%" },
	{ "question": "忍", "answers": [ "しのぶ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "麻衣", "answers": [ "まい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "奈々", "answers": [ "なな" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "恵子", "answers": [ "けいこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "綾", "answers": [ "あや", "りょう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 89%, 6%" },
	{ "question": "佐竹", "answers": [ "さたけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 3%" },
	{ "question": "久保", "answers": [ "ひさやす" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "健二", "answers": [ "けんじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "瞳", "answers": [ "ひとみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 89%" },
	{ "question": "松村", "answers": [ "まつむら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 7%" },
	{ "question": "栄", "answers": [ "さかえ", "えい", "ひさし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 46%, 4%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "純一", "answers": [ "じゅんいち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "五郎", "answers": [ "ごろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "良子", "answers": [ "りょうこ", "よしこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 75%, 25%" },
	{ "question": "幸雄", "answers": [ "ゆきお", "さちお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%, 6%" },
	{ "question": "健太", "answers": [ "けんた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "幸子", "answers": [ "さちこ", "ゆきこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 86%, 13%" },
	{ "question": "正明", "answers": [ "まさあき", "しょうめい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "翔", "answers": [ "しょう", "かける", "つばさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%, 3%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "敦子", "answers": [ "あつこ", "のぶこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "龍太郎", "answers": [ "りゅうたろう", "りょうたろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 63%, 37%" },
	{ "question": "雅彦", "answers": [ "まさひこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "敏", "answers": [ "びん", "さとし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 62%, 35%" },
	{ "question": "次郎", "answers": [ "じろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "一", "answers": [ "はじめ", "イル" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "吉村", "answers": [ "よしむら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 7%" },
	{ "question": "由紀夫", "answers": [ "ゆきお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "藤村", "answers": [ "とうそん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 16%" },
	{ "question": "俊介", "answers": [ "しゅんすけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "彩", "answers": [ "あや", "さやか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "英雄", "answers": [ "ひでお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "裕之", "answers": [ "ひろゆき", "やすし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "純子", "answers": [ "じゅんこ", "すみこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 89%, 11%" },
	{ "question": "哲哉", "answers": [ "てつや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "哲", "answers": [ "てつ", "さとし", "さとる", "あきら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 53%, 37%, 6%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "勝彦", "answers": [ "かつひこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "智子", "answers": [ "ともこ", "さとこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "俊一", "answers": [ "しゅんいち", "としかず", "としいち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%, 3%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "孝", "answers": [ "たかし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "直子", "answers": [ "なおこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "和泉", "answers": [ "いずみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "四郎", "answers": [ "しろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "洋一", "answers": [ "よういち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "桑田", "answers": [ "くわた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "美紀", "answers": [ "みき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "由美子", "answers": [ "ゆみこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "真", "answers": [ "まこと", "しん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 76%, 24%" },
	{ "question": "功", "answers": [ "いさお", "こう", "いさむ", "こお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 89%, 4%, 3%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "真澄", "answers": [ "ますみ", "さねずみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 87%, 13%" },
	{ "question": "恭子", "answers": [ "きょうこ", "やすこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "哲夫", "answers": [ "てつお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "美里", "answers": [ "みさと", "みり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 65%, 12%" },
	{ "question": "京子", "answers": [ "きょうこ", "けいこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "克也", "answers": [ "かつや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "順子", "answers": [ "じゅんこ", "よりこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "山中", "answers": [ "やまなか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 4%" },
	{ "question": "大木", "answers": [ "おおき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 18%" },
	{ "question": "星", "answers": [ "せい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 7%" },
	{ "question": "大", "answers": [ "だい", "まさる", "ひろし", "おおき", "とも" ], "comment": "Frequency: 49%, 25%, 11%, 5%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "周", "answers": [ "しゅう", "あまね" ], "comment": "Frequency: 17%, 8%" },
	{ "question": "信夫", "answers": [ "のぶお", "しのぶ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 79%, 17%" },
	{ "question": "英二", "answers": [ "えいじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "昭", "answers": [ "あきら", "しょう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 86%, 14%" },
	{ "question": "章", "answers": [ "あきら", "しょう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 88%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "猛", "answers": [ "たけし", "たける", "もう", "たけき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%, 3%, 2%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "雄二", "answers": [ "ゆうじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "沙織", "answers": [ "さおり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "秀夫", "answers": [ "ひでお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "亜美", "answers": [ "あみ", "つぐみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "正義", "answers": [ "まさよし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "龍一", "answers": [ "りゅういち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "敦", "answers": [ "あつし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "賢治", "answers": [ "けんじ", "かたはる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "英明", "answers": [ "ひであき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "米子", "answers": [ "よねこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "肇", "answers": [ "はじめ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%" },
	{ "question": "良", "answers": [ "りょう", "まこと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "元", "answers": [ "げん", "はじめ", "もと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 50%, 25%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "博文", "answers": [ "ひろぶみ", "ひろふみ", "はくぶん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 60%, 34%, 6%" },
	{ "question": "由実", "answers": [ "ゆみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "信", "answers": [ "しん", "まこと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 58%, 41%" },
	{ "question": "綾子", "answers": [ "あやこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "香織", "answers": [ "かおり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "雅之", "answers": [ "まさゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "頼朝", "answers": [ "よりとも" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "正人", "answers": [ "まさと", "まさひと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "大和", "answers": [ "やまと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 7%" },
	{ "question": "健司", "answers": [ "けんじ", "たけし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "正治", "answers": [ "まさはる", "しょうじ", "せいじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 71%, 25%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "真弓", "answers": [ "まゆみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 89%" },
	{ "question": "栄一", "answers": [ "えいいち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "浩一", "answers": [ "こういち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "鶴田", "answers": [ "つるた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 21%" },
	{ "question": "守", "answers": [ "まもる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "直美", "answers": [ "なおみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "淳一", "answers": [ "じゅんいち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "淳子", "answers": [ "じゅんこ", "あつこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 76%, 24%" },
	{ "question": "一樹", "answers": [ "かずき", "いっき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 82%, 16%" },
	{ "question": "浩司", "answers": [ "こうじ", "ひろし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 83%, 17%" },
	{ "question": "舞", "answers": [ "まい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "研二", "answers": [ "けんじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "卓", "answers": [ "たく", "すぐる", "たかし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 47%, 34%, 18%" },
	{ "question": "和子", "answers": [ "かずこ", "まさこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%, 6%" },
	{ "question": "雅子", "answers": [ "まさこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "力", "answers": [ "りき", "つとむ", "ちから", "つよし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 52%, 24%, 20%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "慶子", "answers": [ "けいこ", "よしこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "圭", "answers": [ "けい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "雄三", "answers": [ "ゆうぞう", "かつぞう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "敏郎", "answers": [ "としろう", "としお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "登", "answers": [ "のぼる", "とう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "誠一", "answers": [ "せいいち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "慎吾", "answers": [ "しんご" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "明子", "answers": [ "あきこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "一成", "answers": [ "いっせい", "かずなり", "かずしげ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 44%, 42%, 14%" },
	{ "question": "英樹", "answers": [ "ひでき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "均", "answers": [ "ひとし", "きん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 90%, 10%" },
	{ "question": "英夫", "answers": [ "ひでお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "透", "answers": [ "とおる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "克彦", "answers": [ "かつひこ", "よしひこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "中", "answers": [ "あたる", "なか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 15%, 6%" },
	{ "question": "慎太郎", "answers": [ "しんたろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "恵美", "answers": [ "えみ", "めぐみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 63%, 37%" },
	{ "question": "麻美", "answers": [ "あさみ", "まみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 68%, 21%" },
	{ "question": "譲", "answers": [ "ゆずる", "じょう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 60%, 40%" },
	{ "question": "正樹", "answers": [ "まさき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "柏", "answers": [ "かしわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 4%" },
	{ "question": "真司", "answers": [ "しんじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "真理", "answers": [ "まり", "まさみち", "しんり", "まこと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 78%, 12%, 3%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "潔", "answers": [ "きよし", "ジー" ], "comment": "Frequency: 83%, 17%" },
	{ "question": "美樹", "answers": [ "みき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%" },
	{ "question": "智", "answers": [ "さとし", "さとる", "とも", "あきら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 57%, 16%, 15%, 10%" },
	{ "question": "千里", "answers": [ "ちさと", "せんり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 74%, 22%" },
	{ "question": "瑞穂", "answers": [ "みずほ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 63%" },
	{ "question": "旭", "answers": [ "あきら", "あさひ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 38%, 9%" },
	{ "question": "晶子", "answers": [ "あきこ", "しょうこ", "まさこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 89%, 6%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "賢一", "answers": [ "けんいち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "明夫", "answers": [ "あきお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "美智子", "answers": [ "みちこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "文彦", "answers": [ "ふみひこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "秀雄", "answers": [ "ひでお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "日向", "answers": [ "ひなた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "雅美", "answers": [ "まさみ", "まさよし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "大樹", "answers": [ "だいき", "ひろき", "たいき", "だいじゅ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 54%, 18%, 8%, 6%" },
	{ "question": "仁美", "answers": [ "ひとみ", "さとみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "静香", "answers": [ "しずか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "敬", "answers": [ "たかし", "けい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 58%, 42%" },
	{ "question": "堤", "answers": [ "つつみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "渉", "answers": [ "わたる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "智之", "answers": [ "としゆき", "ともゆき", "さとし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 59%, 38%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "翔子", "answers": [ "しょうこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "今日子", "answers": [ "きょうこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "崇", "answers": [ "たかし", "すう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "正雄", "answers": [ "まさお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "愛子", "answers": [ "あいこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%" },
	{ "question": "美奈子", "answers": [ "みなこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "亨", "answers": [ "とおる", "あきら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "裕二", "answers": [ "ゆうじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "治虫", "answers": [ "おさむ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "康夫", "answers": [ "やすお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "充", "answers": [ "みつる", "じゅう", "みつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 89%, 7%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "宏一", "answers": [ "こういち", "ひろかず" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "文", "answers": [ "ぶん", "あや", "ふみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 48%, 16%, 14%" },
	{ "question": "知子", "answers": [ "ともこ", "さとこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "靖", "answers": [ "やすし", "せい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "一雄", "answers": [ "かずお", "いちを", "くにお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 89%, 8%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "康弘", "answers": [ "やすひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "真人", "answers": [ "まさと", "まひと", "まこと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 60%, 30%, 9%" },
	{ "question": "邦彦", "answers": [ "くにひこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "正一", "answers": [ "しょういち", "まさいち", "まさかず" ], "comment": "Frequency: 56%, 32%, 11%" },
	{ "question": "純一郎", "answers": [ "じゅんいちろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "秀一", "answers": [ "しゅういち", "ひでかず", "ひでいち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 72%, 19%, 9%" },
	{ "question": "賢二", "answers": [ "けんじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "武史", "answers": [ "たけし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "真理子", "answers": [ "まりこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "武夫", "answers": [ "たけお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "郁彦", "answers": [ "いくひこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "豪", "answers": [ "ごう", "つよし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 89%, 9%" },
	{ "question": "雅人", "answers": [ "まさと", "まさひと", "がじん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 92%, 6%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "俊夫", "answers": [ "としお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "勤", "answers": [ "つとむ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "丹波", "answers": [ "たんば" ], "comment": "Frequency: 3%" },
	{ "question": "陽一", "answers": [ "よういち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "秀行", "answers": [ "ひでゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "真希", "answers": [ "まき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "桃子", "answers": [ "ももこ", "とうこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "由衣", "answers": [ "ゆい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "朋子", "answers": [ "ともこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "白鳥", "answers": [ "はくちょう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 9%" },
	{ "question": "美香", "answers": [ "みか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "玲子", "answers": [ "れいこ", "りょうこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "洋介", "answers": [ "ようすけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "礼子", "answers": [ "れいこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "貴子", "answers": [ "たかこ", "あつこ", "きし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 90%, 6%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "隆一", "answers": [ "りゅういち", "たかかず" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "里見", "answers": [ "さとみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 3%" },
	{ "question": "悟", "answers": [ "さとる", "さとし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%, 6%" },
	{ "question": "遥", "answers": [ "はるか", "よう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 87%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "拓也", "answers": [ "たくや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "俊之", "answers": [ "としゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "祐一", "answers": [ "ゆういち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "真由美", "answers": [ "まゆみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "悦子", "answers": [ "えつこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "竜也", "answers": [ "たつや", "りゅうや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%, 6%" },
	{ "question": "幸一", "answers": [ "こういち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "良一", "answers": [ "りょういち", "よしかず" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "大平", "answers": [ "たいへい", "おおひら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 3%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "茂樹", "answers": [ "しげき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "伸", "answers": [ "しん", "のぶる", "のぼる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%, 3%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "雄一", "answers": [ "ゆういち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "隆史", "answers": [ "たかし", "たかふみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 85%, 15%" },
	{ "question": "憲一", "answers": [ "けんいち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "宏美", "answers": [ "ひろみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "雅史", "answers": [ "まさし", "まさふみ", "まさひと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 54%, 35%, 11%" },
	{ "question": "高", "answers": [ "たかし", "こう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 29%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "靖子", "answers": [ "やすこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "真央", "answers": [ "まお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "龍之介", "answers": [ "りゅうのすけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "新", "answers": [ "あらた", "しん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 60%, 16%" },
	{ "question": "文雄", "answers": [ "ふみお", "ぶんゆう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%, 6%" },
	{ "question": "朗", "answers": [ "あきら", "ろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 81%, 18%" },
	{ "question": "正之", "answers": [ "まさゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "典子", "answers": [ "のりこ", "ふみこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "明菜", "answers": [ "あきな" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "光雄", "answers": [ "みつお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "涼", "answers": [ "りょう", "すずか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 92%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "義雄", "answers": [ "よしお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%" },
	{ "question": "政宗", "answers": [ "まさむね" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%" },
	{ "question": "俊", "answers": [ "しゅん", "とし", "すぐる", "さとし", "たかし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 76%, 11%, 8%, 3%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "武雄", "answers": [ "たけお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 71%" },
	{ "question": "葉子", "answers": [ "ようこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "千夏", "answers": [ "ちなつ", "ちか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 68%, 32%" },
	{ "question": "寿", "answers": [ "ひさし", "じゅ", "ことぶき", "とし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 28%, 18%, 12%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "正幸", "answers": [ "まさゆき", "まさよし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "小百合", "answers": [ "さゆり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "忠", "answers": [ "ただし", "ちゅう", "まこと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 61%, 27%, 11%" },
	{ "question": "出雲", "answers": [ "いずも" ], "comment": "Frequency: 3%" },
	{ "question": "武彦", "answers": [ "たけひこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "幸男", "answers": [ "ゆきお", "さちお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "聖", "answers": [ "ひじり", "たかし", "さとし", "こうき", "せい", "きよし", "みずき", "しょう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 23%, 16%, 12%, 12%, 9%, 5%, 5%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "史郎", "answers": [ "しろう", "ふみお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 90%, 10%" },
	{ "question": "楊", "answers": [ "よう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 8%" },
	{ "question": "家光", "answers": [ "いえみつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "美和", "answers": [ "みわ", "よしかず" ], "comment": "Frequency: 85%, 14%" },
	{ "question": "俊輔", "answers": [ "しゅんすけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "正彦", "answers": [ "まさひこ", "ただひこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "千春", "answers": [ "ちはる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "拓郎", "answers": [ "たくろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "剛志", "answers": [ "つよし", "たかし", "たけし", "こうじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 55%, 31%, 6%, 6%" },
	{ "question": "秀忠", "answers": [ "ひでただ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "駿", "answers": [ "はやお", "しゅん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 68%, 32%" },
	{ "question": "操", "answers": [ "そう", "みさお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 79%, 21%" },
	{ "question": "朴", "answers": [ "ぼく" ], "comment": "Frequency: 3%" },
	{ "question": "章太郎", "answers": [ "しょうたろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "司", "answers": [ "つかさ", "まもる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 67%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "早苗", "answers": [ "さなえ", "チョミョ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "啓", "answers": [ "けい", "ひらく", "はじめ", "あきら", "ひろむ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 77%, 12%, 5%, 4%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "正和", "answers": [ "まさかず" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "邦男", "answers": [ "くにお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "達郎", "answers": [ "たつろう", "たつお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "謙", "answers": [ "けん", "ゆずる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 91%, 9%" },
	{ "question": "啓介", "answers": [ "けいすけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "省吾", "answers": [ "しょうご", "せいご" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%, 6%" },
	{ "question": "京平", "answers": [ "きょうへい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "春樹", "answers": [ "はるき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "敏夫", "answers": [ "としお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "八郎", "answers": [ "はちろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "由紀", "answers": [ "ゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 62%" },
	{ "question": "翼", "answers": [ "つばさ", "よく", "たすく" ], "comment": "Frequency: 68%, 26%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "真一", "answers": [ "しんいち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "栗山", "answers": [ "りつざん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 4%" },
	{ "question": "佳祐", "answers": [ "けいすけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "直也", "answers": [ "なおや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "伸二", "answers": [ "しんじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "美咲", "answers": [ "みさき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 62%" },
	{ "question": "信雄", "answers": [ "のぶお", "のぶかつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 69%, 31%" },
	{ "question": "直哉", "answers": [ "なおや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%" },
	{ "question": "法子", "answers": [ "のりこ", "ほうこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 56%, 44%" },
	{ "question": "桜", "answers": [ "さくら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 30%" },
	{ "question": "唯", "answers": [ "ゆい", "ただし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "朱", "answers": [ "あけみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 5%" },
	{ "question": "暁", "answers": [ "さとる", "あきら", "あかつき", "ぎょう", "きょう", "さとし", "あき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 40%, 19%, 13%, 8%, 6%, 5%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "信彦", "answers": [ "のぶひこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "亘", "answers": [ "わたる", "こう", "せん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 78%, 11%, 6%" },
	{ "question": "歩", "answers": [ "あゆみ", "あゆむ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 67%, 30%" },
	{ "question": "亮太", "answers": [ "りょうた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "和正", "answers": [ "かずまさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "介石", "answers": [ "かいせき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "康雄", "answers": [ "やすお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "一彦", "answers": [ "かずひこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "義明", "answers": [ "よしあき", "よしはる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "美代子", "answers": [ "みよこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "忠雄", "answers": [ "ただお", "ただかつ", "ただたか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 89%, 8%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "孝雄", "answers": [ "たかお", "よしお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%, 6%" },
	{ "question": "聰", "answers": [ "そう", "さとし", "あきら", "さとる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 40%, 29%, 27%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "裕美", "answers": [ "ひろみ", "ゆみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 67%, 33%" },
	{ "question": "謙信", "answers": [ "けんしん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "龍", "answers": [ "りゅう", "りょう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 74%, 14%" },
	{ "question": "明日香", "answers": [ "あすか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 72%" },
	{ "question": "良平", "answers": [ "りょうへい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "拓", "answers": [ "たく", "ひろし", "ひろむ", "ひらく" ], "comment": "Frequency: 88%, 7%, 4%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "賢", "answers": [ "けん", "まさる", "たかし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 82%, 13%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "順", "answers": [ "じゅん", "したごう", "すなお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%, 5%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "千秋", "answers": [ "ちあき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 85%" },
	{ "question": "晋三", "answers": [ "しんぞう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "ひろ子", "answers": [ "ひろこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "雅治", "answers": [ "まさはる", "まさじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "隼人", "answers": [ "はやと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%" },
	{ "question": "千尋", "answers": [ "ちひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "順一", "answers": [ "じゅんいち", "まさかず" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "明美", "answers": [ "あけみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "研", "answers": [ "けん", "みがく" ], "comment": "Frequency: 53%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "アキ子", "answers": [ "あきこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "静", "answers": [ "しずか", "シズカ", "せい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%, 2%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "清隆", "answers": [ "きよたか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "隆之", "answers": [ "たかゆき", "たかし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "百合子", "answers": [ "ゆりこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "慎二", "answers": [ "しんじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "和久", "answers": [ "かずひさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 90%" },
	{ "question": "太一", "answers": [ "たいち", "たかかつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "百恵", "answers": [ "ももえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "晶", "answers": [ "あきら", "あき", "ひかり", "しょう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 66%, 8%, 3%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "信行", "answers": [ "のぶゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "真也", "answers": [ "しんや", "まや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "和幸", "answers": [ "かずゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "中津", "answers": [ "ちゅうしん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 4%" },
	{ "question": "正行", "answers": [ "まさゆき", "まさつら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 90%, 10%" },
	{ "question": "ゆう子", "answers": [ "ゆうこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "竜", "answers": [ "りゅう", "りょう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 35%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "佳奈", "answers": [ "かな" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "博史", "answers": [ "ひろし", "ひろふみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "紀", "answers": [ "おさむ", "ただし", "き", "のり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 11%, 5%, 2%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "和義", "answers": [ "かずよし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "康二", "answers": [ "こうじ", "やすじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 86%, 14%" },
	{ "question": "寛子", "answers": [ "ひろこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "紳助", "answers": [ "しんすけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "浩之", "answers": [ "ひろゆき", "ひろし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "尚", "answers": [ "ひさし", "しょう", "たかし", "なお", "なおや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 55%, 22%, 8%, 5%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "香美", "answers": [ "こうみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 36%" },
	{ "question": "秀幸", "answers": [ "ひでゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "尊氏", "answers": [ "たかうじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "美空", "answers": [ "みそら", "みく" ], "comment": "Frequency: 3%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "洋平", "answers": [ "ようへい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "一三", "answers": [ "いちぞう", "かずみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 87%, 13%" },
	{ "question": "葵", "answers": [ "あおい", "まもる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 57%, 18%" },
	{ "question": "幸治", "answers": [ "こうじ", "ゆきはる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 91%, 8%" },
	{ "question": "庄司", "answers": [ "しょうじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 6%" },
	{ "question": "利明", "answers": [ "としあき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "耕一", "answers": [ "こういち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "馨", "answers": [ "かおる", "かおり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 91%, 9%" },
	{ "question": "未来", "answers": [ "みらい", "みく", "みき", "みこい", "みくる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 34%, 31%, 14%, 7%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "太", "answers": [ "ふとし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%" },
	{ "question": "漱石", "answers": [ "そうせき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "雅弘", "answers": [ "まさひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "滋", "answers": [ "しげる", "しげ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "裕一", "answers": [ "ゆういち", "ひろかず" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "等", "answers": [ "ひとし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "泰", "answers": [ "たい", "やすし", "ゆたか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 58%, 18%, 15%" },
	{ "question": "幸", "answers": [ "こう", "みゆき", "ゆき", "さち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 28%, 25%, 7%, 7%" },
	{ "question": "義男", "answers": [ "よしお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "慶", "answers": [ "けい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "弘樹", "answers": [ "ひろき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "隆司", "answers": [ "たかし", "りゅうじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 57%, 43%" },
	{ "question": "義経", "answers": [ "よしつね" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "克己", "answers": [ "かつみ", "かつき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 91%, 7%" },
	{ "question": "亜紀", "answers": [ "あき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "真紀", "answers": [ "まき", "まさき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 88%, 12%" },
	{ "question": "幸夫", "answers": [ "ゆきお", "さちお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 92%, 8%" },
	{ "question": "誠治", "answers": [ "せいじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "秀明", "answers": [ "ひであき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "文子", "answers": [ "あやこ", "ふみこ", "のりこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 56%, 38%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "俊二", "answers": [ "しゅんじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "健治", "answers": [ "けんじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "景子", "answers": [ "けいこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "正士", "answers": [ "まさし", "せいし", "まさひと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%, 5%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "望", "answers": [ "のぞむ", "のぞみ", "ぼう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 69%, 25%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "公一", "answers": [ "こういち", "きんかず" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "敬之", "answers": [ "のりゆき", "たかゆき", "よしゆき", "ひろゆき", "けいし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 71%, 18%, 6%, 3%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "圭介", "answers": [ "けいすけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "由貴", "answers": [ "ゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "光司", "answers": [ "こうじ", "みつじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "向井", "answers": [ "むかい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 4%" },
	{ "question": "正夫", "answers": [ "まさお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "篤", "answers": [ "あつし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "勇人", "answers": [ "はやと", "ゆうと", "たけと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 88%, 9%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "和博", "answers": [ "かずひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "義隆", "answers": [ "よしたか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "弘之", "answers": [ "ひろゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "道真", "answers": [ "みちざね" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "和哉", "answers": [ "かずや", "かずちか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 92%, 8%" },
	{ "question": "貴史", "answers": [ "たかし", "たかふみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 87%, 12%" },
	{ "question": "河内", "answers": [ "かわち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 8%" },
	{ "question": "義人", "answers": [ "よしと", "よしひと", "ぎじん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 73%, 21%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "祐介", "answers": [ "ゆうすけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "尚子", "answers": [ "なおこ", "ひさこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 60%, 39%" },
	{ "question": "佐渡", "answers": [ "さど" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "準", "answers": [ "じゅん", "ひとし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 87%, 13%" },
	{ "question": "栄作", "answers": [ "えいさく" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "誠一郎", "answers": [ "せいいちろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "達夫", "answers": [ "たつお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "潤一", "answers": [ "じゅんいち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "堅", "answers": [ "けん", "かたし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%, 6%" },
	{ "question": "一生", "answers": [ "いっせい", "かずお", "かずみ", "かずき", "いっしょう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 68%, 20%, 4%, 4%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "拓哉", "answers": [ "たくや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "麗", "answers": [ "れい", "うらら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 60%, 40%" },
	{ "question": "高志", "answers": [ "たかし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "春夫", "answers": [ "はるお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "光子", "answers": [ "みつこ", "てるこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "妙子", "answers": [ "たえこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "久", "answers": [ "ひさし", "ひさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "健児", "answers": [ "けんじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "貢", "answers": [ "みつぐ", "みつぎ", "こう", "すすむ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 85%, 7%, 4%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "敏行", "answers": [ "としゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "夏子", "answers": [ "なつこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "重信", "answers": [ "しげのぶ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%" },
	{ "question": "七瀬", "answers": [ "ななせ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 53%" },
	{ "question": "穂積", "answers": [ "ほづみ", "ほずみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 19%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "信一", "answers": [ "しんいち", "のぶかず" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%, 6%" },
	{ "question": "奈美恵", "answers": [ "なみえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "進一", "answers": [ "しんいち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "俊郎", "answers": [ "としろう", "としお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 77%, 22%" },
	{ "question": "渚", "answers": [ "なぎさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 76%" },
	{ "question": "卓也", "answers": [ "たくや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "邦夫", "answers": [ "くにお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "勝美", "answers": [ "かつみ", "かつよし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "一男", "answers": [ "かずお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "吉宗", "answers": [ "よしむね" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "哲章", "answers": [ "てっしょう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "真二", "answers": [ "しんじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "脩", "answers": [ "おさむ", "しゅう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 81%, 19%" },
	{ "question": "美保", "answers": [ "みほ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 71%" },
	{ "question": "有紀", "answers": [ "ゆき", "あき", "ゆうき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 82%, 13%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "信之", "answers": [ "のぶゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "雅也", "answers": [ "まさや", "まさなり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "正則", "answers": [ "まさのり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "圭一", "answers": [ "けいいち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "陽介", "answers": [ "ようすけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "信子", "answers": [ "のぶこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "正美", "answers": [ "まさみ", "まさよし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "隆盛", "answers": [ "たかもり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "昌子", "answers": [ "まさこ", "しょうこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 88%, 10%" },
	{ "question": "晃一", "answers": [ "こういち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "渡", "answers": [ "わたる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 35%" },
	{ "question": "修司", "answers": [ "しゅうじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "剛士", "answers": [ "たけし", "たかし", "つよし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 60%, 34%, 6%" },
	{ "question": "千歳", "answers": [ "ちとせ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "綱吉", "answers": [ "つなよし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "道夫", "answers": [ "みちお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "和男", "answers": [ "かずお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "麻衣子", "answers": [ "まいこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "亜希子", "answers": [ "あきこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "弘子", "answers": [ "ひろこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "和弘", "answers": [ "かずひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "乾", "answers": [ "すすむ", "けん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 6%, 6%" },
	{ "question": "正博", "answers": [ "まさひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "喜久子", "answers": [ "きくこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "新司", "answers": [ "しんじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "邦子", "answers": [ "くにこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "龍馬", "answers": [ "りょうま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "久美", "answers": [ "くみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 92%" },
	{ "question": "八千代", "answers": [ "やちよ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 30%" },
	{ "question": "藍", "answers": [ "あい", "らん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 91%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "半田", "answers": [ "はんだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "忠義", "answers": [ "ただよし", "ただあき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 92%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "辰巳", "answers": [ "たつみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 25%" },
	{ "question": "智一", "answers": [ "ともかず" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "英一", "answers": [ "えいいち", "ひでかず" ], "comment": "Frequency: 88%, 11%" },
	{ "question": "要", "answers": [ "かなめ", "よう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 69%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "大地", "answers": [ "だいち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 40%" },
	{ "question": "琢也", "answers": [ "たくや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "真一郎", "answers": [ "しんいちろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "道子", "answers": [ "みちこ", "どうし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "昌弘", "answers": [ "まさひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "隆行", "answers": [ "たかゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "來未", "answers": [ "くみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "新一", "answers": [ "しんいち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "三次", "answers": [ "さんじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 6%" },
	{ "question": "公平", "answers": [ "こうへい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "義昭", "answers": [ "よしあき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "巌", "answers": [ "いわお", "がん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "大二郎", "answers": [ "だいじろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "耕司", "answers": [ "こうじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "健次", "answers": [ "けんじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "真里", "answers": [ "まり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "昌也", "answers": [ "まさや", "よしや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "沢東", "answers": [ "たくとう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "安", "answers": [ "あん", "やすし", "やす" ], "comment": "Frequency: 10%, 9%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "康成", "answers": [ "やすなり", "こうせい", "やすしげ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%, 2%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "吾郎", "answers": [ "ごろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "陽水", "answers": [ "ようすい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "松", "answers": [ "しょう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 16%" },
	{ "question": "淑子", "answers": [ "よしこ", "としこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 53%, 47%" },
	{ "question": "祐子", "answers": [ "ゆうこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "健次郎", "answers": [ "けんじろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "正隆", "answers": [ "まさたか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "由紀子", "answers": [ "ゆきこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "貞夫", "answers": [ "さだお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "力也", "answers": [ "りきや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "俊哉", "answers": [ "としや", "しゅんや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%, 7%" },
	{ "question": "十三", "answers": [ "じゅうぞう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 71%" },
	{ "question": "保", "answers": [ "たもつ", "やすし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "信義", "answers": [ "のぶよし", "しんぎ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 92%, 6%" },
	{ "question": "雄一郎", "answers": [ "ゆういちろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "光秀", "answers": [ "みつひで" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "孝弘", "answers": [ "たかひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "兼人", "answers": [ "かねと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "栄子", "answers": [ "えいこ", "えいし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "美郷", "answers": [ "みさと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 14%" },
	{ "question": "紀子", "answers": [ "のりこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "哲朗", "answers": [ "てつろう", "てつお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "北山", "answers": [ "ほくざん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "都", "answers": [ "みやこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 44%" },
	{ "question": "由佳", "answers": [ "ゆか", "ゆうか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "崇史", "answers": [ "たかし", "たかふみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 90%, 10%" },
	{ "question": "信介", "answers": [ "のぶすけ", "しんすけ", "しんかい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 66%, 31%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "郭", "answers": [ "かく" ], "comment": "Frequency: 3%" },
	{ "question": "裕司", "answers": [ "ゆうじ", "ひろし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "圭吾", "answers": [ "けいご" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "直", "answers": [ "ただし", "すなお", "なおし", "なお", "ちょく", "なおき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 47%, 21%, 13%, 13%, 4%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "忠夫", "answers": [ "ただお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "誠司", "answers": [ "せいじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "芳忠", "answers": [ "ほうちゅう", "よしただ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%, 7%" },
	{ "question": "伸一", "answers": [ "しんいち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "幸喜", "answers": [ "こうき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "高史", "answers": [ "たかし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "たか子", "answers": [ "たかこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "譲治", "answers": [ "じょうじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "正広", "answers": [ "まさひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "智久", "answers": [ "ともひさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "明彦", "answers": [ "あきひこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "陸", "answers": [ "りく" ], "comment": "Frequency: 31%" },
	{ "question": "大助", "answers": [ "だいすけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "浩史", "answers": [ "ひろし", "ひろふみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 88%, 11%" },
	{ "question": "三船", "answers": [ "みふね" ], "comment": "Frequency: 5%" },
	{ "question": "五月", "answers": [ "さつき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 64%" },
	{ "question": "孝之", "answers": [ "たかゆき", "のりゆき", "こうじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 87%, 8%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "慶喜", "answers": [ "よしのぶ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "武人", "answers": [ "たけひと", "たけと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "美幸", "answers": [ "みゆき", "よしゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 92%, 8%" },
	{ "question": "新太郎", "answers": [ "しんたろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "聡美", "answers": [ "さとみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "文夫", "answers": [ "ふみお", "あやお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%, 7%" },
	{ "question": "浩子", "answers": [ "ひろこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "久志", "answers": [ "ひさし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%" },
	{ "question": "奈央", "answers": [ "なお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "晋", "answers": [ "すすむ", "しん", "チン" ], "comment": "Frequency: 52%, 46%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "朝日", "answers": [ "あさひ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 3%" },
	{ "question": "仁志", "answers": [ "ひとし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 81%" },
	{ "question": "千恵子", "answers": [ "ちえこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "熊野", "answers": [ "ゆや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "貴", "answers": [ "たかし", "き", "たか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 92%, 5%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "啓治", "answers": [ "けいじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "賢雄", "answers": [ "けんゆう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "京", "answers": [ "きょう", "けい", "たかし", "みさと", "みやこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 36%, 11%, 7%, 3%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "吉見", "answers": [ "よしみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 7%" },
	{ "question": "光男", "answers": [ "みつお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "晃司", "answers": [ "こうじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "晴臣", "answers": [ "はるおみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "昭一", "answers": [ "しょういち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "篤史", "answers": [ "あつし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "真琴", "answers": [ "まこと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 80%" },
	{ "question": "俊樹", "answers": [ "としき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "赳夫", "answers": [ "たけお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "譲二", "answers": [ "じょうじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "義弘", "answers": [ "よしひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "加奈子", "answers": [ "かなこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "昌彦", "answers": [ "まさひこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "次利", "answers": [ "つぐとし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "大作", "answers": [ "だいさく" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "城", "answers": [ "くに", "じょう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 5%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "省三", "answers": [ "しょうぞう", "せいぞう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "圭子", "answers": [ "けいこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "茂雄", "answers": [ "しげお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "義夫", "answers": [ "よしお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "重治", "answers": [ "しげはる", "じゅうじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 69%, 31%" },
	{ "question": "美子", "answers": [ "よしこ", "みこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "真知子", "answers": [ "まちこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "隆信", "answers": [ "たかのぶ", "りゅうしん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "健介", "answers": [ "けんすけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "清子", "answers": [ "きよこ", "さやこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 88%, 11%" },
	{ "question": "良太", "answers": [ "りょうた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "和雄", "answers": [ "かずお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "英治", "answers": [ "えいじ", "ひではる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 90%, 10%" },
	{ "question": "鶴瓶", "answers": [ "つるべ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "裕次郎", "answers": [ "ゆうじろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "麻里", "answers": [ "まり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%" },
	{ "question": "彬", "answers": [ "あきら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "和之", "answers": [ "かずゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "義一", "answers": [ "ぎいち", "よしかず" ], "comment": "Frequency: 73%, 25%" },
	{ "question": "利夫", "answers": [ "としお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "鉄矢", "answers": [ "てつや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%" },
	{ "question": "大倉", "answers": [ "おおくら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 15%" },
	{ "question": "結衣", "answers": [ "ゆい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "栄治", "answers": [ "えいじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "理", "answers": [ "おさむ", "さとし", "さとる", "ただし", "り" ], "comment": "Frequency: 81%, 10%, 4%, 3%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "高見", "answers": [ "たかみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 4%" },
	{ "question": "玲", "answers": [ "れい", "りょう", "あきら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 72%, 14%, 12%" },
	{ "question": "一平", "answers": [ "いっぺい", "かずひら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "辰夫", "answers": [ "たつお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "潤一郎", "answers": [ "じゅんいちろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "克幸", "answers": [ "かつゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "昭彦", "answers": [ "あきひこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "修一", "answers": [ "しゅういち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "亜弥", "answers": [ "あや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "規夫", "answers": [ "のりお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "清張", "answers": [ "せいちょう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "新平", "answers": [ "しんぺい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%" },
	{ "question": "秀和", "answers": [ "ひでかず", "しゅうわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "成", "answers": [ "せい", "なる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 82%, 13%" },
	{ "question": "勝己", "answers": [ "かつみ", "かつき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "真美", "answers": [ "まみ", "まさみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "清盛", "answers": [ "きよもり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "建", "answers": [ "けん", "ゴン", "たつる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 82%, 5%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "順平", "answers": [ "じゅんぺい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "晋也", "answers": [ "しんや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "光一", "answers": [ "こういち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "遼", "answers": [ "りょう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "俊太郎", "answers": [ "しゅんたろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "康隆", "answers": [ "やすたか", "こうりゅう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "徳子", "answers": [ "よしこ", "とくし", "のりこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 71%, 17%, 11%" },
	{ "question": "敬三", "answers": [ "けいぞう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "日南", "answers": [ "にちなん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 4%" },
	{ "question": "真彦", "answers": [ "まさひこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "佐和子", "answers": [ "さわこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "寅泰", "answers": [ "ともやす" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "三成", "answers": [ "みつなり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%" },
	{ "question": "龍二", "answers": [ "りゅうじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "長政", "answers": [ "ながまさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "雅俊", "answers": [ "まさとし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "博子", "answers": [ "ひろこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "八雲", "answers": [ "やくも" ], "comment": "Frequency: 45%" },
	{ "question": "葉月", "answers": [ "はづき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 26%" },
	{ "question": "英彦", "answers": [ "ひでひこ", "ひでを" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "貴志", "answers": [ "たかし", "たかゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 62%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "裕介", "answers": [ "ゆうすけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "昭三", "answers": [ "しょうぞう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "正志", "answers": [ "まさし", "しょうじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "秀喜", "answers": [ "ひでき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "麗子", "answers": [ "れいこ", "れいし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "晴彦", "answers": [ "はるひこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "牧", "answers": [ "まき", "ぼく" ], "comment": "Frequency: 9%, 9%" },
	{ "question": "椿", "answers": [ "つばき", "ちん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 10%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "一柳", "answers": [ "いちりゅう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 3%" },
	{ "question": "友紀", "answers": [ "ゆき", "ゆうき", "とものり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 67%, 24%, 8%" },
	{ "question": "漣", "answers": [ "れん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 84%" },
	{ "question": "ゆり子", "answers": [ "ゆりこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "美貴", "answers": [ "みき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "亜貴", "answers": [ "あき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "正史", "answers": [ "せいし", "まさふみ", "まさし", "ただし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 53%, 25%, 15%, 7%" },
	{ "question": "眞一郎", "answers": [ "しんいちろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "慶太", "answers": [ "けいた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "喜一", "answers": [ "きいち", "よしかず" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "義郎", "answers": [ "よしろう", "よしお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 87%, 12%" },
	{ "question": "咲", "answers": [ "さき", "えみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 72%, 21%" },
	{ "question": "勝久", "answers": [ "かつひさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "奈美", "answers": [ "なみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 69%" },
	{ "question": "智美", "answers": [ "ともみ", "さとみ", "としみ", "ともよし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 81%, 13%, 4%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "友和", "answers": [ "ともかず" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "武蔵", "answers": [ "むさし", "たけぞう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 90%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "智也", "answers": [ "ともや", "ともなり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "義信", "answers": [ "よしのぶ", "ウィシン" ], "comment": "Frequency: 89%, 11%" },
	{ "question": "美加", "answers": [ "みか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "伸介", "answers": [ "しんすけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "義久", "answers": [ "よしひさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "祐二", "answers": [ "ゆうじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "哲治", "answers": [ "てつはる", "てつじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 81%, 19%" },
	{ "question": "正章", "answers": [ "まさあき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "徹也", "answers": [ "てつや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "夏希", "answers": [ "なつき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "京介", "answers": [ "きょうすけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "宗", "answers": [ "そう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 10%" },
	{ "question": "元就", "answers": [ "もとなり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "昌宏", "answers": [ "まさひろ", "よしひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "佳子", "answers": [ "よしこ", "けいこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 79%, 21%" },
	{ "question": "景勝", "answers": [ "かげかつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "絵里", "answers": [ "えり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "泰彦", "answers": [ "やすひこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "志穂", "answers": [ "しほ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "民夫", "answers": [ "たみお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "元気", "answers": [ "げんき", "もとき", "もとおき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 76%, 16%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "竜二", "answers": [ "りゅうじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "隆夫", "answers": [ "たかお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "智和", "answers": [ "ともかず" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "民生", "answers": [ "たみお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "琢磨", "answers": [ "たくま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "貴之", "answers": [ "たかゆき", "たかし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%, 7%" },
	{ "question": "永吉", "answers": [ "えいきち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 89%" },
	{ "question": "奈緒", "answers": [ "なお", "なを" ], "comment": "Frequency: 88%, 11%" },
	{ "question": "成美", "answers": [ "なるみ", "せいび" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "敏彦", "answers": [ "としひこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "竹山", "answers": [ "ちくざん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 4%" },
	{ "question": "礼", "answers": [ "れい", "あや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "弘道", "answers": [ "ひろみち", "こうどう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 77%, 19%" },
	{ "question": "董", "answers": [ "ただす", "ただし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 12%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "洋次", "answers": [ "ようじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "正三", "answers": [ "しょうぞう", "まさかず", "しょうさん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 91%, 6%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "飛鳥", "answers": [ "あすか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 44%" },
	{ "question": "舞子", "answers": [ "まいこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 86%" },
	{ "question": "紘一", "answers": [ "こういち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "穣", "answers": [ "ゆたか", "じょう", "みのる", "みのり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 53%, 27%, 18%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "緑", "answers": [ "みどり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 55%" },
	{ "question": "樹", "answers": [ "いつき", "みき", "たつる", "たつき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 33%, 24%, 13%, 13%" },
	{ "question": "真子", "answers": [ "まこ", "まさこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 82%, 16%" },
	{ "question": "広明", "answers": [ "ひろあき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "正太郎", "answers": [ "しょうたろう", "まさたろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "北斗", "answers": [ "ほくと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 17%" },
	{ "question": "有希", "answers": [ "ゆき", "ゆうき", "あき", "ゆぅき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 54%, 28%, 10%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "尚美", "answers": [ "なおみ", "なほみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 70%, 30%" },
	{ "question": "厚", "answers": [ "あつし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "玲奈", "answers": [ "れな", "れいな" ], "comment": "Frequency: 71%, 29%" },
	{ "question": "直政", "answers": [ "なおまさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "翔太", "answers": [ "しょうた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "梓", "answers": [ "あずさ", "あづさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 84%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "晴子", "answers": [ "はるこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "健一郎", "answers": [ "けんいちろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "輝", "answers": [ "てる", "あきら", "ひかる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 48%, 30%, 12%" },
	{ "question": "寛之", "answers": [ "ひろゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "慎也", "answers": [ "しんや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "由香", "answers": [ "ゆか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "英一郎", "answers": [ "えいいちろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "了", "answers": [ "りょう", "りよう", "さとる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 62%, 27%, 10%" },
	{ "question": "よう子", "answers": [ "ようこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "正男", "answers": [ "まさお", "ジョンナム" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%, 7%" },
	{ "question": "久雄", "answers": [ "ひさお", "ひさたか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "信二", "answers": [ "しんじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "源一郎", "answers": [ "げんいちろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "正昭", "answers": [ "まさあき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "温子", "answers": [ "あつこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "正弘", "answers": [ "まさひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "夏木", "answers": [ "なつき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 9%" },
	{ "question": "英郎", "answers": [ "ひでお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "直方", "answers": [ "なおかた", "なおまさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 20%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "里菜", "answers": [ "りな" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "久世", "answers": [ "ひさよ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "光晴", "answers": [ "みつはる", "こうせい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%, 6%" },
	{ "question": "檀", "answers": [ "まゆみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 4%" },
	{ "question": "潮", "answers": [ "うしお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 29%" },
	{ "question": "弘一", "answers": [ "こういち", "ひろかず", "ひろいち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 89%, 8%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "欽一", "answers": [ "きんいち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "一義", "answers": [ "かずよし", "いちぎ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%, 6%" },
	{ "question": "勝平", "answers": [ "かっぺい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "里美", "answers": [ "さとみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 91%" },
	{ "question": "康介", "answers": [ "こうすけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "千明", "answers": [ "ちあき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 89%" },
	{ "question": "丈史", "answers": [ "たけし", "たけふみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 71%, 29%" },
	{ "question": "友美", "answers": [ "ともみ", "ゆみ", "ゆうみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 92%, 6%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "和歌子", "answers": [ "わかこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "孝宏", "answers": [ "たかひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "三枝", "answers": [ "みえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 4%" },
	{ "question": "信綱", "answers": [ "のぶつな" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "育江", "answers": [ "いくえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "家斉", "answers": [ "いえなり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "幹夫", "answers": [ "みきお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "博幸", "answers": [ "ひろゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "海舟", "answers": [ "かいしゅう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "正信", "answers": [ "まさのぶ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "政信", "answers": [ "まさのぶ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "浩志", "answers": [ "こうし", "ひろし", "こうじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 71%, 27%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "昭夫", "answers": [ "あきお", "てるお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "隆志", "answers": [ "たかし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "周平", "answers": [ "しゅうへい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "憲司", "answers": [ "けんじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "人志", "answers": [ "ひとし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "秀次", "answers": [ "ひでつぐ", "しゅうじ", "ひでじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 83%, 15%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "貞雄", "answers": [ "さだお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "剣", "answers": [ "けん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 83%" },
	{ "question": "里奈", "answers": [ "りな" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "謙二郎", "answers": [ "けんじろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "博一", "answers": [ "ひろかず", "ひろし", "ひろいち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 43%, 41%, 16%" },
	{ "question": "夏樹", "answers": [ "なつき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 30%" },
	{ "question": "啓二", "answers": [ "けいじ", "ひろじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "諭吉", "answers": [ "ゆきち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "冬樹", "answers": [ "ふゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%" },
	{ "question": "達雄", "answers": [ "たつお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "晃子", "answers": [ "あきこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "れい子", "answers": [ "れいこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "隆三", "answers": [ "りゅうぞう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "備", "answers": [ "び" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "周夫", "answers": [ "ちかお", "かねお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "愛美", "answers": [ "まなみ", "あいみ", "めぐみ", "まみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 54%, 40%, 3%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "高士", "answers": [ "たかし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "伊知郎", "answers": [ "いちろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "嶋", "answers": [ "しま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 3%" },
	{ "question": "芭蕉", "answers": [ "ばしょう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "九", "answers": [ "きゅう", "グ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 83%, 17%" },
	{ "question": "宏樹", "answers": [ "ひろき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "直純", "answers": [ "なおずみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "和枝", "answers": [ "かずえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "白", "answers": [ "はく", "きよし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 28%, 6%" },
	{ "question": "秀頼", "answers": [ "ひでより" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "一行", "answers": [ "いっこう", "かずゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 72%, 28%" },
	{ "question": "義行", "answers": [ "よしゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "幸三", "answers": [ "こうぞう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "平八郎", "answers": [ "へいはちろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "節", "answers": [ "たかし", "せつ", "みさお", "まこと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 65%, 27%, 7%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "隆男", "answers": [ "たかお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "一也", "answers": [ "かずや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "杏奈", "answers": [ "あんな" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "慧", "answers": [ "さとし", "けい", "とし", "さとる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 58%, 26%, 13%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "英子", "answers": [ "えいこ", "ひでこ", "あやこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 81%, 15%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "大伴", "answers": [ "おおとも" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "麻美子", "answers": [ "まみこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "昌夫", "answers": [ "まさお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "琴乃", "answers": [ "ことの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "乱歩", "answers": [ "らんぽ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "広樹", "answers": [ "ひろき", "こうき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "春菜", "answers": [ "はるな" ], "comment": "Frequency: 87%" },
	{ "question": "義満", "answers": [ "よしみつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "由里子", "answers": [ "ゆりこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "敏之", "answers": [ "としゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "俊雄", "answers": [ "としお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "喬", "answers": [ "たかし", "きょう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 88%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "崑", "answers": [ "こん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "正道", "answers": [ "まさみち", "なおみち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 65%, 35%" },
	{ "question": "仙一", "answers": [ "せんいち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "林檎", "answers": [ "りんご" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "清正", "answers": [ "きよまさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "鳳", "answers": [ "ほう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 4%" },
	{ "question": "恒夫", "answers": [ "つねお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "秀勝", "answers": [ "ひでかつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "理恵子", "answers": [ "りえこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "亮子", "answers": [ "りょうこ", "ゆきこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "由悠季", "answers": [ "よしゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "真綾", "answers": [ "まあや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "護", "answers": [ "まもる", "ご" ], "comment": "Frequency: 75%, 10%" },
	{ "question": "直之", "answers": [ "なおゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "甲州", "answers": [ "こうしゅう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 11%" },
	{ "question": "俊幸", "answers": [ "としゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "正勝", "answers": [ "まさかつ", "まさかず", "ただかつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 90%, 4%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "幸彦", "answers": [ "ゆきひこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "実里", "answers": [ "みのり", "みさと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 91%, 9%" },
	{ "question": "正成", "answers": [ "まさしげ", "まさなり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 70%, 30%" },
	{ "question": "広司", "answers": [ "こうじ", "ひろし", "ひろじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 72%, 26%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "香菜", "answers": [ "かな" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "清志郎", "answers": [ "きよしろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "茜", "answers": [ "あかね" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%" },
	{ "question": "慎一", "answers": [ "しんいち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "万丈", "answers": [ "ばんじょう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "律子", "answers": [ "りつこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "昌幸", "answers": [ "まさゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "利家", "answers": [ "としいえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "潤子", "answers": [ "じゅんこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "謙三", "answers": [ "けんぞう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "宇佐美", "answers": [ "うさみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "亜希", "answers": [ "あき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "清一", "answers": [ "せいいち", "きよかず" ], "comment": "Frequency: 81%, 19%" },
	{ "question": "孝一", "answers": [ "こういち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "杏里", "answers": [ "あんり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "康晴", "answers": [ "やすはる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "恵一", "answers": [ "けいいち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "陽", "answers": [ "よう", "あきら", "あき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 39%, 30%, 10%" },
	{ "question": "梁", "answers": [ "りょう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 13%" },
	{ "question": "長", "answers": [ "ひさし", "ちょう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 5%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "國男", "answers": [ "くにお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "久彌", "answers": [ "ひさや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "郁夫", "answers": [ "いくお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "久子", "answers": [ "ひさこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "博満", "answers": [ "ひろみつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "樹里", "answers": [ "じゅり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 86%" },
	{ "question": "四朗", "answers": [ "しろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "一博", "answers": [ "かずひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "家綱", "answers": [ "いえつな" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "蘭", "answers": [ "らん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "和郎", "answers": [ "かずろう", "かずお", "わろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 68%, 27%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "和美", "answers": [ "かずみ", "かずよし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 90%, 10%" },
	{ "question": "辰徳", "answers": [ "たつのり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "綾香", "answers": [ "あやか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "寛治", "answers": [ "かんじ", "ひろはる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 83%, 17%" },
	{ "question": "勝頼", "answers": [ "かつより" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "運昇", "answers": [ "うんしょう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "梨香", "answers": [ "りか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "巧", "answers": [ "たくみ", "こう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 92%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "志郎", "answers": [ "しろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "西沢", "answers": [ "にしざわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 12%" },
	{ "question": "浩美", "answers": [ "ひろみ", "はるみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 85%, 15%" },
	{ "question": "和宏", "answers": [ "かずひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "宏之", "answers": [ "ひろゆき", "ひろし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "祐", "answers": [ "ひろし", "ゆう", "たすく" ], "comment": "Frequency: 54%, 31%, 14%" },
	{ "question": "哲司", "answers": [ "てつじ", "てつし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 67%, 33%" },
	{ "question": "英之", "answers": [ "ひでゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "玉木", "answers": [ "たまき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 3%" },
	{ "question": "義光", "answers": [ "よしみつ", "よしあき", "よしてる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 53%, 44%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "良雄", "answers": [ "よしお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "美佳", "answers": [ "みか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "敏雄", "answers": [ "としお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "杏", "answers": [ "あん", "あんず" ], "comment": "Frequency: 67%, 10%" },
	{ "question": "静夫", "answers": [ "しずお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "英梨", "answers": [ "えり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "麻子", "answers": [ "あさこ", "まこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%, 6%" },
	{ "question": "昭雄", "answers": [ "あきお", "てるお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "零士", "answers": [ "れいじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "高明", "answers": [ "たかあき", "たかあきら", "こうめい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 73%, 17%, 10%" },
	{ "question": "朝雄", "answers": [ "あさお", "ともお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 91%, 9%" },
	{ "question": "沖", "answers": [ "ちゅう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "真奈美", "answers": [ "まなみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "清司", "answers": [ "せいじ", "きよし", "きよじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 60%, 37%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "真治", "answers": [ "しんじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "忠勝", "answers": [ "ただかつ", "ただとう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "里沙", "answers": [ "りさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "雪之丞", "answers": [ "ゆきのじょう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "智則", "answers": [ "とものり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "信也", "answers": [ "しんや", "のぶや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 87%, 13%" },
	{ "question": "義家", "answers": [ "よしいえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 83%" },
	{ "question": "弘行", "answers": [ "ひろいき", "ひろゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 80%, 20%" },
	{ "question": "正徳", "answers": [ "まさのり", "しょうとく" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "勝也", "answers": [ "かつや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "美馬", "answers": [ "みま", "びば" ], "comment": "Frequency: 12%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "正敏", "answers": [ "まさとし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "希", "answers": [ "のぞみ", "しずか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "智充", "answers": [ "ともみつ", "ともみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 74%, 26%" },
	{ "question": "雄大", "answers": [ "ゆうだい", "ゆうた", "ゆうたい", "たけひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 67%, 20%, 7%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "美沙子", "answers": [ "みさこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "福地", "answers": [ "ふくち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 4%" },
	{ "question": "竜童", "answers": [ "りゅうどう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "有美", "answers": [ "ゆみ", "ゆうみ", "ありよし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 91%, 6%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "孝行", "answers": [ "たかゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "誠二", "answers": [ "せいじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "明宏", "answers": [ "あきひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "衛", "answers": [ "まもる", "えい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 79%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "信孝", "answers": [ "のぶたか", "のぶなり", "のぶよし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%, 4%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "正浩", "answers": [ "まさひろ", "せいこう", "ジョンホ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 80%, 16%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "剛史", "answers": [ "つよし", "たけし", "よしふみ", "たけふみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 66%, 29%, 3%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "紀章", "answers": [ "きしょう", "のりあき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "和樹", "answers": [ "かずき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "燕", "answers": [ "えん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 7%" },
	{ "question": "義元", "answers": [ "よしもと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "美都子", "answers": [ "みつこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "石松", "answers": [ "いしまつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 78%" },
	{ "question": "三豊", "answers": [ "さんぽう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 6%" },
	{ "question": "康之", "answers": [ "やすゆき", "やすちか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%, 6%" },
	{ "question": "麻里子", "answers": [ "まりこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "光太郎", "answers": [ "こうたろう", "みつたろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "光夫", "answers": [ "みつお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "十郎太", "answers": [ "じゅうろうた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "章子", "answers": [ "あきこ", "あやこ", "しょうこ", "たかこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 79%, 11%, 8%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "正日", "answers": [ "ジョンイル" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "円", "answers": [ "まどか", "まろし", "つぶら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 43%, 4%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "武志", "answers": [ "たけし", "たけゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "怜", "answers": [ "れい", "さとし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 91%, 8%" },
	{ "question": "大門", "answers": [ "だいもん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 7%" },
	{ "question": "日成", "answers": [ "イルソン" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "努", "answers": [ "つとむ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "由子", "answers": [ "ゆうこ", "よしこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "拳", "answers": [ "けん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "裕也", "answers": [ "ゆうや", "ひろや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "雅夫", "answers": [ "まさお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "不二夫", "answers": [ "ふじお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "とも子", "answers": [ "ともこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "忠政", "answers": [ "ただまさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "美嘉", "answers": [ "みか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "芳雄", "answers": [ "よしお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "有", "answers": [ "ゆう", "たもつ", "なお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%, 4%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "真吾", "answers": [ "しんご" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "幸二", "answers": [ "こうじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "健三郎", "answers": [ "けんざぶろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "政夫", "answers": [ "まさお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "欣也", "answers": [ "きんや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "王子", "answers": [ "おうじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 33%" },
	{ "question": "清志", "answers": [ "きよし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "貴美子", "answers": [ "きみこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "国", "answers": [ "くに", "こく" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "岳", "answers": [ "がく", "たけし", "たかし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 71%, 5%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "彩乃", "answers": [ "あやの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 87%" },
	{ "question": "佳彦", "answers": [ "よしひこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "英司", "answers": [ "えいじ", "ひでじ", "ひでし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 76%, 22%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "永", "answers": [ "えい", "ひさし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 12%, 7%" },
	{ "question": "純次", "answers": [ "じゅんじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "信吾", "answers": [ "しんご" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "道雄", "answers": [ "みちお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "弥生", "answers": [ "やよい", "みお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 70%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "燿子", "answers": [ "ようこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "英機", "answers": [ "ひでき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "裕香", "answers": [ "ゆか", "ゆうか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "七海", "answers": [ "ななみ", "なみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 47%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "貴明", "answers": [ "たかあき", "たかあきら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "光昭", "answers": [ "みつあき", "てるあき", "みつてる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 85%, 12%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "亜矢子", "answers": [ "あやこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "喜朗", "answers": [ "よしろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "朋美", "answers": [ "ともみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "一輝", "answers": [ "かずき", "いっき", "かずてる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 57%, 37%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "雅功", "answers": [ "まさとし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "貫太郎", "answers": [ "かんたろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "一徳", "answers": [ "いっとく", "かずのり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 73%, 27%" },
	{ "question": "冬美", "answers": [ "ふゆみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "志保", "answers": [ "しほ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "重松", "answers": [ "しげまつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "泰子", "answers": [ "やすこ", "ひろこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "祥子", "answers": [ "しょうこ", "さちこ", "よしこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 50%, 48%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "利通", "answers": [ "としみち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "江", "answers": [ "こう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 23%" },
	{ "question": "恵美子", "answers": [ "えみこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "和", "answers": [ "わ", "やわら", "かず", "か", "なごみ", "やまと", "いずみ", "わたる", "のどか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 28%, 10%, 10%, 10%, 8%, 7%, 7%, 4%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "杜夫", "answers": [ "もりお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "敏男", "answers": [ "としお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "郁恵", "answers": [ "いくえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "健三", "answers": [ "けんぞう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "敬司", "answers": [ "けいじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "恒彦", "answers": [ "つねひこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "敬子", "answers": [ "けいこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "竜太", "answers": [ "りゅうた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "碧", "answers": [ "あおい", "みどり", "あお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 46%, 41%, 12%" },
	{ "question": "田", "answers": [ "でん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 7%" },
	{ "question": "正俊", "answers": [ "まさとし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "雅一", "answers": [ "まさいち", "まさかず" ], "comment": "Frequency: 61%, 38%" },
	{ "question": "修之", "answers": [ "のぶゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "天海", "answers": [ "てんかい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 3%" },
	{ "question": "由香里", "answers": [ "ゆかり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "保典", "answers": [ "やすのり", "やすすけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "雄太", "answers": [ "ゆうた", "ゆうだい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "宣彦", "answers": [ "のぶひこ", "のりひこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "啓一", "answers": [ "けいいち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "博久", "answers": [ "ひろひさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "のり子", "answers": [ "のりこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "蓮司", "answers": [ "れんじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "幸之助", "answers": [ "こうのすけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "完", "answers": [ "かん", "ひろし", "たもつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%, 2%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "明徳", "answers": [ "あきのり", "めいとく" ], "comment": "Frequency: 92%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "ルミ子", "answers": [ "ルミこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "哲男", "answers": [ "てつお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "行雄", "answers": [ "ゆきお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "久本", "answers": [ "ひさもと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "若菜", "answers": [ "わかな" ], "comment": "Frequency: 65%" },
	{ "question": "陽一郎", "answers": [ "よういちろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "裕貴", "answers": [ "ゆうき", "ひろき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 77%, 23%" },
	{ "question": "真矢", "answers": [ "しんや", "まや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 38%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "昌晃", "answers": [ "まさあき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "俊也", "answers": [ "としや", "しゅんや", "としなり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 70%, 16%, 14%" },
	{ "question": "大幸", "answers": [ "だいこう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "史子", "answers": [ "ふみこ", "あやこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 54%, 46%" },
	{ "question": "知世", "answers": [ "ともよ", "ちせ", "ちよ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 81%, 15%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "聡志", "answers": [ "さとし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "摩季", "answers": [ "まき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "知道", "answers": [ "ともみち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "杏子", "answers": [ "きょうこ", "ももこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 91%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "大蔵", "answers": [ "だいぞう", "たいぞう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 23%, 17%" },
	{ "question": "節子", "answers": [ "せつこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "藍子", "answers": [ "あいこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "雄介", "answers": [ "ゆうすけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "英男", "answers": [ "ひでお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "早紀", "answers": [ "さき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "須賀", "answers": [ "すが" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "犬養", "answers": [ "いぬかい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 3%" },
	{ "question": "龍三郎", "answers": [ "りゅうざぶろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "幹雄", "answers": [ "みきお", "もとお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 85%, 15%" },
	{ "question": "美帆", "answers": [ "みほ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "孝夫", "answers": [ "たかお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "隆太", "answers": [ "りゅうた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "竜一", "answers": [ "りゅういち", "たつひと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 82%, 18%" },
	{ "question": "美月", "answers": [ "みつき", "みづき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 50%, 31%" },
	{ "question": "富雄", "answers": [ "とみお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 92%" },
	{ "question": "六朗", "answers": [ "ろくろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "利雄", "answers": [ "としお", "としかつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "鶴太郎", "answers": [ "つるたろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "基紀", "answers": [ "もとき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "義貞", "answers": [ "よしさだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "一人", "answers": [ "かずと", "かずひと", "ひとり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 75%, 22%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "顕子", "answers": [ "あきこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "詩郎", "answers": [ "しろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "孝介", "answers": [ "こうすけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "徹子", "answers": [ "てつこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "香", "answers": [ "かおり", "かおる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 90%, 9%" },
	{ "question": "敦也", "answers": [ "あつや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "芳樹", "answers": [ "よしき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "三枝子", "answers": [ "みえこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "広", "answers": [ "ひろし", "こう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 74%, 10%" },
	{ "question": "正芳", "answers": [ "まさよし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "忠興", "answers": [ "ただおき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "権", "answers": [ "けん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%" },
	{ "question": "勝巳", "answers": [ "かつみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "佳織", "answers": [ "かおり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "祐樹", "answers": [ "ゆうき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "聡子", "answers": [ "さとこ", "そうこ", "あきこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%, 3%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "桂子", "answers": [ "けいこ", "かつらこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "優希", "answers": [ "ゆうき", "ゆき", "ゆうすけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 53%, 10%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "安二郎", "answers": [ "やすじろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "知良", "answers": [ "かずよし", "ともよし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 72%, 28%" },
	{ "question": "歳三", "answers": [ "としぞう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "隼", "answers": [ "じゅん", "しゅん", "はやと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 71%, 10%, 6%" },
	{ "question": "悟朗", "answers": [ "ごろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "賢司", "answers": [ "けんじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "直江", "answers": [ "なおえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 5%" },
	{ "question": "匠", "answers": [ "たくみ", "しょう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 69%, 18%" },
	{ "question": "宏治", "answers": [ "こうじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "敏也", "answers": [ "としや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "周作", "answers": [ "しゅうさく" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "暁人", "answers": [ "あきひと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "伸也", "answers": [ "しんや", "のぶや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "勝家", "answers": [ "かついえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "伊万里", "answers": [ "いまり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 7%" },
	{ "question": "太一郎", "answers": [ "たいちろう", "たいいちろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 90%, 10%" },
	{ "question": "昌平", "answers": [ "しょうへい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%" },
	{ "question": "富美子", "answers": [ "ふみこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "嘉門", "answers": [ "かもん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 12%" },
	{ "question": "真沙子", "answers": [ "まさこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "黒石", "answers": [ "こくせき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 3%" },
	{ "question": "勝生", "answers": [ "かつお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "寿一", "answers": [ "じゅいち", "としかず", "ひさいち", "ひさかず" ], "comment": "Frequency: 48%, 28%, 19%, 6%" },
	{ "question": "農", "answers": [ "みのり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "二朗", "answers": [ "じろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "義和", "answers": [ "よしかず", "よしまさ", "よしなり", "よしより" ], "comment": "Frequency: 84%, 7%, 5%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "由紀恵", "answers": [ "ゆきえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "悟空", "answers": [ "ごくう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "孝二", "answers": [ "こうじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "絵美", "answers": [ "えみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "鉄也", "answers": [ "てつや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "世凱", "answers": [ "せいがい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "正二", "answers": [ "しょうじ", "まさじ", "まさつぐ", "せいじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 85%, 9%, 4%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "五十六", "answers": [ "いそろく" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "稲城", "answers": [ "いなぎ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "義政", "answers": [ "よしまさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "有希子", "answers": [ "ゆきこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "雄", "answers": [ "ゆう", "たけし", "シャン" ], "comment": "Frequency: 57%, 40%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "直紀", "answers": [ "なおき", "なおただ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "耕史", "answers": [ "こうじ", "こうし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 92%, 8%" },
	{ "question": "善治", "answers": [ "よしはる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "祐希", "answers": [ "ゆうき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "浩三", "answers": [ "こうぞう", "ひろみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "一恵", "answers": [ "かずえ", "かづえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 57%, 43%" },
	{ "question": "正子", "answers": [ "まさこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "圭三", "answers": [ "けいぞう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "勝男", "answers": [ "かつお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "麗奈", "answers": [ "れな", "れいな" ], "comment": "Frequency: 80%, 20%" },
	{ "question": "裕太", "answers": [ "ゆうた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "登志夫", "answers": [ "としお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "悟志", "answers": [ "さとし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "丁", "answers": [ "とう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 26%" },
	{ "question": "典弘", "answers": [ "のりひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "功一", "answers": [ "こういち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "祐三", "answers": [ "ゆうぞう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "真実", "answers": [ "まみ", "まさみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 81%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "幸司", "answers": [ "こうじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "花子", "answers": [ "はなこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "千景", "answers": [ "ちかげ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "丘", "answers": [ "たかし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 13%" },
	{ "question": "義則", "answers": [ "よしのり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "正洋", "answers": [ "まさひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "弘明", "answers": [ "ひろあき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "忠治", "answers": [ "ちゅうじ", "ただはる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 78%, 22%" },
	{ "question": "準一", "answers": [ "じゅんいち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "藤吉", "answers": [ "とうきち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 57%" },
	{ "question": "恵三", "answers": [ "けいぞう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "金光", "answers": [ "かねみつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 4%" },
	{ "question": "孝則", "answers": [ "たかのり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "孝子", "answers": [ "たかこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%" },
	{ "question": "奨", "answers": [ "しょう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "浩治", "answers": [ "こうじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "英", "answers": [ "えい", "ひで", "たけし", "すぐる", "イン" ], "comment": "Frequency: 26%, 17%, 6%, 3%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "尚登", "answers": [ "なおと", "ひさと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 84%, 16%" },
	{ "question": "襄", "answers": [ "じょう", "のぼる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 57%, 43%" },
	{ "question": "眞", "answers": [ "まこと", "しん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 77%, 19%" },
	{ "question": "岩松", "answers": [ "いわまつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 16%" },
	{ "question": "利彦", "answers": [ "としひこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "晋太郎", "answers": [ "しんたろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "統", "answers": [ "おさむ", "もとい", "とう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 73%, 18%, 8%" },
	{ "question": "良介", "answers": [ "りょうすけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "克実", "answers": [ "かつみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "克寿", "answers": [ "かつひさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "英史", "answers": [ "えいじ", "えいし", "ひでし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 77%, 12%, 9%" },
	{ "question": "義仲", "answers": [ "よしなか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "貴久", "answers": [ "たかひさ", "よしひさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "保志", "answers": [ "やすし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 10%" },
	{ "question": "義之", "answers": [ "よしゆき", "ぎし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "一貴", "answers": [ "かずたか", "かずき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 50%, 50%" },
	{ "question": "夏彦", "answers": [ "なつひこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "慶一郎", "answers": [ "けいいちろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "右京", "answers": [ "うきょう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "正巳", "answers": [ "まさみ", "まさおと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "展男", "answers": [ "のぶお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "光政", "answers": [ "みつまさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "勝人", "answers": [ "まさと", "かつひと", "かつと", "かつんど" ], "comment": "Frequency: 56%, 23%, 13%, 7%" },
	{ "question": "光良", "answers": [ "てるよし", "みつよし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "慶一", "answers": [ "けいいち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "愛生", "answers": [ "あき", "よしお", "まなお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%, 3%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "寅彦", "answers": [ "とらひこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "俊明", "answers": [ "としあき", "しゅんみょう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "志麻", "answers": [ "しま", "しお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 63%, 25%" },
	{ "question": "浩輔", "answers": [ "こうすけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "正英", "answers": [ "まさひで", "まさふさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "松太郎", "answers": [ "まつたろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "冬馬", "answers": [ "とうま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "輝元", "answers": [ "てるもと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "彩子", "answers": [ "あやこ", "さいこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "辰雄", "answers": [ "たつお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "佳", "answers": [ "けい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "詠一", "answers": [ "えいいち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "魯", "answers": [ "ろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 23%" },
	{ "question": "翠", "answers": [ "みどり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 79%" },
	{ "question": "政子", "answers": [ "まさこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "邦", "answers": [ "ほう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 90%" },
	{ "question": "秀征", "answers": [ "ひでゆき", "しゅうせい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 83%, 17%" },
	{ "question": "利伸", "answers": [ "としのぶ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "恒雄", "answers": [ "つねお", "のりお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "峻", "answers": [ "しゅん", "たかし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 81%, 19%" },
	{ "question": "淳司", "answers": [ "じゅんじ", "あつし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "惠子", "answers": [ "けいこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "亮一", "answers": [ "りょういち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "寛平", "answers": [ "かんぺい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "耕生", "answers": [ "こうせい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "勝一", "answers": [ "かついち", "しょういち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 75%, 25%" },
	{ "question": "慎之介", "answers": [ "しんのすけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "貞子", "answers": [ "さだこ", "ていこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "深水", "answers": [ "しんすい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 14%" },
	{ "question": "隆聖", "answers": [ "りゅうせい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "羊介", "answers": [ "ようすけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "友香", "answers": [ "ともか", "ゆか", "ゆうか", "ひろか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 47%, 40%, 11%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "昭和", "answers": [ "あきかず" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "秋月", "answers": [ "シュウゲツ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "隆治", "answers": [ "りゅうじ", "たかはる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 66%, 34%" },
	{ "question": "道彦", "answers": [ "みちひこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "華", "answers": [ "はな", "か", "はる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 46%, 5%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "信繁", "answers": [ "のぶしげ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "弘美", "answers": [ "ひろみ", "ひろとみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "夏生", "answers": [ "なつき", "なつお", "なつを" ], "comment": "Frequency: 42%, 33%, 15%" },
	{ "question": "玄", "answers": [ "げん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%" },
	{ "question": "大中", "answers": [ "デジュン" ], "comment": "Frequency: 83%" },
	{ "question": "良太郎", "answers": [ "りょうたろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "幸宏", "answers": [ "ゆきひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "千和", "answers": [ "ちわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "談志", "answers": [ "だんし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "静也", "answers": [ "しずや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "留美", "answers": [ "るみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "裕行", "answers": [ "ひろゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "広之", "answers": [ "ひろゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "壮", "answers": [ "そう", "つよし", "たけし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 48%, 20%, 13%" },
	{ "question": "康彦", "answers": [ "やすひこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "まり子", "answers": [ "まりこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "敏子", "answers": [ "としこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "守屋", "answers": [ "もりや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 22%" },
	{ "question": "良和", "answers": [ "よしかず" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "夕子", "answers": [ "ゆうこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "昌明", "answers": [ "まさあき", "まさあきら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "佐知子", "answers": [ "さちこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "克巳", "answers": [ "かつみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "智昭", "answers": [ "ともあき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "智恵子", "answers": [ "ちえこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "和人", "answers": [ "かずと", "かずひと", "まさと", "かずしと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 53%, 41%, 3%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "武士", "answers": [ "たけし", "たけひと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "正光", "answers": [ "まさみつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "秀彦", "answers": [ "ひでひこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "晋作", "answers": [ "しんさく" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "旬", "answers": [ "しゅん", "じゅん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "哲平", "answers": [ "てっぺい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "祥太郎", "answers": [ "しょうたろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "康治", "answers": [ "やすはる", "こうじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 53%, 47%" },
	{ "question": "博美", "answers": [ "ひろみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "退助", "answers": [ "たいすけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "乗児", "answers": [ "じょうじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "英次", "answers": [ "えいじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "家茂", "answers": [ "いえもち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "利奈", "answers": [ "りな" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "土佐", "answers": [ "とさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 4%" },
	{ "question": "大典", "answers": [ "たいてん", "だいすけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 82%, 18%" },
	{ "question": "幸也", "answers": [ "ゆきや", "ゆきなり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "重光", "answers": [ "しげみつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 41%" },
	{ "question": "元親", "answers": [ "もとちか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "啓之", "answers": [ "ひろゆき", "けいゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "紘", "answers": [ "ひろ", "ひろし", "こう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 84%, 12%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "晃之", "answers": [ "てるゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "五朗", "answers": [ "ごろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "憲", "answers": [ "けん", "ホン" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "あさ美", "answers": [ "あさみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "芳子", "answers": [ "よしこ", "ほうし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "真守", "answers": [ "まもる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "愛菜", "answers": [ "まな", "あいな" ], "comment": "Frequency: 46%, 18%" },
	{ "question": "貴文", "answers": [ "たかふみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "文明", "answers": [ "ぶんめい", "ふみあき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 71%, 29%" },
	{ "question": "睦", "answers": [ "むつみ", "あつし", "まこと", "ちかし", "むつき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 31%, 8%, 8%, 5%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "有作", "answers": [ "ゆうさく" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "笠", "answers": [ "りゅう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 3%" },
	{ "question": "紫", "answers": [ "むらさき", "ツィ", "ゆかり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 34%, 34%, 7%" },
	{ "question": "正純", "answers": [ "まさずみ", "まさすみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 90%, 10%" },
	{ "question": "文太", "answers": [ "ぶんた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "秀子", "answers": [ "ひでこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "昭光", "answers": [ "あきみつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "比嘉", "answers": [ "ひが" ], "comment": "Frequency: 3%" },
	{ "question": "喜多", "answers": [ "きた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 3%" },
	{ "question": "喜八", "answers": [ "きはち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "豊明", "answers": [ "ほうめい", "とよあき", "とよあきら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 16%, 11%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "元春", "answers": [ "もとはる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "広志", "answers": [ "ひろし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "晴香", "answers": [ "はるか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "正也", "answers": [ "まさや", "せいや", "ジョンヤ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 67%, 31%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "浩平", "answers": [ "こうへい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "那智", "answers": [ "なち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 91%" },
	{ "question": "治郎", "answers": [ "じろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "新伍", "answers": [ "しんご" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "良輔", "answers": [ "りょうすけ", "よしすけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "萌", "answers": [ "もえ", "はじめ", "ぼう", "もゆ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 80%, 13%, 5%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "武男", "answers": [ "たけお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "大柴", "answers": [ "おおしば" ], "comment": "Frequency: 75%" },
	{ "question": "金村", "answers": [ "かなむら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 11%" },
	{ "question": "登紀子", "answers": [ "ときこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "重雄", "answers": [ "しげお", "しげかつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%, 7%" },
	{ "question": "万里", "answers": [ "ばんり", "まり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 54%, 26%" },
	{ "question": "邦雄", "answers": [ "くにお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "美濃", "answers": [ "みの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 7%" },
	{ "question": "理沙", "answers": [ "りさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "達矢", "answers": [ "たつや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "泰三", "answers": [ "たいぞう", "やすみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 88%, 12%" },
	{ "question": "邦洋", "answers": [ "くにひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "美佐子", "answers": [ "みさこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "マリ子", "answers": [ "まりこ", "マリこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 89%, 11%" },
	{ "question": "知美", "answers": [ "ともみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "大吉", "answers": [ "だいきち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 84%" },
	{ "question": "修平", "answers": [ "しゅうへい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "雅羅", "answers": [ "がら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "美波", "answers": [ "みなみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 28%" },
	{ "question": "紀香", "answers": [ "のりか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "可奈子", "answers": [ "かなこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "千曲", "answers": [ "ちくま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "総一朗", "answers": [ "そういちろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "汪", "answers": [ "ひろし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 4%" },
	{ "question": "嘉", "answers": [ "よし", "か", "よみし", "よしみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 71%, 20%, 6%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "麻里奈", "answers": [ "まりな" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "雅刀", "answers": [ "まさとう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "太朗", "answers": [ "たろう", "たかお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%, 7%" },
	{ "question": "安彦", "answers": [ "やすひこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 27%" },
	{ "question": "夏海", "answers": [ "なつみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 89%" },
	{ "question": "修造", "answers": [ "しゅうぞう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "欽也", "answers": [ "きんや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "洋一郎", "answers": [ "よういちろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "充昭", "answers": [ "みつあき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "敏生", "answers": [ "としき", "としお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 80%, 18%" },
	{ "question": "徳馬", "answers": [ "とくま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "通", "answers": [ "とおる", "どおり", "つう", "とう", "かよう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 58%, 14%, 12%, 5%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "尚史", "answers": [ "しょうじ", "ひさし", "なおふみ", "ひさふみ", "なおし", "たかし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 45%, 26%, 19%, 5%, 2%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "和明", "answers": [ "かずあき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "行方", "answers": [ "ゆきかた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 3%" },
	{ "question": "何", "answers": [ "か" ], "comment": "Frequency: 14%" },
	{ "question": "裕樹", "answers": [ "ひろき", "ゆうき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 69%, 31%" },
	{ "question": "利勝", "answers": [ "としかつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "幸太郎", "answers": [ "こうたろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "赤城", "answers": [ "あかぎ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "華子", "answers": [ "はなこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "佳代子", "answers": [ "かよこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "奈津美", "answers": [ "なつみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "孝太郎", "answers": [ "こうたろう", "たかたろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 91%, 9%" },
	{ "question": "美和子", "answers": [ "みわこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "将大", "answers": [ "まさひろ", "まさとも" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "俊彰", "answers": [ "としあき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "光圀", "answers": [ "みつくに" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "輝彦", "answers": [ "てるひこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "一朗", "answers": [ "いちろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "氏家", "answers": [ "うじいえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 5%" },
	{ "question": "祐実", "answers": [ "ゆみ", "すけざね" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%, 6%" },
	{ "question": "時子", "answers": [ "ときこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "憲次", "answers": [ "けんじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "一機", "answers": [ "かずき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "茉美", "answers": [ "まみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "泰司", "answers": [ "たいじ", "やすし", "やすじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 77%, 19%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "長春", "answers": [ "ちょうしゅん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 20%" },
	{ "question": "六輔", "answers": [ "ろくすけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "央生", "answers": [ "ひさお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "重里", "answers": [ "しげさと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "定家", "answers": [ "さだいえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "邦衛", "answers": [ "くにえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "一美", "answers": [ "かずみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "新太", "answers": [ "あらた", "しんた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 78%, 22%" },
	{ "question": "和光", "answers": [ "かずてる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 5%" },
	{ "question": "夏", "answers": [ "なつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "正次", "answers": [ "しょうじ", "まさつぐ", "まさじ", "せいじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 46%, 39%, 8%, 6%" },
	{ "question": "清之", "answers": [ "きよゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "裕彦", "answers": [ "ひろひこ", "やすひこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 82%, 18%" },
	{ "question": "桂樹", "answers": [ "けいじゅ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "實", "answers": [ "みのる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "奈津子", "answers": [ "なつこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "長久", "answers": [ "ながひさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "美佳子", "answers": [ "みかこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "尚之", "answers": [ "なおゆき", "ひさゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "雅樹", "answers": [ "まさき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "長介", "answers": [ "ちょうすけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "忠一", "answers": [ "ちゅういち", "ただかず", "ただつね" ], "comment": "Frequency: 87%, 10%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "敬二", "answers": [ "けいじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "計", "answers": [ "けい", "はかる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%, 7%" },
	{ "question": "鑑", "answers": [ "あきら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "悠一", "answers": [ "ゆういち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "秀之", "answers": [ "ひでゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "三平", "answers": [ "さんぺい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 90%" },
	{ "question": "奈保子", "answers": [ "なおこ", "なほこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "公康", "answers": [ "きみやす" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "義実", "answers": [ "よしみ", "よしざね", "よしさね" ], "comment": "Frequency: 76%, 21%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "輝政", "answers": [ "てるまさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "武揚", "answers": [ "たけあき", "たけおき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "謙二", "answers": [ "けんじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "公望", "answers": [ "きんもち", "こうぼう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "水城", "answers": [ "みずき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "邑子", "answers": [ "ゆうこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "長治", "answers": [ "ながはる", "ちょうじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "環", "answers": [ "たまき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 83%" },
	{ "question": "忠良", "answers": [ "ただよし", "ちゅうりょう", "ただなが", "ただかた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 47%, 28%, 21%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "義孝", "answers": [ "よしたか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "幸代", "answers": [ "ゆきよ", "さちよ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 89%, 10%" },
	{ "question": "一浩", "answers": [ "かずひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "楓", "answers": [ "かえで" ], "comment": "Frequency: 50%" },
	{ "question": "若葉", "answers": [ "わかば" ], "comment": "Frequency: 23%" },
	{ "question": "康誠", "answers": [ "やすなり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "雅勇", "answers": [ "まさお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "晃嗣", "answers": [ "こうじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "恵介", "answers": [ "けいすけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "郁子", "answers": [ "いくこ", "くにこ", "ゆうこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 86%, 10%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "直弼", "answers": [ "なおすけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "明博", "answers": [ "ミョンバク", "あきひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 76%, 24%" },
	{ "question": "好子", "answers": [ "よしこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "正久", "answers": [ "まさひさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "英太郎", "answers": [ "えいたろう", "ひでたろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 63%, 37%" },
	{ "question": "太地", "answers": [ "たいち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 8%" },
	{ "question": "紅", "answers": [ "くれない", "こう", "べに" ], "comment": "Frequency: 11%, 4%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "清三", "answers": [ "せいぞう", "きよみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%, 7%" },
	{ "question": "弓子", "answers": [ "ゆみこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "光輝", "answers": [ "みつてる", "こうき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "英和", "answers": [ "ひでかず", "ヨンファ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%, 6%" },
	{ "question": "信昭", "answers": [ "のぶあき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "忠信", "answers": [ "ただのぶ", "ちゅうしん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "洋二", "answers": [ "ようじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "麻耶", "answers": [ "まや", "あさや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 79%, 8%" },
	{ "question": "覚", "answers": [ "さとる", "かく" ], "comment": "Frequency: 66%, 19%" },
	{ "question": "匡", "answers": [ "きょう", "ただし", "ただす", "まさし", "たすく" ], "comment": "Frequency: 38%, 21%, 20%, 9%, 7%" },
	{ "question": "哲雄", "answers": [ "てつお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "強", "answers": [ "つよし", "チャン" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "清治", "answers": [ "せいじ", "きよはる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 85%, 13%" },
	{ "question": "南陽", "answers": [ "なんよう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "洪", "answers": [ "こう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 34%" },
	{ "question": "里穂", "answers": [ "りほ", "りお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "総司", "answers": [ "そうじ", "そうし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "宗一郎", "answers": [ "そういちろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "修二", "answers": [ "しゅうじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "源太郎", "answers": [ "げんたろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "克行", "answers": [ "かつゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "正孝", "answers": [ "まさたか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "政明", "answers": [ "まさあき", "まさあきら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%, 7%" },
	{ "question": "宏明", "answers": [ "ひろあき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "獏", "answers": [ "ばく" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "具視", "answers": [ "ともみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "恩来", "answers": [ "おんらい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "由梨", "answers": [ "ゆり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "孝也", "answers": [ "たかや", "こうや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "淳二", "answers": [ "じゅんじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "信康", "answers": [ "のぶやす" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "定信", "answers": [ "さだのぶ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "堅太郎", "answers": [ "けんたろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "義春", "answers": [ "よしはる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "正利", "answers": [ "まさとし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "春子", "answers": [ "はるこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "稔侍", "answers": [ "ねんじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "忠利", "answers": [ "ただとし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "克典", "answers": [ "かつのり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "泉水", "answers": [ "いずみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 90%" },
	{ "question": "結花", "answers": [ "ゆか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "由依", "answers": [ "ゆい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "文男", "answers": [ "ふみお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "昭宏", "answers": [ "あきひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "千", "answers": [ "せん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 11%" },
	{ "question": "康子", "answers": [ "やすこ", "こうこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 79%, 21%" },
	{ "question": "晴美", "answers": [ "はるみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "孜", "answers": [ "つとむ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "湖南", "answers": [ "こなん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 30%" },
	{ "question": "義教", "answers": [ "よしのり", "ぎきょう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "春繁", "answers": [ "はるしげ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "千鶴", "answers": [ "ちづる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "智恵", "answers": [ "ちえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "淳平", "answers": [ "じゅんぺい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "貴一", "answers": [ "きいち", "たかかず" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%, 6%" },
	{ "question": "氏康", "answers": [ "うじやす" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "浩太朗", "answers": [ "こうたろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "ピン子", "answers": [ "ピンこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "梨乃", "answers": [ "りの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "良美", "answers": [ "よしみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "美津子", "answers": [ "みつこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "敏史", "answers": [ "としふみ", "さとし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 73%, 26%" },
	{ "question": "淵", "answers": [ "えん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "安芸", "answers": [ "あき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 3%" },
	{ "question": "美姫", "answers": [ "みき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "富士子", "answers": [ "ふじこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "信忠", "answers": [ "のぶただ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "孝司", "answers": [ "たかし", "こうじ", "こうし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 78%, 17%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "憲治", "answers": [ "けんじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "湊", "answers": [ "みなと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 18%" },
	{ "question": "香里", "answers": [ "かおり", "かほり", "ヒャンリ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 90%, 7%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "富美男", "answers": [ "ふみお", "とみお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 58%, 42%" },
	{ "question": "友子", "answers": [ "ともこ", "ゆうこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 92%, 8%" },
	{ "question": "精三", "answers": [ "せいぞう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "吉", "answers": [ "きつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 13%" },
	{ "question": "洋孝", "answers": [ "ひろたか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "信成", "answers": [ "のぶなり", "のぶしげ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 74%, 26%" },
	{ "question": "隆景", "answers": [ "たかかげ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "松陰", "answers": [ "しょういん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "亜樹", "answers": [ "あき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 68%" },
	{ "question": "義彦", "answers": [ "よしひこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "浩市", "answers": [ "こういち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "惇", "answers": [ "あつし", "とん", "じゅん", "つとむ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 45%, 33%, 18%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "仲", "answers": [ "ちゅう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 13%" },
	{ "question": "龍平", "answers": [ "りゅうへい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "晴明", "answers": [ "せいめい", "はるあき", "せいまん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 75%, 19%, 6%" },
	{ "question": "健作", "answers": [ "けんさく" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "一幸", "answers": [ "かずゆき", "いっこう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 76%, 24%" },
	{ "question": "伊代", "answers": [ "いよ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "真由", "answers": [ "まゆ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "宣長", "answers": [ "のりなが" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "章介", "answers": [ "しょうすけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "みな実", "answers": [ "みなみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "長英", "answers": [ "ちょうえい", "ながふさ", "ながひで" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%, 2%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "錦之介", "answers": [ "きんのすけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "道大", "answers": [ "みちひろ", "みちおお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%, 6%" },
	{ "question": "輝男", "answers": [ "てるお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "十郎", "answers": [ "じゅうろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "欽隆", "answers": [ "きんりゅう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "優奈", "answers": [ "ゆうな", "ゆな" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "真樹", "answers": [ "まき", "まさき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 53%, 19%" },
	{ "question": "彪", "answers": [ "たけし", "ひょう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 72%, 28%" },
	{ "question": "良二", "answers": [ "りょうじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "梨加", "answers": [ "りか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "光洋", "answers": [ "こうよう", "みつひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 64%, 36%" },
	{ "question": "義重", "answers": [ "よししげ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "裕志", "answers": [ "ゆうじ", "ひろし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 73%, 27%" },
	{ "question": "雅", "answers": [ "みやび", "まさし", "ただし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 52%, 30%, 7%" },
	{ "question": "みつ子", "answers": [ "みつこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "浩介", "answers": [ "こうすけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "兼太", "answers": [ "かねた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "一騎", "answers": [ "いっき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "重盛", "answers": [ "しげもり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 51%" },
	{ "question": "雪野", "answers": [ "ゆきの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 3%" },
	{ "question": "秀典", "answers": [ "ひでのり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "秀俊", "answers": [ "ひでとし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "武敏", "answers": [ "たけとし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "羽", "answers": [ "う" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "博太郎", "answers": [ "ひろたろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "千絵", "answers": [ "ちえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "義央", "answers": [ "よしひさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "未祐", "answers": [ "みゆ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "白秋", "answers": [ "はくしゅう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "希林", "answers": [ "きりん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "久作", "answers": [ "きゅうさく" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "雷太", "answers": [ "らいた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "史之", "answers": [ "ふみゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "久光", "answers": [ "ひさみつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%" },
	{ "question": "鉄男", "answers": [ "てつお", "かねお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "千恵蔵", "answers": [ "ちえぞう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "伸一郎", "answers": [ "しんいちろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "勇紀", "answers": [ "ゆうき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "延年", "answers": [ "のぶとし", "えんねん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%, 7%" },
	{ "question": "富三郎", "answers": [ "とみさぶろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "秀平", "answers": [ "しゅうへい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "将司", "answers": [ "まさし", "しょうじ", "まさよし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 77%, 14%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "秀人", "answers": [ "ひでと", "しゅうと", "ひでひと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 90%, 6%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "梢", "answers": [ "こずえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 91%" },
	{ "question": "巨泉", "answers": [ "きょせん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "留美子", "answers": [ "るみこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "瑠美", "answers": [ "るみ", "るび" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "芳正", "answers": [ "よしまさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "美佐", "answers": [ "みさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "直義", "answers": [ "ただよし", "なおよし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 91%, 9%" },
	{ "question": "迅", "answers": [ "じん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "信太郎", "answers": [ "しんたろう", "のぶたろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%, 7%" },
	{ "question": "謙次郎", "answers": [ "けんじろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "彩夏", "answers": [ "あやか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%" },
	{ "question": "菜摘", "answers": [ "なつみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "貴博", "answers": [ "たかひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "慎一郎", "answers": [ "しんいちろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "敦夫", "answers": [ "あつお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "余", "answers": [ "よ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 6%" },
	{ "question": "義晴", "answers": [ "よしはる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "義輝", "answers": [ "よしてる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "有香", "answers": [ "ゆか", "ゆうか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "将之", "answers": [ "まさゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "秀信", "answers": [ "ひでのぶ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "秀章", "answers": [ "ひであき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "荘", "answers": [ "そう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 7%" },
	{ "question": "岩男", "answers": [ "いわお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 13%" },
	{ "question": "光彦", "answers": [ "てるひこ", "みつひこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 71%, 29%" },
	{ "question": "子規", "answers": [ "しき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "窈", "answers": [ "よう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "清彦", "answers": [ "きよひこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "真千子", "answers": [ "まちこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "実朝", "answers": [ "さねとも" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "奈緒美", "answers": [ "なおみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "郁也", "answers": [ "いくや", "ふみや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 92%, 8%" },
	{ "question": "良夫", "answers": [ "よしお", "りょうふ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "素子", "answers": [ "もとこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "宗男", "answers": [ "むねお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "美穂子", "answers": [ "みほこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "春奈", "answers": [ "はるな" ], "comment": "Frequency: 92%" },
	{ "question": "勝之", "answers": [ "かつゆき", "しょうし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "克久", "answers": [ "かつひさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "猪四郎", "answers": [ "いしろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "槇", "answers": [ "まき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 3%" },
	{ "question": "良純", "answers": [ "よしずみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "菜々子", "answers": [ "ななこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "沙苗", "answers": [ "さなえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "和代", "answers": [ "かずよ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "勇気", "answers": [ "ゆうき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 90%" },
	{ "question": "裕一郎", "answers": [ "ゆういちろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "万作", "answers": [ "まんさく", "ばんさく" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "伸夫", "answers": [ "のぶお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "信次", "answers": [ "しんじ", "のぶつぐ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 83%, 17%" },
	{ "question": "家治", "answers": [ "いえはる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "近江", "answers": [ "おうみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 6%" },
	{ "question": "忠彦", "answers": [ "ただひこ", "たださと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "温", "answers": [ "おん", "あつし", "ならう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 33%, 11%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "久弥", "answers": [ "ひさや", "きゅうや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 49%, 44%" },
	{ "question": "俊作", "answers": [ "しゅんさく" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "謙治", "answers": [ "けんじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "一馬", "answers": [ "かずま", "はじめ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 90%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "美沙", "answers": [ "みさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "貴司", "answers": [ "たかし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%" },
	{ "question": "左京", "answers": [ "さきょう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "弘毅", "answers": [ "こうき", "ひろあき", "ひろき", "ひろたけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 85%, 8%, 5%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "彩花", "answers": [ "あやか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 72%" },
	{ "question": "角", "answers": [ "かく" ], "comment": "Frequency: 20%" },
	{ "question": "博樹", "answers": [ "ひろき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "秀郷", "answers": [ "ひでさと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "達朗", "answers": [ "たつろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "精一", "answers": [ "せいいち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "士郎", "answers": [ "しろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 65%" },
	{ "question": "亮介", "answers": [ "りょうすけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "正種", "answers": [ "まさね", "まさたね" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "毅彦", "answers": [ "たけひこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "有明", "answers": [ "ありあけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 9%" },
	{ "question": "翔平", "answers": [ "しょうへい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "英美里", "answers": [ "えみり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "諒", "answers": [ "りょう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "治子", "answers": [ "はるこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "大三郎", "answers": [ "だいざぶろう", "だいさぶろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 62%, 38%" },
	{ "question": "田村麻呂", "answers": [ "たむらまろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "辰爾", "answers": [ "たつみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "心", "answers": [ "しん", "こころ", "のぞみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 55%, 23%, 18%" },
	{ "question": "禎一", "answers": [ "さだかず", "ていいち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 86%, 14%" },
	{ "question": "利一", "answers": [ "りいち", "としかず" ], "comment": "Frequency: 92%, 8%" },
	{ "question": "珍化", "answers": [ "ちんふぁ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "正臣", "answers": [ "まさおみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "官九郎", "answers": [ "かんくろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "創路", "answers": [ "いつじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "広野", "answers": [ "ひろの", "こうや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 8%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "政樹", "answers": [ "まさき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "伸行", "answers": [ "のぶゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "知憲", "answers": [ "ともあき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "忠恒", "answers": [ "ただつね" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "弘治", "answers": [ "こうじ", "ひろはる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "賢太郎", "answers": [ "けんたろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "京太郎", "answers": [ "きょうたろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "綾乃", "answers": [ "あやの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%" },
	{ "question": "容子", "answers": [ "ようこ", "まさこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%, 7%" },
	{ "question": "未央", "answers": [ "みお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "信秀", "answers": [ "のぶひで" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "信明", "answers": [ "のぶあき", "のぶあきら", "しんめい", "さねあきら", "のぶはる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 59%, 23%, 10%, 5%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "知宏", "answers": [ "ともひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "雪", "answers": [ "せつ", "きよし", "ゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 50%, 27%, 23%" },
	{ "question": "一葉", "answers": [ "いちよう", "かずは", "ひとは", "いよ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 88%, 5%, 3%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "秋吉", "answers": [ "しゅうきち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 6%" },
	{ "question": "英寿", "answers": [ "ひでとし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "寿明", "answers": [ "としあき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "達", "answers": [ "とおる", "たつ", "たつし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 47%, 33%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "顕", "answers": [ "けん", "あきら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 68%, 32%" },
	{ "question": "佳孝", "answers": [ "よしたか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "秀政", "answers": [ "ひでまさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "兆銘", "answers": [ "ちょうめい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "健人", "answers": [ "けんと", "たけひと", "たてひと", "はやと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 84%, 12%, 2%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "啓司", "answers": [ "けいじ", "けいし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 89%, 11%" },
	{ "question": "明乃", "answers": [ "あけの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 89%" },
	{ "question": "雅朗", "answers": [ "まさあき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "哲三", "answers": [ "てつぞう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "孝幸", "answers": [ "たかゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "昭子", "answers": [ "あきこ", "しょうこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "元司", "answers": [ "もとし", "もとじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 87%, 13%" },
	{ "question": "満里奈", "answers": [ "まりな" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "将門", "answers": [ "まさかど" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "久男", "answers": [ "ひさお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "珠緒", "answers": [ "たまお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "太陽", "answers": [ "たいよう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "恭平", "answers": [ "きょうへい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "由布", "answers": [ "ゆう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 7%" },
	{ "question": "正恭", "answers": [ "まさやす", "せいきょう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "忠次", "answers": [ "ただつぐ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "弘、", "answers": [ "ひろし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "健二郎", "answers": [ "けんじろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "朱音", "answers": [ "あかね" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%" },
	{ "question": "隆弘", "answers": [ "たかひろ", "りゅうこう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "主浩", "answers": [ "かづひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "育子", "answers": [ "いくこ", "やすこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 92%, 8%" },
	{ "question": "安奈", "answers": [ "あんな" ], "comment": "Frequency: 60%" },
	{ "question": "芳恵", "answers": [ "よしえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "光央", "answers": [ "みつお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "史朗", "answers": [ "しろう", "ふみあき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "耕筰", "answers": [ "こうさく" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "兼続", "answers": [ "かねつぐ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "路子", "answers": [ "みちこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "真帆", "answers": [ "まほ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "智浩", "answers": [ "ともひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "忠男", "answers": [ "ただお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "孝明", "answers": [ "たかあき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "精二", "answers": [ "せいじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "幾三", "answers": [ "いくぞう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "敦士", "answers": [ "あつし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "伸之", "answers": [ "のぶゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "吟", "answers": [ "ぎん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "伊織", "answers": [ "いおり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "彭", "answers": [ "ほう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 9%" },
	{ "question": "凛", "answers": [ "りん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "元信", "answers": [ "もとのぶ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "融", "answers": [ "とおる", "ゆう", "あきら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 46%, 41%, 13%" },
	{ "question": "慎司", "answers": [ "しんじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "敬一", "answers": [ "けいいち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "一哉", "answers": [ "かずや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "博明", "answers": [ "ひろあき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "奈々子", "answers": [ "ななこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "卓志", "answers": [ "たくし", "たかし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 82%, 18%" },
	{ "question": "茂徳", "answers": [ "しげのり", "もちなが" ], "comment": "Frequency: 84%, 15%" },
	{ "question": "沈", "answers": [ "しん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 11%" },
	{ "question": "長矩", "answers": [ "ながのり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "謙一", "answers": [ "けんいち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "圭二", "answers": [ "けいじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "響子", "answers": [ "きょうこ", "きょおこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 82%, 18%" },
	{ "question": "英三", "answers": [ "えいぞう", "ひでみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%, 6%" },
	{ "question": "義朝", "answers": [ "よしとも" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "良枝", "answers": [ "よしえ", "ヤンジ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%, 6%" },
	{ "question": "陽平", "answers": [ "ようへい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "雅弓", "answers": [ "まゆみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "憲武", "answers": [ "のりたけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "鷹志", "answers": [ "たかし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "浩次", "answers": [ "こうじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "和希", "answers": [ "かずき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 53%" },
	{ "question": "正煕", "answers": [ "チョンヒ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "曜子", "answers": [ "ようこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "敏文", "answers": [ "としふみ", "としぶみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%, 6%" },
	{ "question": "佑", "answers": [ "たすく", "ゆう", "ゆたか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 66%, 31%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "良明", "answers": [ "よしあき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "大士", "answers": [ "ひろし", "たいし", "だいし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 77%, 19%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "信男", "answers": [ "のぶお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "直己", "answers": [ "なおみ", "なおき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 78%, 22%" },
	{ "question": "忠明", "answers": [ "ただあき", "ただあきら", "ちゅうめい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 51%, 37%, 12%" },
	{ "question": "家慶", "answers": [ "いえよし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "双葉", "answers": [ "ふたば", "そうよう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 7%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "幸生", "answers": [ "ゆきお", "こうせい", "さちお", "さきお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 80%, 8%, 8%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "建三", "answers": [ "けんぞう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "龍司", "answers": [ "りゅうじ", "りゅうし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "康男", "answers": [ "やすお", "こうなん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "正直", "answers": [ "まさなお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "紀行", "answers": [ "のりゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "忠司", "answers": [ "ちゅうじ", "ただし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 63%, 37%" },
	{ "question": "大祐", "answers": [ "だいすけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "能収", "answers": [ "よしかず" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "演之", "answers": [ "のぶゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "長秀", "answers": [ "ながひで" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "千種", "answers": [ "ちぐさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 43%" },
	{ "question": "六郎", "answers": [ "ろくろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "涼介", "answers": [ "りょうすけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "基", "answers": [ "もとい", "はじめ", "き" ], "comment": "Frequency: 46%, 12%, 9%" },
	{ "question": "正憲", "answers": [ "まさのり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "陽菜", "answers": [ "はるな", "ひな" ], "comment": "Frequency: 79%, 21%" },
	{ "question": "倫子", "answers": [ "のりこ", "りんこ", "りんし", "ともこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 62%, 14%, 13%, 9%" },
	{ "question": "徳", "answers": [ "とく" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%" },
	{ "question": "美由紀", "answers": [ "みゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "荷風", "answers": [ "かふう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "朝香", "answers": [ "あさか", "ともか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 67%, 10%" },
	{ "question": "昭仁", "answers": [ "あきひと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "吉彦", "answers": [ "よしひこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%" },
	{ "question": "卓郎", "answers": [ "たくろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "正剛", "answers": [ "せいごう", "しょうご", "まさかた", "まさよし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 81%, 15%, 3%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "盛", "answers": [ "せい", "さかり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 13%, 13%" },
	{ "question": "要一", "answers": [ "よういち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "久秀", "answers": [ "ひさひで" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "友幸", "answers": [ "ともゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "俊博", "answers": [ "としひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "忠敬", "answers": [ "ただたか", "ただのり", "ただひろ", "ただゆき", "ただよし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 76%, 10%, 5%, 5%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "一豊", "answers": [ "かつとよ", "かずとよ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 83%, 17%" },
	{ "question": "廉", "answers": [ "れん", "きよし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 85%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "洋輔", "answers": [ "ようすけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "正己", "answers": [ "まさみ", "まさき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 86%, 14%" },
	{ "question": "信吉", "answers": [ "のぶよし", "しんきち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 70%, 29%" },
	{ "question": "忠成", "answers": [ "ただなり", "ただあきら", "ただしげ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 77%, 18%, 6%" },
	{ "question": "末広", "answers": [ "すえひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 53%" },
	{ "question": "信三", "answers": [ "しんぞう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "義興", "answers": [ "よしおき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "佑介", "answers": [ "ゆうすけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "満男", "answers": [ "みつお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "成実", "answers": [ "なみ", "しげざね" ], "comment": "Frequency: 71%, 29%" },
	{ "question": "幹", "answers": [ "かん", "もとい", "みき", "もとき", "つよし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 40%, 26%, 19%, 6%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "羽衣", "answers": [ "うい", "はごろも" ], "comment": "Frequency: 68%, 8%" },
	{ "question": "五十鈴", "answers": [ "いすず" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%" },
	{ "question": "淳史", "answers": [ "あつし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "美輪", "answers": [ "みわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "大城", "answers": [ "テソン" ], "comment": "Frequency: 3%" },
	{ "question": "麻弥", "answers": [ "まや", "まみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 83%, 17%" },
	{ "question": "正晴", "answers": [ "まさはる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "秀成", "answers": [ "ひでなり", "ひでしげ", "しゅうせい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 77%, 12%, 11%" },
	{ "question": "丕", "answers": [ "ひ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "達哉", "answers": [ "たつや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "康太", "answers": [ "こうた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "頼房", "answers": [ "よりふさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "希典", "answers": [ "まれすけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "斉昭", "answers": [ "なりあき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "重吉", "answers": [ "じゅうきち", "しげよし", "ちょうきち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 87%, 8%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "義徳", "answers": [ "よしのり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "光宏", "answers": [ "みつひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "裕史", "answers": [ "ひろふみ", "ひろし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 71%, 29%" },
	{ "question": "高虎", "answers": [ "たかとら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "家宣", "answers": [ "いえのぶ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "涼香", "answers": [ "りょうか", "さやか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "莽", "answers": [ "もう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "牧子", "answers": [ "まきこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "房之助", "answers": [ "ふさのすけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "千穂", "answers": [ "ちほ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "貴雄", "answers": [ "たかお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "紳一郎", "answers": [ "しんいちろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "昭如", "answers": [ "あきゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "善之", "answers": [ "よしゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "佑樹", "answers": [ "ゆうき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "友", "answers": [ "ゆう", "とも" ], "comment": "Frequency: 74%, 23%" },
	{ "question": "美奈", "answers": [ "みな" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "一仁", "answers": [ "かずひと", "かつひと", "かずと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 90%, 8%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "優木", "answers": [ "ゆうき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 3%" },
	{ "question": "班", "answers": [ "はん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 6%" },
	{ "question": "瀬奈", "answers": [ "せな" ], "comment": "Frequency: 20%" },
	{ "question": "信幸", "answers": [ "のぶゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "伸郎", "answers": [ "のぶお", "のぶろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 58%, 42%" },
	{ "question": "絢子", "answers": [ "じゅんこ", "あやこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 64%, 36%" },
	{ "question": "英孝", "answers": [ "えいこう", "ひでたか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 82%, 18%" },
	{ "question": "高久", "answers": [ "たかひさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 29%" },
	{ "question": "伊能", "answers": [ "いのう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 6%" },
	{ "question": "正澄", "answers": [ "まさずみ", "まさすみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 91%, 9%" },
	{ "question": "高広", "answers": [ "たかひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "進也", "answers": [ "しんや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "要次", "answers": [ "ようじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "南朋", "answers": [ "なお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "超", "answers": [ "ちょう", "すすむ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 81%, 6%" },
	{ "question": "忠志", "answers": [ "ただし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "和寿", "answers": [ "かずとし", "かずひさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 89%, 11%" },
	{ "question": "明奈", "answers": [ "あきな" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "敏満", "answers": [ "としみつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "俊英", "answers": [ "としひで", "しゅんえい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "澄子", "answers": [ "すみこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "昇一", "answers": [ "しょういち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "紹", "answers": [ "しょう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "幸四郎", "answers": [ "こうしろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "賈", "answers": [ "か" ], "comment": "Frequency: 9%" },
	{ "question": "雄司", "answers": [ "ゆうじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "光博", "answers": [ "みつひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "政長", "answers": [ "まさなが" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "岬", "answers": [ "みさき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 7%" },
	{ "question": "鳴海", "answers": [ "なるみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 5%" },
	{ "question": "善臣", "answers": [ "よしとみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "眞弓", "answers": [ "まゆみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "春雄", "answers": [ "はるお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "隆明", "answers": [ "たかあき", "りゅうめい", "たかあきら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 86%, 10%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "州和", "answers": [ "くにかず" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "金太郎", "answers": [ "きんたろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "清美", "answers": [ "きよみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "家定", "answers": [ "いえさだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "祐輔", "answers": [ "ゆうすけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "智秋", "answers": [ "ちあき", "ともあき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 92%, 8%" },
	{ "question": "英志", "answers": [ "えいじ", "えいし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "宮", "answers": [ "きゅう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 21%" },
	{ "question": "聖人", "answers": [ "まさと", "しかと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 91%, 9%" },
	{ "question": "貞之助", "answers": [ "ていのすけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "忠之", "answers": [ "ただゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "英介", "answers": [ "えいすけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "香月", "answers": [ "かづき", "こうげつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 5%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "直太朗", "answers": [ "なおたろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "隆範", "answers": [ "たかのり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "征爾", "answers": [ "せいじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "紅葉", "answers": [ "こうよう", "もみじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 53%, 41%" },
	{ "question": "亮平", "answers": [ "りょうへい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "蓉子", "answers": [ "ようこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "成一", "answers": [ "まさかず", "せいいち", "しげかず" ], "comment": "Frequency: 67%, 26%, 7%" },
	{ "question": "紀之", "answers": [ "のりゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "鏡花", "answers": [ "きょうか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "克洋", "answers": [ "かつひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "正典", "answers": [ "まさのり", "しょうすけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 75%, 24%" },
	{ "question": "淳之介", "answers": [ "じゅんのすけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "幹二朗", "answers": [ "みきじろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "達彦", "answers": [ "たつひこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "加奈", "answers": [ "かな" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "義直", "answers": [ "よしなお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "菜桜子", "answers": [ "なおこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "頼義", "answers": [ "よりよし", "よりちか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 84%, 16%" },
	{ "question": "隆博", "answers": [ "たかひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "善太郎", "answers": [ "ぜんたろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "出", "answers": [ "いずる", "いづる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 85%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "良三", "answers": [ "りょうぞう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "さと子", "answers": [ "さとこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "恭兵", "answers": [ "きょうへい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "絵理子", "answers": [ "えりこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "全", "answers": [ "たもつ", "ぜん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "圭右", "answers": [ "けいすけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "喜三郎", "answers": [ "きさぶろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "莉乃", "answers": [ "りの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "優香", "answers": [ "ゆうか", "ゆか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 75%, 23%" },
	{ "question": "泰幸", "answers": [ "やすゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "博也", "answers": [ "ひろや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "春彦", "answers": [ "はるひこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "知幸", "answers": [ "ともゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "聖一", "answers": [ "せいいち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "彩奈", "answers": [ "あやな", "りな" ], "comment": "Frequency: 92%, 8%" },
	{ "question": "亜衣", "answers": [ "あい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "安元", "answers": [ "やすもと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 8%" },
	{ "question": "佳乃", "answers": [ "よしの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "布", "answers": [ "ふ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 88%" },
	{ "question": "乃梨子", "answers": [ "のりこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "尚樹", "answers": [ "なおき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "照之", "answers": [ "てるゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "大悟", "answers": [ "だいご", "たいご" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%, 6%" },
	{ "question": "誠也", "answers": [ "せいや", "しげなり", "まさや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 91%, 5%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "彰晃", "answers": [ "しょうこう", "あきてる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 92%, 8%" },
	{ "question": "康嗣", "answers": [ "こうじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "憲史", "answers": [ "けんし", "けんじ", "のりひと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 47%, 38%, 13%" },
	{ "question": "貴理子", "answers": [ "きりこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "孟", "answers": [ "はじめ", "つとむ", "もう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 29%, 15%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "賢次", "answers": [ "けんじ", "ともつぐ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "錦濤", "answers": [ "きんとう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "栄二", "answers": [ "えいじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "沢", "answers": [ "たく" ], "comment": "Frequency: 5%" },
	{ "question": "洋文", "answers": [ "ひろふみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "千広", "answers": [ "ちひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "貴教", "answers": [ "たかのり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "順治", "answers": [ "じゅんじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "七郎", "answers": [ "しちろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "孝平", "answers": [ "こうへい", "たかひら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 89%, 11%" },
	{ "question": "耕平", "answers": [ "こうへい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "友一", "answers": [ "ゆういち", "ともかず", "ともいち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 68%, 21%, 11%" },
	{ "question": "智人", "answers": [ "のりと", "ともひと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 85%, 15%" },
	{ "question": "信弘", "answers": [ "のぶひろ", "としひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "輝雄", "answers": [ "てるお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "岳夫", "answers": [ "たけお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "孝男", "answers": [ "たかお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "小五郎", "answers": [ "こごろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "石", "answers": [ "せき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 11%" },
	{ "question": "梨華", "answers": [ "りか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "美優", "answers": [ "みゆ", "みゆう", "みゅう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 41%, 33%, 21%" },
	{ "question": "正平", "answers": [ "しょうへい", "まさひら", "せいへい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 92%, 7%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "右近", "answers": [ "うこん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 89%" },
	{ "question": "彩陽", "answers": [ "あやひ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "巴", "answers": [ "ともえ", "は" ], "comment": "Frequency: 49%, 6%" },
	{ "question": "愛里", "answers": [ "あいり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 84%" },
	{ "question": "麻友", "answers": [ "まゆ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "忠久", "answers": [ "ただひさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "伸治", "answers": [ "しんじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "逸郎", "answers": [ "いつろう", "いつお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 89%, 11%" },
	{ "question": "敦彦", "answers": [ "あつひこ", "とんげん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "祐穂", "answers": [ "ゆうほ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%" },
	{ "question": "智樹", "answers": [ "ともき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "哲生", "answers": [ "てつお", "てつせい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "俊三", "answers": [ "しゅんぞう", "しゅんみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "克夫", "answers": [ "かつお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "香山", "answers": [ "こうざん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 4%" },
	{ "question": "弘也", "answers": [ "ひろなり", "ひろや", "こうや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 84%, 14%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "秀治", "answers": [ "ひではる", "ひでじ", "しゅうじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 72%, 15%, 13%" },
	{ "question": "三吉", "answers": [ "さんきち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 67%" },
	{ "question": "謙介", "answers": [ "けんすけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "快", "answers": [ "かい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "木の実", "answers": [ "このみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 22%" },
	{ "question": "勇樹", "answers": [ "ゆうき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "美菜子", "answers": [ "みなこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "将也", "answers": [ "まさや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "洋貴", "answers": [ "ひろき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "康平", "answers": [ "こうへい", "やすひら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "政人", "answers": [ "まさと", "まさひと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "裕紀", "answers": [ "ひろき", "ゆうき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 89%, 9%" },
	{ "question": "久義", "answers": [ "ひさよし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "直行", "answers": [ "なおゆき", "なおつら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "昌", "answers": [ "しょう", "まさる", "まさ", "あきら", "まさし", "さかえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 29%, 18%, 16%, 15%, 11%, 8%" },
	{ "question": "三四郎", "answers": [ "さんしろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "連太郎", "answers": [ "れんたろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "秀康", "answers": [ "ひでやす" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "忠英", "answers": [ "ちゅうえい", "ただてる", "ただひで", "ただふさ", "ただつね" ], "comment": "Frequency: 55%, 21%, 13%, 9%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "隆雄", "answers": [ "たかお", "たかかず" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "修介", "answers": [ "しゅうすけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "秀", "answers": [ "しゅう", "ひいず", "すぐる", "ひで", "しげる", "ひいで" ], "comment": "Frequency: 76%, 7%, 6%, 3%, 2%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "若尾", "answers": [ "わかお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 3%" },
	{ "question": "史", "answers": [ "ふみ", "あや", "ひろし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 41%, 10%, 7%" },
	{ "question": "日出子", "answers": [ "ひでこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "秀家", "answers": [ "ひでいえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "耕太郎", "answers": [ "こうたろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "建太", "answers": [ "けんた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "氏郷", "answers": [ "うじさと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "義詮", "answers": [ "よしあきら", "ぎせん", "よしあき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 86%, 12%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "洋司", "answers": [ "ようじ", "ひろし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 72%, 28%" },
	{ "question": "康文", "answers": [ "やすふみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "秀昭", "answers": [ "ひであき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "工", "answers": [ "たくみ", "こう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "左千夫", "answers": [ "さちお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "小次郎", "answers": [ "こじろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "一弘", "answers": [ "かずひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "亜季", "answers": [ "あき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "ルリ子", "answers": [ "ルリこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "のり平", "answers": [ "のりへい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "俊道", "answers": [ "としみち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "静子", "answers": [ "しずこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "篤郎", "answers": [ "あつろう", "とくろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 75%, 24%" },
	{ "question": "政一", "answers": [ "まさかず", "まさいち", "せいいち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 59%, 30%, 11%" },
	{ "question": "沙紀", "answers": [ "さき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "一久", "answers": [ "かずひさ", "いっきゅう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 87%, 13%" },
	{ "question": "巽", "answers": [ "たつみ", "そん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 24%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "恵理子", "answers": [ "えりこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "雅文", "answers": [ "まさふみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "鶴光", "answers": [ "つるこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "紗季", "answers": [ "さき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "圭司", "answers": [ "けいじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "英治郎", "answers": [ "えいじろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "尚己", "answers": [ "なおみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "豊彦", "answers": [ "とよひこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "利治", "answers": [ "としはる", "としじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "和香", "answers": [ "わか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "康生", "answers": [ "やすお", "こうせい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 66%, 34%" },
	{ "question": "昌之", "answers": [ "まさゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "雅裕", "answers": [ "まさひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "允", "answers": [ "まこと", "いん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 66%, 34%" },
	{ "question": "伸旺", "answers": [ "のぶお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "忠通", "answers": [ "ただみち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "忠直", "answers": [ "ただなお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "孟紀", "answers": [ "たけのり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "慎之助", "answers": [ "しんのすけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "佳代", "answers": [ "かよ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "龍山", "answers": [ "りゅうざん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 6%" },
	{ "question": "一路", "answers": [ "いちろ", "いつみち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 35%, 19%" },
	{ "question": "遼一", "answers": [ "りょういち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "悠子", "answers": [ "ゆうこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "靖彦", "answers": [ "やすひこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "恒", "answers": [ "ひさし", "ゆずる", "こう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 76%, 12%, 12%" },
	{ "question": "周一郎", "answers": [ "しゅういちろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "錦司", "answers": [ "きんじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "かな恵", "answers": [ "かなえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "悦司", "answers": [ "えつし", "えつじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "梨絵", "answers": [ "りえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "結子", "answers": [ "ゆうこ", "ゆいこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 92%, 8%" },
	{ "question": "康陽", "answers": [ "やすはる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "美也子", "answers": [ "みやこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "美登里", "answers": [ "みどり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "光明", "answers": [ "みつあき", "こうめい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 39%, 21%" },
	{ "question": "正実", "answers": [ "まさみ", "まさざね" ], "comment": "Frequency: 89%, 11%" },
	{ "question": "千晶", "answers": [ "ちあき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%" },
	{ "question": "純也", "answers": [ "じゅんや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "咲子", "answers": [ "さきこ", "しょうこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "花音", "answers": [ "かのん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "和典", "answers": [ "かずのり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "郁", "answers": [ "かおる", "いく", "いくお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 68%, 21%, 9%" },
	{ "question": "日明", "answers": [ "あきら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "承晩", "answers": [ "スンマン" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "英俊", "answers": [ "ひでとし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "千鶴子", "answers": [ "ちづこ", "ちずこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 81%, 19%" },
	{ "question": "高廣", "answers": [ "たかひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "圭太", "answers": [ "けいた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "鴨", "answers": [ "かも" ], "comment": "Frequency: 52%" },
	{ "question": "勝之祐", "answers": [ "かつのすけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "芳太郎", "answers": [ "よしたろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "広務", "answers": [ "ひろむ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "那奈", "answers": [ "なな" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "晋一郎", "answers": [ "しんいちろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "伊玖磨", "answers": [ "いくま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "芳郎", "answers": [ "よしろう", "よしお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "成政", "answers": [ "なりまさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "泰明", "answers": [ "やすあき", "たいめい", "ひろあき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 59%, 36%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "美枝子", "answers": [ "みえこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "恭介", "answers": [ "きょうすけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "雅司", "answers": [ "まさし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "亘輝", "answers": [ "のぶてる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "東洋", "answers": [ "とうよう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 59%" },
	{ "question": "豊山", "answers": [ "ぶざん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 4%" },
	{ "question": "行長", "answers": [ "ゆきなが" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "宗光", "answers": [ "むねみつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "幹久", "answers": [ "みきひさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "万太郎", "answers": [ "まんたろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "雅博", "answers": [ "まさひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "政則", "answers": [ "まさのり", "せいそく" ], "comment": "Frequency: 76%, 24%" },
	{ "question": "政伸", "answers": [ "まさのぶ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "秀長", "answers": [ "ひでなが" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "富市", "answers": [ "とみいち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "進歩", "answers": [ "すすむ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "愛理", "answers": [ "えり", "あいり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 82%, 18%" },
	{ "question": "洋之", "answers": [ "ひろゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "英昭", "answers": [ "ひであき", "えいしょう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "貴裕", "answers": [ "たかひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "重慶", "answers": [ "しげよし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "祥雄", "answers": [ "さちお", "よしお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%, 7%" },
	{ "question": "康一", "answers": [ "こういち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "雲", "answers": [ "うん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "日出", "answers": [ "ひで", "イルチュル" ], "comment": "Frequency: 6%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "初音", "answers": [ "はつね" ], "comment": "Frequency: 35%" },
	{ "question": "武鉉", "answers": [ "ムヒョン" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "由里", "answers": [ "ゆり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "靖夫", "answers": [ "やすお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "真夜", "answers": [ "まよ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "千佳", "answers": [ "ちか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "建夫", "answers": [ "たけお", "たてお", "ゆきお", "たつお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 64%, 26%, 6%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "隆寛", "answers": [ "たかひろ", "たかのぶ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "幸季", "answers": [ "こうき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "陸奥", "answers": [ "むつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "道哉", "answers": [ "みちや", "ゆきや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 84%, 16%" },
	{ "question": "興", "answers": [ "こう", "しげる", "おこる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 68%, 29%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "由奈", "answers": [ "ゆな" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "由樹", "answers": [ "ゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "範子", "answers": [ "のりこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "達幸", "answers": [ "たっこう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "重政", "answers": [ "しげまさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 77%" },
	{ "question": "京香", "answers": [ "きょうか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "勝太郎", "answers": [ "かつたろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "政行", "answers": [ "まさゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "眞一", "answers": [ "しんいち", "みちかず" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%, 6%" },
	{ "question": "康範", "answers": [ "こうはん", "やすのり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 80%, 20%" },
	{ "question": "朱未", "answers": [ "あけみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "長慶", "answers": [ "ながよし", "ちょうけい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "忠相", "answers": [ "ただすけ", "ただみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "耕三", "answers": [ "こうぞう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "公次", "answers": [ "こうじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "勝利", "answers": [ "かつとし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "一茂", "answers": [ "かずしげ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "恵理", "answers": [ "えり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "義勝", "answers": [ "よしかつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "小春", "answers": [ "こはる", "シウチョン" ], "comment": "Frequency: 90%, 6%" },
	{ "question": "恵里菜", "answers": [ "えりな" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "涼成", "answers": [ "りょうせい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "由利加", "answers": [ "ゆりか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "昌樹", "answers": [ "まさき", "あつき", "もとき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 52%, 43%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "浩輝", "answers": [ "ひろき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "のぶ代", "answers": [ "のぶよ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "信友", "answers": [ "のぶとも" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "健吾", "answers": [ "けんご" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "義景", "answers": [ "よしかげ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "幸広", "answers": [ "ゆきひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "敏和", "answers": [ "としかず" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "哲太", "answers": [ "てった" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "信治", "answers": [ "しんじ", "のぶはる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 81%, 19%" },
	{ "question": "静雄", "answers": [ "しずお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "憲二", "answers": [ "けんじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "勝成", "answers": [ "かつなり", "かつしげ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 90%, 10%" },
	{ "question": "昭博", "answers": [ "あきひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "由利", "answers": [ "ゆり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 6%" },
	{ "question": "春野", "answers": [ "はるの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 7%" },
	{ "question": "大海", "answers": [ "ひろみ", "たいかい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 56%, 13%" },
	{ "question": "浩紀", "answers": [ "ひろき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "利光", "answers": [ "としみつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 59%" },
	{ "question": "辰吾", "answers": [ "しんご" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "幸二郎", "answers": [ "こうじろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "謙次", "answers": [ "けんじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "幹太", "answers": [ "かんた", "みきた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "亜久里", "answers": [ "あぐり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "葉", "answers": [ "よう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 14%" },
	{ "question": "頼宣", "answers": [ "よりのぶ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "夏美", "answers": [ "なつみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "なお美", "answers": [ "なおみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "登輝", "answers": [ "とうき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "和巳", "answers": [ "かずみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "三春", "answers": [ "みはる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "洋二郎", "answers": [ "ようじろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "嘉次郎", "answers": [ "かじろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "康裕", "answers": [ "やすひろ", "こうすけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 89%, 11%" },
	{ "question": "表", "answers": [ "ひょう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 66%" },
	{ "question": "拓三", "answers": [ "たくぞう", "たくみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%, 7%" },
	{ "question": "金吾", "answers": [ "きんご" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "隆二", "answers": [ "りゅうじ", "たかじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 81%, 19%" },
	{ "question": "用高", "answers": [ "ようこう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "祐太", "answers": [ "ゆうた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "美希", "answers": [ "みき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "正文", "answers": [ "まさふみ", "まさぶみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%, 6%" },
	{ "question": "彰布", "answers": [ "あきのぶ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "善廣", "answers": [ "よしひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "洋治", "answers": [ "ようじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "松之助", "answers": [ "まつのすけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "政雄", "answers": [ "まさお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "寿子", "answers": [ "ひさこ", "としこ", "かずこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 80%, 14%, 6%" },
	{ "question": "花", "answers": [ "はな" ], "comment": "Frequency: 88%" },
	{ "question": "舜臣", "answers": [ "しゅんしん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "耕二", "answers": [ "こうじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "宗徳", "answers": [ "むねのり", "むねえ", "そうとく", "しゅうとく" ], "comment": "Frequency: 80%, 12%, 6%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "政彦", "answers": [ "まさひこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "敏樹", "answers": [ "としき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "古", "answers": [ "こ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 5%" },
	{ "question": "頼家", "answers": [ "よりいえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "英世", "answers": [ "ひでよ", "えいせい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "定次", "answers": [ "さだつぐ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "又吉", "answers": [ "またきち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 6%" },
	{ "question": "芳光", "answers": [ "よしみつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "美江", "answers": [ "みえ", "よしえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 57%, 43%" },
	{ "question": "秀秋", "answers": [ "ひであき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "俊成", "answers": [ "としなり", "とししげ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "行", "answers": [ "こう", "いく", "あきら", "ぎょう", "ゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 37%, 30%, 6%, 3%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "恭一", "answers": [ "きょういち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "鑑三", "answers": [ "かんぞう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "吉元", "answers": [ "よしもと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 28%" },
	{ "question": "頼光", "answers": [ "よりみつ", "らいこう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 88%, 12%" },
	{ "question": "義清", "answers": [ "よしきよ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "門左衛門", "answers": [ "もんざえもん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "秀隆", "answers": [ "ひでたか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "規子", "answers": [ "のりこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "丈夫", "answers": [ "たけお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "圭市", "answers": [ "けいいち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "久仁子", "answers": [ "くにこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "雅行", "answers": [ "まさゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "飛", "answers": [ "ひ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "道灌", "answers": [ "どうかん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "卓哉", "answers": [ "たくや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "信一郎", "answers": [ "しんいちろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "朱里", "answers": [ "あかり", "じゅり", "しゅり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 41%, 39%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "優樹菜", "answers": [ "ゆきな" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "光代", "answers": [ "みつよ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "美智恵", "answers": [ "みちえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "信虎", "answers": [ "のぶとら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "季衣", "answers": [ "としえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "龍雄", "answers": [ "たつお", "りょうゆう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 90%, 10%" },
	{ "question": "忠正", "answers": [ "ただまさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "卓三", "answers": [ "たくぞう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "潤三", "answers": [ "じゅんぞう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "武市", "answers": [ "ぶいち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 13%" },
	{ "question": "宝田", "answers": [ "ほうでん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "大屋", "answers": [ "おおや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 4%" },
	{ "question": "愛音", "answers": [ "あやね" ], "comment": "Frequency: 5%" },
	{ "question": "利長", "answers": [ "としなが" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "湛山", "answers": [ "たんざん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "啓子", "answers": [ "けいこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "間部", "answers": [ "まべ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 3%" },
	{ "question": "康博", "answers": [ "やすひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "雅志", "answers": [ "まさし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "智衆", "answers": [ "ちしゅう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "茂光", "answers": [ "しげみつ", "もちみつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%, 7%" },
	{ "question": "亜子", "answers": [ "あこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "信濃", "answers": [ "しなの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "庸", "answers": [ "よう", "ひとし", "ちから" ], "comment": "Frequency: 92%, 5%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "自由", "answers": [ "みゆ", "じゆう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "益男", "answers": [ "ますお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "文世", "answers": [ "ふみよ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "創", "answers": [ "はじめ", "そう", "つくる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 70%, 19%, 11%" },
	{ "question": "達央", "answers": [ "たつひさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "祐弘", "answers": [ "すけひろ", "ゆうこう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "森一", "answers": [ "しんいち", "もりかず" ], "comment": "Frequency: 90%, 10%" },
	{ "question": "茂吉", "answers": [ "もきち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "史奈", "answers": [ "ふみな" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "武宏", "answers": [ "たけひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "善幸", "answers": [ "ぜんこう", "よしゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%, 6%" },
	{ "question": "公生", "answers": [ "きみお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "花菜", "answers": [ "かな", "はな" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "家長", "answers": [ "いえなが" ], "comment": "Frequency: 71%" },
	{ "question": "亜紀子", "answers": [ "あきこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "裕久", "answers": [ "ひろひさ", "やすひさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 71%, 29%" },
	{ "question": "春香", "answers": [ "はるか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 78%" },
	{ "question": "とん平", "answers": [ "とんぺい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "貴男", "answers": [ "たかお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "昭二", "answers": [ "しょうじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "吾一", "answers": [ "ごいち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "源内", "answers": [ "げんない" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "容保", "answers": [ "かたもり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "収", "answers": [ "おさむ", "しゅう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "一誠", "answers": [ "いっせい", "かずみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 84%, 16%" },
	{ "question": "滉", "answers": [ "あきら", "こう", "ひろし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 85%, 11%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "厳", "answers": [ "げん", "いさお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 38%, 9%" },
	{ "question": "爽", "answers": [ "そう", "さわ", "さやか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%, 2%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "宣", "answers": [ "せん", "とおる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 47%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "家重", "answers": [ "いえしげ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "昭生", "answers": [ "あきお", "しょうせい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 91%, 9%" },
	{ "question": "庄", "answers": [ "あつし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 6%" },
	{ "question": "泰造", "answers": [ "たいぞう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "氏政", "answers": [ "うじまさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "二葉", "answers": [ "ふたば" ], "comment": "Frequency: 22%" },
	{ "question": "理保子", "answers": [ "りほこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "雅則", "answers": [ "まさのり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "吹雪", "answers": [ "ふぶき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "英也", "answers": [ "ひでや", "えいや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "俊男", "answers": [ "としお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "次男", "answers": [ "つぎお", "つぐお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 61%, 39%" },
	{ "question": "壽賀子", "answers": [ "すがこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "一伸", "answers": [ "いっしん", "かずのぶ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "懿", "answers": [ "い" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "愛佳", "answers": [ "あいか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "真宏", "answers": [ "まさひろ", "まひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 65%, 35%" },
	{ "question": "紀洋", "answers": [ "のりひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "豊雄", "answers": [ "とよお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "宙明", "answers": [ "ちゅうめい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "大知", "answers": [ "だいち", "やまと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 91%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "准一", "answers": [ "じゅんいち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "周一", "answers": [ "しゅういち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "心美", "answers": [ "ここみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "浩太郎", "answers": [ "こうたろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "銀次", "answers": [ "ぎんじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "長友", "answers": [ "ながとも" ], "comment": "Frequency: 8%" },
	{ "question": "風太郎", "answers": [ "ふうたろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "洋行", "answers": [ "ひろゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "信光", "answers": [ "のぶみつ", "しんこう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "沢民", "answers": [ "たくみん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "尚志", "answers": [ "たかし", "なおゆき", "なおし", "ひさし", "たかゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 35%, 35%, 22%, 4%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "高国", "answers": [ "たかくに" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "静江", "answers": [ "しずえ", "せいこう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 91%, 9%" },
	{ "question": "瑛士", "answers": [ "えいじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "芳生", "answers": [ "よしふ", "みちお", "よしき", "よしお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 50%, 32%, 15%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "義宣", "answers": [ "よしのぶ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "昌男", "answers": [ "まさお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "直家", "answers": [ "なおいえ", "なおや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "豊子", "answers": [ "とよこ", "ほうし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "貴弘", "answers": [ "たかひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "健壱", "answers": [ "けんいち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "松代", "answers": [ "まつよ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 8%" },
	{ "question": "吉保", "answers": [ "よしやす" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "暢子", "answers": [ "ようこ", "のぶこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 82%, 18%" },
	{ "question": "祇晶", "answers": [ "まさあき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "福", "answers": [ "ふく" ], "comment": "Frequency: 74%" },
	{ "question": "隆也", "answers": [ "たかや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "祥三", "answers": [ "しょうぞう", "よしかず" ], "comment": "Frequency: 79%, 21%" },
	{ "question": "一之", "answers": [ "かずゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "叶", "answers": [ "かない", "かの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 10%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "克", "answers": [ "まさる", "かつ", "かつみ", "すぐる", "こく" ], "comment": "Frequency: 35%, 27%, 15%, 12%, 12%" },
	{ "question": "弘将", "answers": [ "ひろまさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "忠順", "answers": [ "ただまさ", "ただより", "ただおさ", "ただのぶ", "ただとし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 65%, 18%, 8%, 5%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "紗友里", "answers": [ "さゆり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "沙緒里", "answers": [ "さおり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "明和", "answers": [ "あきかず" ], "comment": "Frequency: 5%" },
	{ "question": "保夫", "answers": [ "やすお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "真幸", "answers": [ "まさゆき", "まさち", "まゆき", "まさき", "さねゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 34%, 29%, 17%, 4%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "忠則", "answers": [ "ただのり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "征一郎", "answers": [ "せいいちろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "薩夫", "answers": [ "さつお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "賢一郎", "answers": [ "けんいちろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "一正", "answers": [ "かずまさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "昭男", "answers": [ "あきお", "てるお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%, 7%" },
	{ "question": "乙羽", "answers": [ "おとわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 5%" },
	{ "question": "悠介", "answers": [ "ゆうすけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "麻帆", "answers": [ "まほ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "文也", "answers": [ "ふみや", "ぶんや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%, 7%" },
	{ "question": "鉄二", "answers": [ "てつじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "千恵", "answers": [ "ちえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "宗一", "answers": [ "そういち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "晋哉", "answers": [ "しんや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "正吾", "answers": [ "しょうご", "せいご" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "耕作", "answers": [ "こうさく" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "意次", "answers": [ "おきつぐ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "南雲", "answers": [ "ナムン" ], "comment": "Frequency: 5%" },
	{ "question": "義稙", "answers": [ "よしたね" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "斉", "answers": [ "ひとし", "せい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 69%, 7%" },
	{ "question": "武郎", "answers": [ "たけお", "たけろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 76%, 24%" },
	{ "question": "紗子", "answers": [ "さえこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "是清", "answers": [ "これきよ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "絹代", "answers": [ "きぬよ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "貫一", "answers": [ "かんいち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "和広", "answers": [ "かずひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "雄次", "answers": [ "ゆうじ", "かつつぐ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "祐司", "answers": [ "ゆうじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "三千代", "answers": [ "みちよ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "麻由美", "answers": [ "まゆみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "誠人", "answers": [ "まこと", "まさと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 80%, 20%" },
	{ "question": "甫", "answers": [ "ほ", "はじめ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 56%, 44%" },
	{ "question": "敏治", "answers": [ "としはる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "長一郎", "answers": [ "ちょういちろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "季実子", "answers": [ "きみこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "ひろ美", "answers": [ "ひろみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "智佐", "answers": [ "ちさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "威夫", "answers": [ "たけお", "いつお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "隆幸", "answers": [ "たかゆき", "りゅうこう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "啓示", "answers": [ "けいし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "千豊", "answers": [ "かずとよ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "瑛二", "answers": [ "えいじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "正宗", "answers": [ "まさむね" ], "comment": "Frequency: 49%" },
	{ "question": "安宅", "answers": [ "やすおり", "やすいえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 11%, 6%" },
	{ "question": "政次", "answers": [ "まさじ", "まさつぐ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 76%, 19%" },
	{ "question": "遥香", "answers": [ "はるか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "龍夫", "answers": [ "たつお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "大志", "answers": [ "たいし", "だいし", "ひろし", "まさし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 53%, 36%, 9%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "昇平", "answers": [ "しょうへい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "作霖", "answers": [ "さくりん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "章夫", "answers": [ "あきお", "ふみお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 87%, 13%" },
	{ "question": "安平", "answers": [ "やすひら", "やすへい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 7%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "六宏", "answers": [ "ろっこう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "智宏", "answers": [ "ともひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "忠長", "answers": [ "ただなが" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "圭佑", "answers": [ "けいすけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "圭亮", "answers": [ "けいすけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "義博", "answers": [ "よしひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "洋三", "answers": [ "ようぞう", "ひろぞう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 91%, 9%" },
	{ "question": "鱒二", "answers": [ "ますじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "秀利", "answers": [ "ひでとし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "菜穂", "answers": [ "なほ", "なお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 90%, 10%" },
	{ "question": "貴幸", "answers": [ "たかゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "圭一郎", "answers": [ "けいいちろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "一益", "answers": [ "いちます" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "神", "answers": [ "かみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 8%" },
	{ "question": "航", "answers": [ "わたる", "こう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 66%, 33%" },
	{ "question": "梨花", "answers": [ "りか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 79%" },
	{ "question": "弥太郎", "answers": [ "やたろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "麻実", "answers": [ "まみ", "あさみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 43%, 17%" },
	{ "question": "才加", "answers": [ "さやか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "孝治", "answers": [ "こうじ", "たかはる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 73%, 27%" },
	{ "question": "啓太", "answers": [ "けいた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "吉郎", "answers": [ "きちろう", "よしろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 63%, 36%" },
	{ "question": "香苗", "answers": [ "かなえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "泰弘", "answers": [ "やすひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "満仲", "answers": [ "みつなか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 72%" },
	{ "question": "未恵", "answers": [ "みえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "倍達", "answers": [ "ますたつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "真先", "answers": [ "まさき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "弘幸", "answers": [ "ひろゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "久司", "answers": [ "ひさし", "ひさじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "博士", "answers": [ "はかせ", "ひろし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 72%, 28%" },
	{ "question": "民輔", "answers": [ "たみすけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "順二", "answers": [ "じゅんじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "紗理奈", "answers": [ "さりな" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "亜矢", "answers": [ "あや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "彰彦", "answers": [ "あきひこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "末吉", "answers": [ "すえきち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 18%" },
	{ "question": "依子", "answers": [ "よりこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "良成", "answers": [ "よしなり", "りょうせい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 86%, 14%" },
	{ "question": "友里", "answers": [ "ゆり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "舞以", "answers": [ "まい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "久寛", "answers": [ "ひさひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "富太郎", "answers": [ "とみたろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "利行", "answers": [ "としゆき", "としみち", "りこう", "としつら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 82%, 8%, 7%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "貞一", "answers": [ "ていいち", "さだいち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 90%, 10%" },
	{ "question": "千代丸", "answers": [ "ちよまる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%" },
	{ "question": "重成", "answers": [ "しげなり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 85%" },
	{ "question": "邦茂", "answers": [ "くにしげ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "映見", "answers": [ "えみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "眞由美", "answers": [ "まゆみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "平蔵", "answers": [ "へいぞう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "春海", "answers": [ "はるみ", "しゅんかい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 47%, 20%" },
	{ "question": "喜八郎", "answers": [ "きはちろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "逸見", "answers": [ "いつみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "義広", "answers": [ "よしひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "師岡", "answers": [ "もろおか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 66%" },
	{ "question": "浩正", "answers": [ "ひろまさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "智春", "answers": [ "ともはる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "哲弥", "answers": [ "てつや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "兆治", "answers": [ "ちょうじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "千香子", "answers": [ "ちかこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "純希", "answers": [ "じゅんき", "すみき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "康史", "answers": [ "こうじ", "やすひと", "やすちか", "やすし", "やすふみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 46%, 19%, 19%, 10%, 6%" },
	{ "question": "幸一郎", "answers": [ "こういちろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "勝義", "answers": [ "かつよし", "しょうぎ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "高陽", "answers": [ "たかはる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 4%" },
	{ "question": "有里", "answers": [ "ゆり", "あり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 68%, 25%" },
	{ "question": "八十", "answers": [ "やそ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%" },
	{ "question": "望都", "answers": [ "もと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "馬琴", "answers": [ "ばきん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "斉彬", "answers": [ "なりあきら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "尚紀", "answers": [ "なおき", "ひさのり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 85%, 15%" },
	{ "question": "忠平", "answers": [ "ただひら", "ちゅうへい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 69%, 31%" },
	{ "question": "淳三郎", "answers": [ "じゅんざぶろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "真咲", "answers": [ "まさき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 27%" },
	{ "question": "善彦", "answers": [ "よしひこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "義治", "answers": [ "よしはる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "元彦", "answers": [ "もとひこ", "ゆきひこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 92%, 8%" },
	{ "question": "麻理子", "answers": [ "まりこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "忠晴", "answers": [ "ただはる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "忠邦", "answers": [ "ただくに" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "順三", "answers": [ "じゅんぞう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "佐江", "answers": [ "さえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 89%" },
	{ "question": "名", "answers": [ "めい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 12%" },
	{ "question": "中洲", "answers": [ "ちゅうしゅう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 17%" },
	{ "question": "好", "answers": [ "よしみ", "こう", "よしむ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 86%, 10%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "嘉明", "answers": [ "よしあき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "武雅", "answers": [ "むが", "たけまさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "正春", "answers": [ "まさはる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "拓篤", "answers": [ "たくま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "詩織", "answers": [ "しおり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "あゆ美", "answers": [ "あゆみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "亮二", "answers": [ "りょうじ", "りゅうじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "立", "answers": [ "りゅう", "りつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 41%, 28%" },
	{ "question": "幸長", "answers": [ "よしなが", "ゆきなが" ], "comment": "Frequency: 59%, 41%" },
	{ "question": "義忠", "answers": [ "よしただ", "よしだた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "美恵子", "answers": [ "みえこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "恒久", "answers": [ "つねひさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "多香子", "answers": [ "たかこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "砂記子", "answers": [ "さきこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "蔵之介", "answers": [ "くらのすけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "栄太郎", "answers": [ "えいたろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "和佳奈", "answers": [ "わかな" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "靖幸", "answers": [ "やすゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "宮土理", "answers": [ "みどり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "正親", "answers": [ "まさちか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "博行", "answers": [ "ひろゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "宏典", "answers": [ "ひろみち", "ひろのり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 81%, 19%" },
	{ "question": "寧々", "answers": [ "ねね" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "大貴", "answers": [ "だいき", "ひろたか", "ひろき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 90%, 4%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "育夫", "answers": [ "いくお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "有恒", "answers": [ "ありつね", "ゆうこう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 84%, 16%" },
	{ "question": "長生", "answers": [ "ながなり", "ちょうせい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 22%, 13%" },
	{ "question": "露伴", "answers": [ "ろはん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "頼綱", "answers": [ "よりつな" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "勇太", "answers": [ "ゆうた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "茉莉也", "answers": [ "まりや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "雅昭", "answers": [ "まさあき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "伸晃", "answers": [ "のぶてる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "眠子", "answers": [ "ねこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "幸平", "answers": [ "こうへい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "晏", "answers": [ "あん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 25%" },
	{ "question": "螢", "answers": [ "ほたる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 26%" },
	{ "question": "瑠偉", "answers": [ "ルイ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "佳幸", "answers": [ "よしゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "友樹", "answers": [ "ゆうき", "ともき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 71%, 29%" },
	{ "question": "政元", "answers": [ "まさもと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "弘和", "answers": [ "ひろかず" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "久信", "answers": [ "ひさのぶ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "敏明", "answers": [ "としあき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "輝基", "answers": [ "てるもと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "忠昌", "answers": [ "ただまさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "太作", "answers": [ "たいさく", "だいさく", "たさく" ], "comment": "Frequency: 83%, 9%, 7%" },
	{ "question": "喜重郎", "answers": [ "きじゅうろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "裕三", "answers": [ "ゆうぞう", "ひろみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 89%, 11%" },
	{ "question": "千枝子", "answers": [ "ちえこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "至", "answers": [ "いたる", "し" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "泰夫", "answers": [ "やすお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "三恵子", "answers": [ "みえこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "博光", "answers": [ "ひろみつ", "はっこう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "宗恵", "answers": [ "しゅうえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "幸次郎", "answers": [ "こうじろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "亜依", "answers": [ "あい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "音羽", "answers": [ "おとわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 12%" },
	{ "question": "与一", "answers": [ "よいち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "町子", "answers": [ "まちこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "範康", "answers": [ "のりやす" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "憲広", "answers": [ "のりひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "徳衛", "answers": [ "とくえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "妻三郎", "answers": [ "つまさぶろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "達男", "answers": [ "たつお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "さと美", "answers": [ "さとみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "稲造", "answers": [ "いなぞう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "武見", "answers": [ "たけみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 47%" },
	{ "question": "大道", "answers": [ "だいどう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 28%" },
	{ "question": "芳夫", "answers": [ "よしお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "番", "answers": [ "ばん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 64%" },
	{ "question": "八方", "answers": [ "はっぽう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "徳三", "answers": [ "とくぞう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "哲士", "answers": [ "てつし", "さとし", "てつじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 73%, 14%, 13%" },
	{ "question": "丈裕", "answers": [ "たけひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "家正", "answers": [ "いえまさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "旦", "answers": [ "あきら", "たん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 88%, 6%" },
	{ "question": "吉成", "answers": [ "よしなり", "きっせい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 24%, 18%" },
	{ "question": "未來", "answers": [ "みらい", "みく" ], "comment": "Frequency: 83%, 17%" },
	{ "question": "溥儀", "answers": [ "ふぎ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "晴男", "answers": [ "はるお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "信隆", "answers": [ "のぶたか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "成氏", "answers": [ "しげうじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "三太夫", "answers": [ "さんだゆう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "鴻章", "answers": [ "こうしょう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "栄一郎", "answers": [ "えいいちろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "如月", "answers": [ "きさらぎ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 3%" },
	{ "question": "智哉", "answers": [ "ともや", "ともちか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 64%, 36%" },
	{ "question": "徳太郎", "answers": [ "とくたろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "公房", "answers": [ "こうぼう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "小角", "answers": [ "おづの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "無我", "answers": [ "むが" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "万梨阿", "answers": [ "まりあ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "政司", "answers": [ "まさじ", "まさし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 71%, 29%" },
	{ "question": "裕和", "answers": [ "ひろかず" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "久之", "answers": [ "ひさゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "寿美", "answers": [ "としみ", "すみ", "ひさみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 42%, 12%, 7%" },
	{ "question": "新吾", "answers": [ "しんご" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "正司", "answers": [ "しょうじ", "まさし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 39%, 24%" },
	{ "question": "修三", "answers": [ "しゅうぞう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "志乃", "answers": [ "しの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "公三郎", "answers": [ "こうざぶろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "恵亮", "answers": [ "けいすけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "勝正", "answers": [ "かつまさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "凌", "answers": [ "りょう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 85%" },
	{ "question": "善行", "answers": [ "よしゆき", "ぜんこう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 84%, 6%" },
	{ "question": "安志", "answers": [ "やすし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "元長", "answers": [ "もとなが", "もとます" ], "comment": "Frequency: 74%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "宗茂", "answers": [ "むねしげ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "ひろ志", "answers": [ "ひろし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "瑞山", "answers": [ "ずいざん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 59%" },
	{ "question": "元璋", "answers": [ "げんしょう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "圭祐", "answers": [ "けいすけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "里香", "answers": [ "りか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "穂希", "answers": [ "ほまれ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "時政", "answers": [ "ときまさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "琢郎", "answers": [ "たくろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "新八", "answers": [ "しんぱち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "秀二", "answers": [ "しゅうじ", "ひでじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 51%, 49%" },
	{ "question": "下地", "answers": [ "しもじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 6%" },
	{ "question": "有沢", "answers": [ "ありさわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 25%" },
	{ "question": "道太郎", "answers": [ "みちたろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "直輝", "answers": [ "なおき", "なおてる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 86%, 14%" },
	{ "question": "知樹", "answers": [ "ともき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "和司", "answers": [ "かずし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "由加里", "answers": [ "ゆかり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "泰文", "answers": [ "やすふみ", "やすのり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 88%, 11%" },
	{ "question": "政光", "answers": [ "まさみつ", "まさひこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%, 7%" },
	{ "question": "晴久", "answers": [ "はるひさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "常寛", "answers": [ "つねひろ", "つねとお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "義賢", "answers": [ "よしかた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "真衣", "answers": [ "まい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "時枝", "answers": [ "ときえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 83%" },
	{ "question": "雄彦", "answers": [ "たけひこ", "ゆうひこ", "かつひこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 86%, 10%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "孝信", "answers": [ "たかのぶ", "こうしん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "禅", "answers": [ "ぜん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "央美", "answers": [ "おみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "由伸", "answers": [ "よしのぶ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "吐夢", "answers": [ "とむ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "整", "answers": [ "せい", "ひとし", "おさむ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 72%, 26%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "砂羽", "answers": [ "さわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "稼頭央", "answers": [ "かずお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "良彦", "answers": [ "よしひこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "村重", "answers": [ "むらしげ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 85%" },
	{ "question": "昌孝", "answers": [ "まさたか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "正輝", "answers": [ "まさき", "まさてる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "逍遥", "answers": [ "しょうよう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "和矢", "answers": [ "かずや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "愛梨", "answers": [ "あいり", "えり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "芙美子", "answers": [ "ふみこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "裕英", "answers": [ "ひろひで" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "一二三", "answers": [ "ひふみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 92%" },
	{ "question": "享", "answers": [ "とおる", "すすむ", "うける", "あきら", "りょう", "きょう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 49%, 26%, 11%, 7%, 5%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "新将", "answers": [ "しんしょう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "将", "answers": [ "しょう", "まさる", "たすく", "すすむ", "まさし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 40%, 27%, 23%, 7%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "西鶴", "answers": [ "さいかく" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "公延", "answers": [ "こうえん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "憲伸", "answers": [ "けんしん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "勝春", "answers": [ "かつはる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "勝則", "answers": [ "かつのり", "まさのり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "和行", "answers": [ "かずゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "恵梨香", "answers": [ "えりか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "義朗", "answers": [ "よしろう", "よしあき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 64%, 35%" },
	{ "question": "光信", "answers": [ "みつのぶ", "こうしん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 91%, 9%" },
	{ "question": "宣親", "answers": [ "のりちか", "のぶちか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "知里", "answers": [ "ちさと", "ちり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 54%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "高弘", "answers": [ "たかひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "実篤", "answers": [ "さねあつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "光一郎", "answers": [ "こういちろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "球児", "answers": [ "きゅうじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "正宏", "answers": [ "まさひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "昌利", "answers": [ "まさとし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "麻琴", "answers": [ "まこと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "寛貴", "answers": [ "ひろき", "ひろたか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 92%, 8%" },
	{ "question": "信直", "answers": [ "のぶなお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "天心", "answers": [ "てんしん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 92%" },
	{ "question": "徹平", "answers": [ "てっぺい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "吉太郎", "answers": [ "きちたろう", "よしたろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 88%, 12%" },
	{ "question": "加世子", "answers": [ "かよこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "勝元", "answers": [ "かつもと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "蘭太郎", "answers": [ "らんたろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "義澄", "answers": [ "よしずみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "弘志", "answers": [ "ひろし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "仁紀", "answers": [ "ひとき", "よしのり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "憲明", "answers": [ "のりあき", "けんめい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 88%, 12%" },
	{ "question": "稔久", "answers": [ "なるひさ", "としひさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 92%, 8%" },
	{ "question": "貴彦", "answers": [ "たかひこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "章一", "answers": [ "しょういち", "のりかず" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%, 6%" },
	{ "question": "彰一", "answers": [ "しょういち", "あきかず" ], "comment": "Frequency: 84%, 16%" },
	{ "question": "固", "answers": [ "こ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "優也", "answers": [ "ゆうや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "安治", "answers": [ "やすはる", "やすじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 78%, 22%" },
	{ "question": "秀則", "answers": [ "ひでのり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "信正", "answers": [ "のぶまさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "友恵", "answers": [ "ともえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "富枝", "answers": [ "とみえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "虚子", "answers": [ "きょし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "寛美", "answers": [ "かんび", "ひろみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 72%, 28%" },
	{ "question": "理名", "answers": [ "りな" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "義文", "answers": [ "よしぶみ", "よしふみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 71%, 29%" },
	{ "question": "陽区", "answers": [ "ようく" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "寧", "answers": [ "やすし", "ねい", "やす" ], "comment": "Frequency: 60%, 32%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "基博", "answers": [ "もとひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "将生", "answers": [ "まさき", "しょうき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 73%, 27%" },
	{ "question": "浩行", "answers": [ "ひろゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "修宏", "answers": [ "のぶひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "澄江", "answers": [ "すみえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "恵研", "answers": [ "えけん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "詠二", "answers": [ "えいじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "喜美", "answers": [ "よしみ", "きみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 89%, 11%" },
	{ "question": "優乃", "answers": [ "ゆうの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "忠宗", "answers": [ "ただむね" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "寂聴", "answers": [ "じゃくちょう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "紳司", "answers": [ "しんじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "香奈", "answers": [ "かな" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "錦", "answers": [ "にしき", "きん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 8%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "羽後", "answers": [ "うご" ], "comment": "Frequency: 19%" },
	{ "question": "四方", "answers": [ "しほう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 36%" },
	{ "question": "陽太", "answers": [ "ようた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "康光", "answers": [ "やすみつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "政弘", "answers": [ "まさひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "静六", "answers": [ "せいろく" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "従道", "answers": [ "じゅうどう", "つぐみち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "亜沙美", "answers": [ "あさみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "佳容", "answers": [ "チアユン", "よしひろ", "かよ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 62%, 22%, 16%" },
	{ "question": "義持", "answers": [ "よしもち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "裕而", "answers": [ "ゆうじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "みゆ希", "answers": [ "みゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "愛実", "answers": [ "まなみ", "つぐみ", "めぐみ", "あいみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 40%, 26%, 23%, 11%" },
	{ "question": "卓球", "answers": [ "たっきゅう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "成功", "answers": [ "せいこう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 86%" },
	{ "question": "俊治", "answers": [ "しゅんじ", "としはる", "としじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 52%, 43%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "興毅", "answers": [ "こうき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "勘助", "answers": [ "かんすけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "安吾", "answers": [ "あんご" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "鏡", "answers": [ "きょう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 3%" },
	{ "question": "柳太郎", "answers": [ "りゅうたろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "由人", "answers": [ "よしと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "宗矩", "answers": [ "むねのり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "光貞", "answers": [ "みつさだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "幹郎", "answers": [ "みきお", "みきろう", "もとお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 72%, 17%, 11%" },
	{ "question": "功男", "answers": [ "のりお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "虎之助", "answers": [ "とらのすけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "時男", "answers": [ "ときお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "千代", "answers": [ "ちよ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 66%" },
	{ "question": "蘇峰", "answers": [ "そほう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "正太", "answers": [ "しょうた", "まさたか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "功至", "answers": [ "かつじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "和生", "answers": [ "かずお", "わせい", "かずき", "かずい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 81%, 10%, 5%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "格", "answers": [ "いたる", "ただす", "とおる", "かく", "ただし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 73%, 9%, 9%, 6%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "小鹿", "answers": [ "ころく" ], "comment": "Frequency: 6%" },
	{ "question": "令三", "answers": [ "りょうぞう", "れいぞう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "光聖", "answers": [ "みつよし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "真珠", "answers": [ "まじゅ", "しんじゅ", "まこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 83%, 11%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "宏司", "answers": [ "ひろし", "こうじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 60%, 40%" },
	{ "question": "清輝", "answers": [ "せいき", "きよてる", "きよき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 56%, 42%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "心平", "answers": [ "しんぺい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "和実", "answers": [ "かずみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "令仁", "answers": [ "れいじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "夕貴", "answers": [ "ゆうき", "ゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 92%, 8%" },
	{ "question": "光弘", "answers": [ "みつひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "雅英", "answers": [ "まさひで" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "信盛", "answers": [ "のぶもり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "為義", "answers": [ "ためよし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "三省", "answers": [ "さんせい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "航平", "answers": [ "こうへい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "和昭", "answers": [ "かずあき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "あつ子", "answers": [ "あつこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "浅夫", "answers": [ "あさお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "義長", "answers": [ "よしなが" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "保仁", "answers": [ "やすひと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "美雪", "answers": [ "みゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 92%" },
	{ "question": "正紀", "answers": [ "まさき", "まさのり", "まさみち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 79%, 17%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "文太郎", "answers": [ "ぶんたろう", "ふみたろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "宏昌", "answers": [ "ひろまさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "初範", "answers": [ "はつのり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "流行", "answers": [ "ながれ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "忠重", "answers": [ "ただしげ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "卓造", "answers": [ "たくぞう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "章造", "answers": [ "しょうぞう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "兼一", "answers": [ "けんいち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "吉三郎", "answers": [ "きちさぶろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "学良", "answers": [ "がくりょう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "松茂", "answers": [ "まつしげ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 19%" },
	{ "question": "隆一郎", "answers": [ "りゅういちろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "裕士", "answers": [ "ゆうじ", "ひろし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 79%, 21%" },
	{ "question": "敏八", "answers": [ "としや", "びんぱち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 62%, 38%" },
	{ "question": "貞義", "answers": [ "さだよし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "賢人", "answers": [ "けんと", "まさひと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 78%, 21%" },
	{ "question": "家継", "answers": [ "いえつぐ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "莉奈", "answers": [ "りな" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "泰光", "answers": [ "やすみつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "公則", "answers": [ "まさのり", "きんのり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "太紀", "answers": [ "たいき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "荘司", "answers": [ "そうじ", "しょうじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 81%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "山陽", "answers": [ "さんよう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "定", "answers": [ "さだむ", "さだ", "やすし", "てい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 53%, 21%, 19%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "一矢", "answers": [ "かずや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "江威子", "answers": [ "えいこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "弥彦", "answers": [ "やひこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 11%" },
	{ "question": "由記", "answers": [ "ゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "泰郎", "answers": [ "やすお", "たいろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 87%, 13%" },
	{ "question": "雅紀", "answers": [ "まさき", "まさのり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "晴郎", "answers": [ "はるお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "啓雄", "answers": [ "のぶお", "よしお", "ひろお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 59%, 33%, 8%" },
	{ "question": "輝子", "answers": [ "てるこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "尊徳", "answers": [ "たかのり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "春嶽", "answers": [ "しゅんがく" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "邦臣", "answers": [ "くにおみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "清光", "answers": [ "きよみつ", "せいこう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 91%, 9%" },
	{ "question": "莞爾", "answers": [ "かんじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "克広", "answers": [ "かつひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "一利", "answers": [ "かずとし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "以蔵", "answers": [ "いぞう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "明信", "answers": [ "あきのぶ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "富司", "answers": [ "とみじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 8%" },
	{ "question": "快彦", "answers": [ "よしひこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "良樹", "answers": [ "よしき", "りょうじゅ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%, 6%" },
	{ "question": "喜明", "answers": [ "よしあき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "由香利", "answers": [ "ゆかり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "光正", "answers": [ "みつまさ", "こうせい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 51%, 49%" },
	{ "question": "弘至", "answers": [ "ひろし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "琢", "answers": [ "たく" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "昌一", "answers": [ "しょういち", "まさかず", "ますいち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 52%, 39%, 10%" },
	{ "question": "秋生", "answers": [ "あきお", "あきみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 58%, 42%" },
	{ "question": "利重", "answers": [ "とししげ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 26%" },
	{ "question": "保彦", "answers": [ "やすひこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "民賢", "answers": [ "みんけん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "美緒", "answers": [ "みお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "文珍", "answers": [ "ぶんちん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "成人", "answers": [ "なりと", "なるひと", "しげと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 72%, 23%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "直泰", "answers": [ "なおひろ", "なおやす" ], "comment": "Frequency: 86%, 14%" },
	{ "question": "けん太", "answers": [ "けんた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "修身", "answers": [ "おさみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "穂高", "answers": [ "ほだか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 4%" },
	{ "question": "程", "answers": [ "てい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 3%" },
	{ "question": "糸", "answers": [ "いと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 14%" },
	{ "question": "斗煥", "answers": [ "ドゥファン" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "安則", "answers": [ "やすのり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "美紗", "answers": [ "みさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "政利", "answers": [ "まさとし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "正毅", "answers": [ "まさたけ", "まさき", "ただき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 87%, 11%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "俊志", "answers": [ "しゅんじ", "としゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "惟晴", "answers": [ "これはる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "幸太", "answers": [ "こうた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "鎌足", "answers": [ "かまたり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "克之", "answers": [ "かつゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "勝紀", "answers": [ "かつのり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "篤志", "answers": [ "あつし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "朱美", "answers": [ "あけみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "嵯峨", "answers": [ "さが" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "涼太", "answers": [ "りょうた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "良治", "answers": [ "りょうじ", "よしはる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 75%, 25%" },
	{ "question": "浩樹", "answers": [ "ひろき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "伸幸", "answers": [ "のぶゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "水扁", "answers": [ "すいへん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "じゅん子", "answers": [ "じゅんこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "隆之介", "answers": [ "りゅうのすけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "竜介", "answers": [ "りゅうすけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "万理", "answers": [ "まり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "誠志", "answers": [ "まさし", "せいし", "せいじ", "さとし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 70%, 14%, 12%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "飛呂彦", "answers": [ "ひろひこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "宏子", "answers": [ "ひろこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "秀久", "answers": [ "ひでひさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "信芳", "answers": [ "のぶよし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "研一", "answers": [ "けんいち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "兼", "answers": [ "けん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "熊楠", "answers": [ "くまぐす" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "礼二", "answers": [ "れいじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "真奈", "answers": [ "まな" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "富士夫", "answers": [ "ふじお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "大宙", "answers": [ "たかひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "静男", "answers": [ "しずお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "諭", "answers": [ "さとし", "さとる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 67%, 33%" },
	{ "question": "滉一", "answers": [ "こういち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "玉山", "answers": [ "ぎょくざん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 11%" },
	{ "question": "幸徳", "answers": [ "こうとく", "ゆきのり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 11%, 9%" },
	{ "question": "夕夏", "answers": [ "ゆうか", "ゆか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 63%, 37%" },
	{ "question": "芽衣子", "answers": [ "めいこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "春恵", "answers": [ "はるえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "信人", "answers": [ "のぶと", "のぶひと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 90%, 10%" },
	{ "question": "雄浩", "answers": [ "たけひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "拓磨", "answers": [ "たくま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "壮一", "answers": [ "そういち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "瞬", "answers": [ "しゅん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "孝蔵", "answers": [ "こうぞう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "音", "answers": [ "おと", "おん", "いん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 64%, 11%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "歌丸", "answers": [ "うたまる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "一太", "answers": [ "いちた", "かずもと", "いった" ], "comment": "Frequency: 90%, 6%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "勇介", "answers": [ "ゆうすけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "美智", "answers": [ "みち", "よしとも" ], "comment": "Frequency: 77%, 23%" },
	{ "question": "眞人", "answers": [ "まさと", "まひと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "春馬", "answers": [ "はるま", "はるば" ], "comment": "Frequency: 91%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "太津朗", "answers": [ "たつお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "隆則", "answers": [ "たかのり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "俊次", "answers": [ "しゅんじ", "としつぐ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 87%, 13%" },
	{ "question": "鬼奴", "answers": [ "おにやっこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "炎", "answers": [ "えん", "ほのお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 88%, 6%" },
	{ "question": "芳貞", "answers": [ "よしさだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "靖広", "answers": [ "やすひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "安生", "answers": [ "やすお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 61%" },
	{ "question": "臣幸", "answers": [ "ともゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "俊倫", "answers": [ "としみち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "貴俊", "answers": [ "たかとし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "宗佑", "answers": [ "そうすけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "術", "answers": [ "じゅつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "進矢", "answers": [ "しんや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "伸司", "answers": [ "しんじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "定義", "answers": [ "さだよし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "冴子", "answers": [ "さえこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "宏太", "answers": [ "こうた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "英心", "answers": [ "えいしん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "篤紀", "answers": [ "あつのり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "眉山", "answers": [ "びざん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 14%" },
	{ "question": "睦子", "answers": [ "むつこ", "ちかこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 75%, 25%" },
	{ "question": "密", "answers": [ "ひそか", "みつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 55%, 45%" },
	{ "question": "淳也", "answers": [ "じゅんや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "治三郎", "answers": [ "じさぶろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "真太郎", "answers": [ "しんたろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "孝路", "answers": [ "こうじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "小朝", "answers": [ "こあさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "健嗣", "answers": [ "けんじ", "けんし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "圭織", "answers": [ "かおり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "彩佳", "answers": [ "あやか", "さいか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "里花子", "answers": [ "りかこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "慎", "answers": [ "まこと", "しん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 56%, 43%" },
	{ "question": "秀直", "answers": [ "ひでなお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "徳広", "answers": [ "のりひろ", "とくこう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "則子", "answers": [ "のりこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "則夫", "answers": [ "のりお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "虹子", "answers": [ "にじこ", "こうこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 76%, 24%" },
	{ "question": "虎雄", "answers": [ "とらお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "多江", "answers": [ "たえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "佳寿子", "answers": [ "かずこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "水", "answers": [ "いづみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 30%" },
	{ "question": "猫", "answers": [ "ねこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 6%" },
	{ "question": "天山", "answers": [ "てんざん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 5%" },
	{ "question": "博和", "answers": [ "ひろかず" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "日出夫", "answers": [ "ひでお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "照美", "answers": [ "てるみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "貴浩", "answers": [ "たかひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "澄夫", "answers": [ "すみお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "治五郎", "answers": [ "じごろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "象山", "answers": [ "しょうざん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "真之", "answers": [ "さねゆき", "まさゆき", "まさし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 75%, 13%, 11%" },
	{ "question": "義統", "answers": [ "よしむね", "よしずみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 90%, 10%" },
	{ "question": "悠里", "answers": [ "ゆうり", "ゆり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 90%, 10%" },
	{ "question": "美鈴", "answers": [ "みすず", "みりん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "澪", "answers": [ "みお", "れい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 87%, 7%" },
	{ "question": "貫之", "answers": [ "つらゆき", "かんし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "竹善", "answers": [ "ちくぜん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "司郎", "answers": [ "しろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "成彰", "answers": [ "しげあき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "明香", "answers": [ "さやか", "めいか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 83%, 16%" },
	{ "question": "孝次", "answers": [ "こうじ", "たかじ", "たかつぐ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 60%, 27%, 13%" },
	{ "question": "憲吾", "answers": [ "けんご" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "祺瑞", "answers": [ "きずい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "恵里", "answers": [ "えり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "康広", "answers": [ "やすひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "茉莉子", "answers": [ "まりこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "益次郎", "answers": [ "ますじろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "広吉", "answers": [ "ひろよし", "ひろきち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "斗真", "answers": [ "とうま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "務", "answers": [ "つとむ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "清二", "answers": [ "せいじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "征二", "answers": [ "せいじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "真二郎", "answers": [ "しんじろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "祥一郎", "answers": [ "しょういちろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "加代子", "answers": [ "かよこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "呼人", "answers": [ "よひと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%" },
	{ "question": "諭一", "answers": [ "ゆいち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "瑞樹", "answers": [ "みずき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "章枝", "answers": [ "ふみえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "史人", "answers": [ "ふびと", "ふみひと", "ふみと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 80%, 12%, 7%" },
	{ "question": "隼雄", "answers": [ "はやお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "利常", "answers": [ "としつね" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "重四郎", "answers": [ "じゅうしろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "可南子", "answers": [ "かなこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "明雄", "answers": [ "あきお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "喜郎", "answers": [ "よしろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "愛乃", "answers": [ "よしの", "あいの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 79%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "祐未", "answers": [ "ゆみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "祐也", "answers": [ "ゆうや", "すけなり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 88%, 12%" },
	{ "question": "泰裕", "answers": [ "やすひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "文紀", "answers": [ "やすのり", "ふみのり", "ふみかず", "ふみとし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 57%, 32%, 9%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "実花", "answers": [ "みか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "博英", "answers": [ "ひろひで" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "春男", "answers": [ "はるお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "信輝", "answers": [ "のぶてる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "成樹", "answers": [ "なるき", "せいき", "しげき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 57%, 29%, 14%" },
	{ "question": "奈緒子", "answers": [ "なおこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "利男", "answers": [ "としお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "宿禰", "answers": [ "たけのうちの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "成貴", "answers": [ "せいき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "晃彦", "answers": [ "あきひこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "顕家", "answers": [ "あきいえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "娜", "answers": [ "ナ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "頼政", "answers": [ "よりまさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "洋右", "answers": [ "ようすけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "康紀", "answers": [ "やすのり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "麻里安", "answers": [ "まりあ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "寛司", "answers": [ "ひろし", "かんじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%, 6%" },
	{ "question": "廣", "answers": [ "ひろし", "こう", "ひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 69%, 15%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "信勝", "answers": [ "のぶかつ", "しんしょう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 89%, 11%" },
	{ "question": "七生", "answers": [ "ななみ", "ななお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 88%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "俊平", "answers": [ "しゅんぺい", "としひら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 92%, 8%" },
	{ "question": "耕一郎", "answers": [ "こういちろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "顕治", "answers": [ "けんじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "英里子", "answers": [ "えりこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "恋", "answers": [ "れん", "こい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "容莉枝", "answers": [ "よりえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "裕佳梨", "answers": [ "ゆかり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "誠勝", "answers": [ "まさかつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "久乃", "answers": [ "ひさの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "のび太", "answers": [ "のびた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "奈穂子", "answers": [ "なおこ", "なほこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 85%, 15%" },
	{ "question": "利幸", "answers": [ "としゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "得愛", "answers": [ "とくよし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "知佳", "answers": [ "ちか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "忠寛", "answers": [ "ただひろ", "ただとお", "ただとも" ], "comment": "Frequency: 82%, 12%, 6%" },
	{ "question": "多恵子", "answers": [ "たえこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "甚八", "answers": [ "じんぱち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "庄三郎", "answers": [ "しょうざぶろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "和晃", "answers": [ "かずあき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%" },
	{ "question": "高中", "answers": [ "たかなか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 7%" },
	{ "question": "百合", "answers": [ "ゆり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "美奈代", "answers": [ "みなよ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "万里子", "answers": [ "まりこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "誉", "answers": [ "ほまれ", "たかし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 83%, 17%" },
	{ "question": "業平", "answers": [ "なりひら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 91%" },
	{ "question": "斗司夫", "answers": [ "としお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "年雄", "answers": [ "としお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "東子", "answers": [ "とうこ", "さきこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "常雄", "answers": [ "つねお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "珠代", "answers": [ "たまよ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "高次", "answers": [ "たかつぐ", "こうじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 90%, 10%" },
	{ "question": "善次郎", "answers": [ "ぜんじろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "静代", "answers": [ "しずよ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "けい子", "answers": [ "けいこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "和裕", "answers": [ "かずひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "英五", "answers": [ "えいご" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "氏真", "answers": [ "うじざね" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "彩矢", "answers": [ "あや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "天満", "answers": [ "てんま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 10%" },
	{ "question": "村治", "answers": [ "むらじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 5%" },
	{ "question": "広沢", "answers": [ "こうたく" ], "comment": "Frequency: 21%" },
	{ "question": "鷹司", "answers": [ "たかし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "尚中", "answers": [ "サンジュン", "たかなか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 87%, 13%" },
	{ "question": "頼通", "answers": [ "よりみち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "優里", "answers": [ "ゆり", "ゆうり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%, 6%" },
	{ "question": "持氏", "answers": [ "もちうじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "光次郎", "answers": [ "みつじろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "哲二", "answers": [ "てつじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "公彦", "answers": [ "きみひこ", "まさひこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "有沙", "answers": [ "ありさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 92%" },
	{ "question": "龍太", "answers": [ "りゅうた", "りょうた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 73%, 27%" },
	{ "question": "麻紀", "answers": [ "まき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "忠清", "answers": [ "ただきよ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "真介", "answers": [ "しんすけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "志帆", "answers": [ "しほ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "重幸", "answers": [ "しげゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "行生", "answers": [ "こうせい", "ゆきお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "公子", "answers": [ "きみこ", "ひろこ", "こうこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 79%, 12%, 8%" },
	{ "question": "吉武", "answers": [ "よしたけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 5%" },
	{ "question": "常", "answers": [ "じょう", "ときわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 18%, 11%" },
	{ "question": "理子", "answers": [ "りこ", "みちこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%, 7%" },
	{ "question": "理香", "answers": [ "りか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "有三", "answers": [ "ゆうぞう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "三奈", "answers": [ "みな" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "三男", "answers": [ "みつお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "美紀子", "answers": [ "みきこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "真悠子", "answers": [ "まゆこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "秀孝", "answers": [ "ひでたか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "知可子", "answers": [ "ちかこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "健夫", "answers": [ "たけお", "たてお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 73%, 27%" },
	{ "question": "春菊", "answers": [ "しゅんぎく" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "国光", "answers": [ "くにみつ", "こくこう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "羲之", "answers": [ "ぎし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "和洋", "answers": [ "かずひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "泊", "answers": [ "はく" ], "comment": "Frequency: 7%" },
	{ "question": "蓮", "answers": [ "れん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 76%" },
	{ "question": "麻央", "answers": [ "まお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 76%" },
	{ "question": "孝志", "answers": [ "たかし", "こうじ", "たかゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 76%, 19%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "善", "answers": [ "ぜん", "よし", "もりよし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 76%, 4%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "才一", "answers": [ "さいいち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "燿大", "answers": [ "あきひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "里佳", "answers": [ "りか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "直正", "answers": [ "なおまさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "中也", "answers": [ "ちゅうや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "多聞", "answers": [ "たもん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "昌司", "answers": [ "しょうじ", "まさし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 75%, 25%" },
	{ "question": "一起", "answers": [ "かずき", "いっき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 84%, 16%" },
	{ "question": "義剛", "answers": [ "よしたけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "保則", "answers": [ "やすのり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "美智雄", "answers": [ "みちお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "真世", "answers": [ "まよ", "みちよ", "まさよ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 88%, 6%, 6%" },
	{ "question": "半蔵", "answers": [ "はんぞう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "八大", "answers": [ "はちだい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "信宏", "answers": [ "のぶひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "親房", "answers": [ "ちかふさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "鷹彦", "answers": [ "たかひこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "子温", "answers": [ "しおん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "公美子", "answers": [ "くみこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "市朗", "answers": [ "いちろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "小竹", "answers": [ "しょうちく" ], "comment": "Frequency: 18%" },
	{ "question": "信時", "answers": [ "のぶとき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 28%" },
	{ "question": "和平", "answers": [ "わへい", "かずひら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 87%, 6%" },
	{ "question": "雄之", "answers": [ "ゆうじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "祐一郎", "answers": [ "ゆういちろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "元夢", "answers": [ "もとむ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "徹郎", "answers": [ "てつろう", "てつお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "千里子", "answers": [ "ちりこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "徂徠", "answers": [ "そらい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "周五郎", "answers": [ "しゅうごろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "恒三", "answers": [ "こうぞう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "幹士", "answers": [ "かんじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "小熊", "answers": [ "おぐま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "嘉男", "answers": [ "よしお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "祐治", "answers": [ "ゆうじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "昌典", "answers": [ "まさのり", "よしのり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%, 7%" },
	{ "question": "博司", "answers": [ "ひろし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "仁哉", "answers": [ "じんや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "敬介", "answers": [ "けいすけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "清貴", "answers": [ "きよたか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "嘉一", "answers": [ "かいち", "よしかず" ], "comment": "Frequency: 64%, 36%" },
	{ "question": "理央", "answers": [ "りお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "幸恵", "answers": [ "ゆきえ", "さちえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 68%, 32%" },
	{ "question": "泰久", "answers": [ "やすひさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "泰樹", "answers": [ "やすき", "たいじゅ", "たいき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 84%, 11%, 6%" },
	{ "question": "雅世", "answers": [ "まさよ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "正武", "answers": [ "まさたけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "舞美", "answers": [ "まいみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "英嗣", "answers": [ "ひでつぐ", "えいじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 91%, 9%" },
	{ "question": "直茂", "answers": [ "なおしげ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "大裕", "answers": [ "だいすけ", "ともひろ", "だいゆう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 78%, 14%, 8%" },
	{ "question": "信輔", "answers": [ "しんすけ", "のぶすけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 81%, 19%" },
	{ "question": "早希", "answers": [ "さき", "さつき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 87%, 6%" },
	{ "question": "光二", "answers": [ "こうじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "騏一郎", "answers": [ "きいちろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "果穂", "answers": [ "かほ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "和恭", "answers": [ "かずゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "昭典", "answers": [ "あきのり", "しょうすけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "成海", "answers": [ "なるみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 7%" },
	{ "question": "鈴音", "answers": [ "すずね", "リンシェン" ], "comment": "Frequency: 39%, 21%" },
	{ "question": "裕美子", "answers": [ "ゆみこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "康仁", "answers": [ "やすひと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "元久", "answers": [ "もとひさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "弘吉", "answers": [ "ひろきち", "ひろよし", "こうきち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 66%, 32%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "智彦", "answers": [ "ともひこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "忠茂", "answers": [ "ただしげ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "多喜二", "answers": [ "たきじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "重義", "answers": [ "しげよし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "沙樹", "answers": [ "さき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "剛昌", "answers": [ "ごうしょう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "小六", "answers": [ "ころく" ], "comment": "Frequency: 24%" },
	{ "question": "頼信", "answers": [ "よりのぶ", "らいしん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 70%, 30%" },
	{ "question": "真輝", "answers": [ "まき", "まさき", "なおき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 70%, 17%, 13%" },
	{ "question": "伴睦", "answers": [ "ばんぼく", "ともむつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "範頼", "answers": [ "のりより" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "経惟", "answers": [ "のぶよし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "也実", "answers": [ "なりみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "富子", "answers": [ "とみこ", "プジャ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%, 6%" },
	{ "question": "志ん朝", "answers": [ "しんちょう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "勘吉", "answers": [ "かんきち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "右太衛門", "answers": [ "うたえもん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "あや子", "answers": [ "あやこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "右光", "answers": [ "あきみつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "青空", "answers": [ "そら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 48%" },
	{ "question": "吉政", "answers": [ "よしまさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "千代子", "answers": [ "ちよこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "貴宏", "answers": [ "たかひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "善三", "answers": [ "ぜんぞう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "笑瓶", "answers": [ "しょうへい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "智史", "answers": [ "さとし", "ともふみ", "ともし", "ともちか", "ともひと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 66%, 14%, 10%, 5%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "耕助", "answers": [ "こうすけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "研次", "answers": [ "けんじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "澄", "answers": [ "きよし", "とおる", "すみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 79%, 17%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "嘉代", "answers": [ "かよ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "勝重", "answers": [ "かつしげ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "篤胤", "answers": [ "あつたね" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "宇美", "answers": [ "うみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 4%" },
	{ "question": "里英", "answers": [ "りえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "夢声", "answers": [ "むせい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "不比等", "answers": [ "ふひと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "宏幸", "answers": [ "ひろゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "智徳", "answers": [ "とものり", "ちとこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 90%, 10%" },
	{ "question": "聡彦", "answers": [ "としひこ", "ときひこ", "あきひこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 83%, 10%, 7%" },
	{ "question": "恒興", "answers": [ "つねおき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "竹城", "answers": [ "たけじょう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "卓弥", "answers": [ "たくや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "昇太", "answers": [ "しょうた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "康司", "answers": [ "こうじ", "やすし", "やすじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 54%, 38%, 9%" },
	{ "question": "京一", "answers": [ "きょういち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "香菜子", "answers": [ "かなこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "延", "answers": [ "えん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 79%" },
	{ "question": "隆介", "answers": [ "りゅうすけ", "たかすけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "喜子", "answers": [ "よしこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "政広", "answers": [ "まさひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "弘文", "answers": [ "ひろふみ", "こうぶん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "日出男", "answers": [ "ひでお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "信朗", "answers": [ "のぶあき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "直宏", "answers": [ "なおひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "丈博", "answers": [ "たけひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "荘八", "answers": [ "そうはち", "しょうはち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 78%, 22%" },
	{ "question": "清康", "answers": [ "きよやす" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "寛一", "answers": [ "かんいち", "ひろかず" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "嘉葎雄", "answers": [ "かつお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "吉継", "answers": [ "よしつぐ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "真弘", "answers": [ "まさひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "直彦", "answers": [ "なおひこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "忠吉", "answers": [ "ただよし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "敬久", "answers": [ "たかひさ", "のりひさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 77%, 23%" },
	{ "question": "蛾次郎", "answers": [ "がじろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "杏樹", "answers": [ "あんじゅ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "頼之", "answers": [ "よりゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "善夫", "answers": [ "よしお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "三貴", "answers": [ "みつたか", "みき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 80%, 20%" },
	{ "question": "道生", "answers": [ "みちお", "みちたか", "どうせい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 91%, 6%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "博道", "answers": [ "はくどう", "ひろみち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 51%, 49%" },
	{ "question": "朋之", "answers": [ "ともゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "富之", "answers": [ "とみゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "知恵子", "answers": [ "ちえこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "高生", "answers": [ "たかお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "大観", "answers": [ "たいかん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "聖治", "answers": [ "せいじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "信司", "answers": [ "しんじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "重宗", "answers": [ "しげむね" ], "comment": "Frequency: 74%" },
	{ "question": "広治", "answers": [ "こうじ", "ひろはる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "愃一", "answers": [ "けんいち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "瑛子", "answers": [ "えいこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "成利", "answers": [ "なりとし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "長重", "answers": [ "ながしげ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "得郎", "answers": [ "とくろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "左近", "answers": [ "さこん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%" },
	{ "question": "権兵衛", "answers": [ "ごんべえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "小町", "answers": [ "こまち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 83%" },
	{ "question": "勝栄", "answers": [ "かつえい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "栄三", "answers": [ "えいぞう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "あき子", "answers": [ "あきこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "任", "answers": [ "じん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 16%" },
	{ "question": "マチ子", "answers": [ "マチこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "優里奈", "answers": [ "ゆりな" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "勇志", "answers": [ "ゆうじ", "ゆうし", "たけし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 87%, 9%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "実生", "answers": [ "みお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "政義", "answers": [ "まさよし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "比呂志", "answers": [ "ひろし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "樹範", "answers": [ "しげのり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "皓", "answers": [ "こう", "しろい", "しろし", "あきら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 79%, 10%, 9%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "研一郎", "answers": [ "けんいちろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "幹二", "answers": [ "かんじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "玉造", "answers": [ "たまぞう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 13%" },
	{ "question": "亮輔", "answers": [ "りょうすけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "頼長", "answers": [ "よりなが" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "喜孝", "answers": [ "よしたか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "義祐", "answers": [ "よしすけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "桃", "answers": [ "もも", "とう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 91%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "元忠", "answers": [ "もとただ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "政勝", "answers": [ "まさかつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "総子", "answers": [ "ふさこ", "そうこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "英恵", "answers": [ "はなえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "仲麻呂", "answers": [ "なかまろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "忠輝", "answers": [ "ただてる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "静一", "answers": [ "せいいち", "しずかず" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "弘次郎", "answers": [ "こうじろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "有礼", "answers": [ "ありのり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "彩芽", "answers": [ "あやめ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 78%" },
	{ "question": "亜門", "answers": [ "あもん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%" },
	{ "question": "よね子", "answers": [ "よねこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "雄治", "answers": [ "ゆうじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "康長", "answers": [ "やすなが" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "武一", "answers": [ "ぶいち", "たけかず", "たけいち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 78%, 11%, 11%" },
	{ "question": "宏伸", "answers": [ "ひろのぶ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "春生", "answers": [ "はるお", "はるみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 91%, 7%" },
	{ "question": "紀明", "answers": [ "のりあき", "としあき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "臣吾", "answers": [ "しんご" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "豪太", "answers": [ "ごうた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "恵二", "answers": [ "けいじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "紀世彦", "answers": [ "きよひこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "清成", "answers": [ "きよなり", "きよしげ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 40%, 21%" },
	{ "question": "凱斗", "answers": [ "かいと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "康友", "answers": [ "やすとも" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "美千子", "answers": [ "みちこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "洋史", "answers": [ "ひろし", "ひろふみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 70%, 30%" },
	{ "question": "菜穂子", "answers": [ "なおこ", "なほこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 69%, 31%" },
	{ "question": "貴義", "answers": [ "たかよし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "柴三郎", "answers": [ "しばさぶろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "小力", "answers": [ "こりき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "玉祥", "answers": [ "ぎょくしょう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "長和", "answers": [ "ながかず", "ながよし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 14%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "洋七", "answers": [ "ようしち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "佑子", "answers": [ "ゆうこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "保造", "answers": [ "やすぞう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "多代", "answers": [ "ますよ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "広美", "answers": [ "ひろみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "彦次郎", "answers": [ "ひこじろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "寅次郎", "answers": [ "とらじろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "武幸", "answers": [ "たけゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "伸太郎", "answers": [ "しんたろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "茂男", "answers": [ "しげお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "佐智子", "answers": [ "さちこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "貞昌", "answers": [ "さだまさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "貞治", "answers": [ "さだはる", "ていじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 79%, 21%" },
	{ "question": "憲太郎", "answers": [ "けんたろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "啓史", "answers": [ "けいじ", "けいし", "ひろし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 62%, 34%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "勝雄", "answers": [ "かつお", "かつたか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "維新", "answers": [ "いしん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "里依紗", "answers": [ "りいさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "美織", "answers": [ "みおり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "允彦", "answers": [ "まさひこ", "のぶひこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 88%, 12%" },
	{ "question": "千栄子", "answers": [ "ちえこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "隆宏", "answers": [ "たかひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "順司", "answers": [ "じゅんし", "じゅんじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 76%, 24%" },
	{ "question": "幸多", "answers": [ "こうた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "和俊", "answers": [ "かずとし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "栄次", "answers": [ "えいじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "古山", "answers": [ "ふるやま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 7%" },
	{ "question": "知花", "answers": [ "ともか", "ちか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 21%, 16%" },
	{ "question": "武智", "answers": [ "たけとも" ], "comment": "Frequency: 5%" },
	{ "question": "義尚", "answers": [ "よしひさ", "よしなお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 88%, 12%" },
	{ "question": "洋次郎", "answers": [ "ようじろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "康幸", "answers": [ "やすゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "峰子", "answers": [ "みねこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "光久", "answers": [ "みつひさ", "てるひさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "久代", "answers": [ "ひさよ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 77%" },
	{ "question": "親子内親王", "answers": [ "ちかこないしんのう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "貴大", "answers": [ "たかひろ", "たかお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "悟郎", "answers": [ "ごろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "工事", "answers": [ "こうじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "青", "answers": [ "あお", "せい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 56%, 44%" },
	{ "question": "斉加年", "answers": [ "まさかね" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "平之助", "answers": [ "へいのすけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "紀彰", "answers": [ "のりあき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "信重", "answers": [ "のぶしげ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "貞二", "answers": [ "ていじ", "さだじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "伸吾", "answers": [ "しんご" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "植", "answers": [ "しょく", "つぎ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 71%, 20%" },
	{ "question": "茂夫", "answers": [ "しげお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "理美", "answers": [ "さとみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "琴美", "answers": [ "ことみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "清孝", "answers": [ "きよたか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "學", "answers": [ "がく", "まなぶ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "夢二", "answers": [ "ゆめじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "雪次朗", "answers": [ "ゆきじろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "雄也", "answers": [ "ゆうや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "博資", "answers": [ "ひろよし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "比呂", "answers": [ "ひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 88%" },
	{ "question": "成彬", "answers": [ "なりあき", "しげあき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 63%, 37%" },
	{ "question": "晋平", "answers": [ "しんぺい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "和知", "answers": [ "かずとも" ], "comment": "Frequency: 77%" },
	{ "question": "家政", "answers": [ "いえまさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "明弘", "answers": [ "あきひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "吉雄", "answers": [ "よしお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 86%" },
	{ "question": "保子", "answers": [ "やすこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "六月", "answers": [ "むつき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 67%" },
	{ "question": "伴内", "answers": [ "ばんない" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "武司", "answers": [ "たけし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "鷹", "answers": [ "たか", "よう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 89%, 11%" },
	{ "question": "繁男", "answers": [ "しげお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "小太郎", "answers": [ "こたろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "喜一郎", "answers": [ "きいちろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "和則", "answers": [ "かずのり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "一慶", "answers": [ "いっけい", "かずよし", "かずのり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 54%, 27%, 19%" },
	{ "question": "嘉彦", "answers": [ "よしひこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "勇一", "answers": [ "ゆういち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "美玲", "answers": [ "みれい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "道明", "answers": [ "みちあき", "どうめい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 64%, 36%" },
	{ "question": "将斗", "answers": [ "まさと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "秀輝", "answers": [ "ひでき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "晴元", "answers": [ "はるもと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "信昌", "answers": [ "のぶまさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "常光", "answers": [ "ときみつ", "つねみつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 57%, 25%" },
	{ "question": "純平", "answers": [ "じゅんぺい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "沙羅", "answers": [ "さら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 84%" },
	{ "question": "喜久恵", "answers": [ "きくえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "絵理", "answers": [ "えり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "稲次郎", "answers": [ "いねじろう", "いなじろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 80%, 20%" },
	{ "question": "一太郎", "answers": [ "いちたろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "須磨", "answers": [ "すま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "藤生", "answers": [ "ふじお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "長塚", "answers": [ "ながつか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 8%" },
	{ "question": "義親", "answers": [ "よしちか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "道広", "answers": [ "みちひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "寛恵", "answers": [ "ひろえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "博堂", "answers": [ "はくどう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "孝典", "answers": [ "たかのり", "たかふみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 66%, 34%" },
	{ "question": "笙人", "answers": [ "しょうと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "将太", "answers": [ "しょうた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "重頼", "answers": [ "しげより" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "果歩", "answers": [ "かほ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "顔", "answers": [ "がん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 13%" },
	{ "question": "良文", "answers": [ "よしふみ", "よしぶみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "眞澄", "answers": [ "ますみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "雅雄", "answers": [ "まさお", "まさを", "つねお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 69%, 27%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "冨美子", "answers": [ "ふみこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "美齢", "answers": [ "びれい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "直見", "answers": [ "なおみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 92%" },
	{ "question": "利秋", "answers": [ "としあき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "武範", "answers": [ "たけのり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "正造", "answers": [ "しょうぞう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "和恵", "answers": [ "かずえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "敦志", "answers": [ "あつし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "丙太郎", "answers": [ "あきたろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "未知", "answers": [ "みち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 22%" },
	{ "question": "竜次", "answers": [ "りゅうじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "雪広", "answers": [ "ゆきひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 78%" },
	{ "question": "康久", "answers": [ "やすひさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "廣明", "answers": [ "ひろあき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "久彦", "answers": [ "ひさひこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "長安", "answers": [ "ながやす", "ちょうあん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 72%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "千晴", "answers": [ "ちはる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "達吉", "answers": [ "たつきち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "尊", "answers": [ "たける", "そん", "たかし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 75%, 12%, 12%" },
	{ "question": "真輔", "answers": [ "しんすけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "成之", "answers": [ "しげゆき", "なりゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 65%, 35%" },
	{ "question": "重明", "answers": [ "しげあき", "じゅうめい", "しげあきら", "ジュンミョン" ], "comment": "Frequency: 78%, 12%, 5%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "和範", "answers": [ "かずのり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "佳那", "answers": [ "かな" ], "comment": "Frequency: 10%" },
	{ "question": "吉晴", "answers": [ "よしはる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "宗孝", "answers": [ "むねたか", "むねみち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 89%, 11%" },
	{ "question": "深雪", "answers": [ "みゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 59%" },
	{ "question": "通洋", "answers": [ "みちひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "道隆", "answers": [ "みちたか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "美枝", "answers": [ "みえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "真利子", "answers": [ "まりこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "利晃", "answers": [ "としあき", "としてる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "岳志", "answers": [ "たけし", "がくじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "修吾", "answers": [ "しゅうご" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "繁蔵", "answers": [ "しげぞう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "我聞", "answers": [ "がもん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "響", "answers": [ "ひびき", "ひびく", "きょう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 17%, 15%, 13%" },
	{ "question": "柳二", "answers": [ "りゅうじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "好修", "answers": [ "よしのぶ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "保雄", "answers": [ "やすお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "元治", "answers": [ "もとはる", "もとじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 90%, 10%" },
	{ "question": "茉莉", "answers": [ "まり", "まつり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 69%, 31%" },
	{ "question": "纏", "answers": [ "まとめ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "理人", "answers": [ "まさと", "ただひと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 85%, 15%" },
	{ "question": "政景", "answers": [ "まさかげ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "洋夫", "answers": [ "ひろお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "英幸", "answers": [ "ひでゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "伴行", "answers": [ "ともゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "祥平", "answers": [ "しょうへい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "駿介", "answers": [ "しゅんすけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "沙保里", "answers": [ "さおり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "幸次", "answers": [ "こうじ", "ゆきつぐ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%, 7%" },
	{ "question": "経国", "answers": [ "けいこく", "つねくに" ], "comment": "Frequency: 81%, 19%" },
	{ "question": "久造", "answers": [ "きゅうぞう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "一喜", "answers": [ "かずき", "かずよし", "ひとつき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 79%, 19%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "えい子", "answers": [ "えいこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "彩名", "answers": [ "あやな" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "友清", "answers": [ "ともきよ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 12%" },
	{ "question": "スミ子", "answers": [ "スミこ", "すみこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 57%, 43%" },
	{ "question": "善久", "answers": [ "よしひさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "善雄", "answers": [ "よしお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "行男", "answers": [ "ゆきお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "未華子", "answers": [ "みかこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "正十郎", "answers": [ "まさじゅうろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "真緒", "answers": [ "まお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "紘子", "answers": [ "ひろこ", "こうこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 89%, 11%" },
	{ "question": "宏和", "answers": [ "ひろかず" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "秀哉", "answers": [ "ひでや", "しゅうさい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 53%, 47%" },
	{ "question": "奉文", "answers": [ "ともゆき", "ともふみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 89%, 11%" },
	{ "question": "貞", "answers": [ "ただし", "てい", "ただす" ], "comment": "Frequency: 73%, 18%, 8%" },
	{ "question": "潜", "answers": [ "せん", "ひそむ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 91%, 9%" },
	{ "question": "順造", "answers": [ "じゅんぞう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "國彦", "answers": [ "くにひこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "習", "answers": [ "しゅう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 14%" },
	{ "question": "マルクス闘莉王", "answers": [ "マルクス" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "亮吉", "answers": [ "りょうきち", "りょうきつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%, 6%" },
	{ "question": "頼三", "answers": [ "らいぞう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "良顕", "answers": [ "よしあき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "由宇", "answers": [ "ゆう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 86%" },
	{ "question": "康政", "answers": [ "やすまさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "芽以", "answers": [ "めい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "平吉", "answers": [ "へいきち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 79%" },
	{ "question": "春江", "answers": [ "はるえ", "しゅんこう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 46%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "華丸", "answers": [ "はなまる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "友三郎", "answers": [ "ともさぶろう", "ゆうざぶろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 91%, 9%" },
	{ "question": "籍", "answers": [ "せき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "志功", "answers": [ "しこう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "貞通", "answers": [ "さだみち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "行人", "answers": [ "こうじん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "衡", "answers": [ "こう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "原平", "answers": [ "げんぺい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%" },
	{ "question": "啓一郎", "answers": [ "けいいちろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "家宝", "answers": [ "かほう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "英助", "answers": [ "えいすけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "平内", "answers": [ "へいない" ], "comment": "Frequency: 17%" },
	{ "question": "清武", "answers": [ "きよたけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 18%" },
	{ "question": "清河", "answers": [ "きよかわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 16%" },
	{ "question": "李梨", "answers": [ "りり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "芳野", "answers": [ "よしの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 50%" },
	{ "question": "嘉子", "answers": [ "よしこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "正海", "answers": [ "まさみ", "せいかい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "彦六", "answers": [ "ひころく" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "初男", "answers": [ "はつお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "竜夫", "answers": [ "たつお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "辰平", "answers": [ "たっぺい", "たつへい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "忠朝", "answers": [ "ただとも" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "正健", "answers": [ "せいけん", "まさたけ", "まさかた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 76%, 19%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "順一郎", "answers": [ "じゅんいちろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "松之", "answers": [ "しょうし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "秀佳", "answers": [ "しゅうけい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "吾朗", "answers": [ "ごろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "豪志", "answers": [ "ごうし", "つよし", "たけし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 84%, 12%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "崋山", "answers": [ "かざん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "羅山", "answers": [ "らざん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "佳江", "answers": [ "よしえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "唯子", "answers": [ "ゆいこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "三喜男", "answers": [ "みきお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "政治", "answers": [ "まさはる", "せいじ", "まさじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 88%, 7%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "雅晴", "answers": [ "まさはる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "正生", "answers": [ "まさお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "保奈美", "answers": [ "ほなみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "伸彦", "answers": [ "のぶひこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "稔彦王", "answers": [ "なるひこおう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "長盛", "answers": [ "ながもり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "俊子", "answers": [ "としこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "敏江", "answers": [ "としえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "征四郎", "answers": [ "せいしろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "茂一", "answers": [ "しげいち", "もいち", "しげかず" ], "comment": "Frequency: 46%, 32%, 22%" },
	{ "question": "朔太郎", "answers": [ "さくたろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "朔", "answers": [ "さく", "はじめ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 54%, 43%" },
	{ "question": "一清", "answers": [ "かずきよ", "いっせい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 70%, 30%" },
	{ "question": "英次郎", "answers": [ "えいじろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "衣良", "answers": [ "いら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "暁子", "answers": [ "あきこ", "きょうこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "帥", "answers": [ "シュアイ", "すい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "師直", "answers": [ "もろなお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "通雄", "answers": [ "みちお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "寿史", "answers": [ "ひさし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "輝夫", "answers": [ "てるお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "隆義", "answers": [ "たかよし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "大洋", "answers": [ "たいよう", "もとひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 87%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "昭文", "answers": [ "しょうぶん", "あきふみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 89%, 11%" },
	{ "question": "秋水", "answers": [ "しゅうすい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "定吉", "answers": [ "さだきち", "さだよし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 54%, 46%" },
	{ "question": "氏直", "answers": [ "うじなお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "令子", "answers": [ "れいこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "由一", "answers": [ "よしかづ", "ゆいち", "よしかず", "よしいち", "ゆういち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 41%, 34%, 19%, 4%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "優一", "answers": [ "ゆういち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "観音", "answers": [ "みね" ], "comment": "Frequency: 90%" },
	{ "question": "昌行", "answers": [ "まさゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "長房", "answers": [ "ながふさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 90%" },
	{ "question": "高男", "answers": [ "たかお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "清一郎", "answers": [ "せいいちろう", "きよいちろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%, 6%" },
	{ "question": "時朗", "answers": [ "じろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "重文", "answers": [ "しげふみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "謙一郎", "answers": [ "けんいちろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "萬長", "answers": [ "かずなが" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "悦史", "answers": [ "えつし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "馬之助", "answers": [ "うまのすけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "明憲", "answers": [ "あきのり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "庸介", "answers": [ "ようすけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "之紀", "answers": [ "ゆきとし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "雄右", "answers": [ "ゆうすけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "泰宏", "answers": [ "やすひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "靖雄", "answers": [ "やすお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "三雄", "answers": [ "みつお", "さんゆう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "樹生", "answers": [ "みきお", "いつき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%, 7%" },
	{ "question": "孫一", "answers": [ "まごいち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "裕章", "answers": [ "ひろあき", "ゆうしょう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 69%, 31%" },
	{ "question": "尚記", "answers": [ "ひさのり", "なおき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "智仁", "answers": [ "ともひと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "千畝", "answers": [ "ちうね" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "忠世", "answers": [ "ただよ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "俊六", "answers": [ "しゅんろく" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "汐里", "answers": [ "しおり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "克利", "answers": [ "かつとし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "昭吾", "answers": [ "あきひと", "しょうご" ], "comment": "Frequency: 54%, 46%" },
	{ "question": "郷", "answers": [ "ごう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 10%" },
	{ "question": "竜馬", "answers": [ "りょうま", "りゅうま", "たつま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 38%, 38%, 24%" },
	{ "question": "柳太朗", "answers": [ "りゅうたろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "璃子", "answers": [ "りこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "幸正", "answers": [ "ゆきまさ", "こうしょう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "仁成", "answers": [ "ひとなり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "英美", "answers": [ "ひでみ", "えみ", "えいみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 64%, 30%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "秀美", "answers": [ "ひでみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "流", "answers": [ "ながる", "りゅう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 61%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "敏久", "answers": [ "としひさ", "みにく" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%, 6%" },
	{ "question": "貞次郎", "answers": [ "ていじろう", "さだじろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "孝義", "answers": [ "たかよし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "精児", "answers": [ "せいじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "祥", "answers": [ "しょう", "さち", "やすし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 80%, 12%, 8%" },
	{ "question": "重長", "answers": [ "しげなが", "しげたけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 88%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "候一", "answers": [ "こういち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "幾多郎", "answers": [ "きたろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "一朗太", "answers": [ "いちろうた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "有弘", "answers": [ "ありひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "敦史", "answers": [ "あつし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "昭之", "answers": [ "あきゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "章人", "answers": [ "あきひと", "あきと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 72%, 28%" },
	{ "question": "山辺", "answers": [ "やまべ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 4%" },
	{ "question": "優美", "answers": [ "ゆみ", "まさみ", "よしみ", "ゆうみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 81%, 14%, 4%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "将雅", "answers": [ "ゆうが" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "家持", "answers": [ "やかもち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "護熙", "answers": [ "もりひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "真代", "answers": [ "まよ", "まさよ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "満智子", "answers": [ "まちこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "真仁", "answers": [ "まさみ", "まさひと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "昌巳", "answers": [ "まさみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "真樹夫", "answers": [ "まきお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "文昭", "answers": [ "ふみあき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "富士男", "answers": [ "ふじお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "弘光", "answers": [ "ひろみつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "立美", "answers": [ "たつみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "忠房", "answers": [ "ただふさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "振一郎", "answers": [ "しんいちろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "璋", "answers": [ "しょう", "あきら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 92%, 8%" },
	{ "question": "浩吉", "answers": [ "こうきち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "一政", "answers": [ "かずまさ", "いっせい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 72%, 28%" },
	{ "question": "幾雄", "answers": [ "いくお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "清野", "answers": [ "きよの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "善信", "answers": [ "よしのぶ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "祐美子", "answers": [ "ゆみこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "森魚", "answers": [ "もりお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "美喜", "answers": [ "みき", "よしき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%, 6%" },
	{ "question": "智英", "answers": [ "ともふさ", "ちえ", "ともひで" ], "comment": "Frequency: 71%, 21%, 8%" },
	{ "question": "時彦", "answers": [ "ときひこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "資仁", "answers": [ "ただひと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "清純", "answers": [ "せいじゅん", "きよすみ", "きよずみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 70%, 15%, 15%" },
	{ "question": "昌二", "answers": [ "しょうじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "公章", "answers": [ "こうしょう", "きみゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 86%, 14%" },
	{ "question": "健太朗", "answers": [ "けんたろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "国芳", "answers": [ "くによし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "絵美子", "answers": [ "えみこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "亜蘭", "answers": [ "あらん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 20%" },
	{ "question": "佳正", "answers": [ "よしまさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "康徳", "answers": [ "やすのり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "昌俊", "answers": [ "まさとし", "しょうしゅん", "まさのり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 74%, 19%, 7%" },
	{ "question": "真紀子", "answers": [ "まきこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "宣明", "answers": [ "のぶあき", "のぶはる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "利彰", "answers": [ "としあき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "猛夫", "answers": [ "たけお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "誠志郎", "answers": [ "せいしろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "景時", "answers": [ "かげとき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "金剛", "answers": [ "こんごう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 9%" },
	{ "question": "了一", "answers": [ "りょういち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "美一", "answers": [ "よしかず", "びいち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 77%, 23%" },
	{ "question": "庸一", "answers": [ "よういち", "よういつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 64%, 36%" },
	{ "question": "部", "answers": [ "ぶ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "裕幸", "answers": [ "ひろゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "千佳子", "answers": [ "ちかこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "辰男", "answers": [ "たつお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "隆元", "answers": [ "たかもと", "りゅうげん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 75%, 25%" },
	{ "question": "佐和", "answers": [ "さわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 54%" },
	{ "question": "香代子", "answers": [ "かよこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "佳奈子", "answers": [ "かなこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "英九", "answers": [ "えいきゅう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "重村", "answers": [ "しげむら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 43%" },
	{ "question": "隆平", "answers": [ "りゅうへい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "有華", "answers": [ "ゆか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "康次郎", "answers": [ "やすじろう", "こうじろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 83%, 17%" },
	{ "question": "万沙子", "answers": [ "まさこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "奈穂", "answers": [ "なほ", "なお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 89%, 11%" },
	{ "question": "琢朗", "answers": [ "たくろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "崇彦", "answers": [ "たかひこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "進次郎", "answers": [ "しんじろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "公義", "answers": [ "きみよし", "ただし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "維", "answers": [ "い" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "眞木", "answers": [ "まき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 21%" },
	{ "question": "莉菜", "answers": [ "りな" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "頼重", "answers": [ "よりしげ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "洋吉", "answers": [ "ようきち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "勇輝", "answers": [ "ゆうき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "盛重", "answers": [ "もりしげ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 86%" },
	{ "question": "宗直", "answers": [ "むねなお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "正容", "answers": [ "まさひろ", "まさかた", "まさやす" ], "comment": "Frequency: 57%, 42%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "文人", "answers": [ "ふみんど", "ふみひと", "ふみと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 74%, 17%, 9%" },
	{ "question": "治彦", "answers": [ "はるひこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "奈月", "answers": [ "なつき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 76%" },
	{ "question": "綱紀", "answers": [ "つなのり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "主税", "answers": [ "ちから" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "達三", "answers": [ "たつぞう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "忠俊", "answers": [ "ただとし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "愼一", "answers": [ "しんいち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "元一", "answers": [ "げんいち", "もとかず", "もといち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 58%, 36%, 6%" },
	{ "question": "一心", "answers": [ "いっしん", "かずただ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "彰久", "answers": [ "あきひさ", "てるひさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 88%, 12%" },
	{ "question": "安芸子", "answers": [ "あきこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "和木", "answers": [ "かずき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 6%" },
	{ "question": "有紀子", "answers": [ "ゆきこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "雄二郎", "answers": [ "ゆうじろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "三厳", "answers": [ "みつよし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "麻由", "answers": [ "まゆ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "秀武", "answers": [ "ひでたけ", "ひでぶ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%, 7%" },
	{ "question": "敏弘", "answers": [ "としひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "大輝", "answers": [ "だいき", "たいき", "ひろき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 60%, 8%, 6%" },
	{ "question": "譚", "answers": [ "たん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 47%" },
	{ "question": "貴士", "answers": [ "たかし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "重次", "answers": [ "しげつぐ", "しげじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 91%, 9%" },
	{ "question": "紗耶香", "answers": [ "さやか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "貞世", "answers": [ "さだよ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "貞則", "answers": [ "さだのり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "光三郎", "answers": [ "こうざぶろう", "みつさぶろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 54%, 46%" },
	{ "question": "粂子", "answers": [ "くめこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "一枝", "answers": [ "かずえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 70%" },
	{ "question": "開", "answers": [ "かい", "ひらく" ], "comment": "Frequency: 77%, 13%" },
	{ "question": "えり子", "answers": [ "えりこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "梁川", "answers": [ "りょうせん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 7%" },
	{ "question": "充徳", "answers": [ "みつのり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "寛夫", "answers": [ "ひろお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "憲政", "answers": [ "のりまさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "長可", "answers": [ "ながよし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "直弘", "answers": [ "なおひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "熾仁親王", "answers": [ "たるひとしんのう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "崇矢", "answers": [ "たかや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "孝浩", "answers": [ "たかひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "淳治", "answers": [ "じゅんじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "慈英", "answers": [ "じえい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "晋二郎", "answers": [ "しんじろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "広一", "answers": [ "こういち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "元太郎", "answers": [ "げんたろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "克昌", "answers": [ "かつまさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "香衣", "answers": [ "かえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "泳三", "answers": [ "ヨンサム" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "良幸", "answers": [ "よしゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "康貴", "answers": [ "やすたか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "直幸", "answers": [ "なおゆき", "なおひで" ], "comment": "Frequency: 72%, 28%" },
	{ "question": "智広", "answers": [ "ともひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "干城", "answers": [ "たてき", "かんじょう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "孝丸", "answers": [ "たかまる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "宗久", "answers": [ "そうきゅう", "むねひさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 66%, 34%" },
	{ "question": "紗弥加", "answers": [ "さやか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "沙耶香", "answers": [ "さやか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "宏博", "answers": [ "こうはく" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "清秀", "answers": [ "きよひで" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "和紀", "answers": [ "わき", "かずのり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 61%, 39%" },
	{ "question": "頼広", "answers": [ "よしひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "雪子", "answers": [ "ゆきこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "恭久", "answers": [ "やすひさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "幹恵", "answers": [ "みきえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "不二男", "answers": [ "ふじお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "博志", "answers": [ "ひろし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "秀彰", "answers": [ "ひであき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "竜彦", "answers": [ "たつひこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "剛彦", "answers": [ "たけひこ", "よしひこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 92%, 8%" },
	{ "question": "竹識", "answers": [ "たけし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "宗仁", "answers": [ "そうじん", "そうにん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 86%, 14%" },
	{ "question": "小枝", "answers": [ "こえだ", "さえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 89%, 6%" },
	{ "question": "稲子", "answers": [ "いねこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 87%" },
	{ "question": "山花", "answers": [ "やまか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 4%" },
	{ "question": "成勲", "answers": [ "よしひろ", "せいくん", "ソンフン" ], "comment": "Frequency: 78%, 14%, 8%" },
	{ "question": "洋三郎", "answers": [ "ようざぶろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "征夫", "answers": [ "ゆきお", "いくお", "いさお", "まさお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 48%, 42%, 6%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "美春", "answers": [ "みはる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "真己", "answers": [ "まみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%" },
	{ "question": "雅代", "answers": [ "まさよ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "広元", "answers": [ "ひろもと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "朋紘", "answers": [ "ともひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "潮五郎", "answers": [ "ちょうごろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "丹", "answers": [ "たん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 75%" },
	{ "question": "立夫", "answers": [ "たつお", "りつふ", "たてお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 75%, 19%, 6%" },
	{ "question": "忠真", "answers": [ "ただざね" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "忠国", "answers": [ "ただくに" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "武久", "answers": [ "たけひさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "武庸", "answers": [ "たけつね" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "高徳", "answers": [ "たかのり", "ごうとく" ], "comment": "Frequency: 58%, 28%" },
	{ "question": "丈太郎", "answers": [ "じょうたろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "兄", "answers": [ "けい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "軍平", "answers": [ "ぐんぺい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "壱成", "answers": [ "いっせい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "彩香", "answers": [ "あやか", "さやか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 87%, 13%" },
	{ "question": "秋緒", "answers": [ "あきお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "長江", "answers": [ "ちょうこう", "ながえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 21%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "隆法", "answers": [ "りゅうほう", "りゅんぽっ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "竜三", "answers": [ "りゅうぞう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "義盛", "answers": [ "よしもり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "雄基", "answers": [ "ゆうき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "春女", "answers": [ "はるめ", "はるみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 55%, 45%" },
	{ "question": "八光", "answers": [ "はちみつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "智雄", "answers": [ "ともお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "沙希", "answers": [ "さき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "洸", "answers": [ "こう", "たけし", "あきら", "ひかる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 74%, 11%, 9%, 6%" },
	{ "question": "公人", "answers": [ "きみと", "きみんど", "きみひと", "こうじん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 37%, 34%, 23%, 6%" },
	{ "question": "兼平", "answers": [ "かねひら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 86%" },
	{ "question": "且元", "answers": [ "かつもと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%" },
	{ "question": "伊佐夫", "answers": [ "いさお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "芳彦", "answers": [ "よしひこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "由佳理", "answers": [ "ゆかり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "侑子", "answers": [ "ゆうこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "昌代", "answers": [ "まさよ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "正寛", "answers": [ "まさひろ", "まさのり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 84%, 16%" },
	{ "question": "福志郎", "answers": [ "ふくしろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "英典", "answers": [ "ひでのり", "えいすけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 91%, 9%" },
	{ "question": "憲男", "answers": [ "のりお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "知弘", "answers": [ "ともひろ", "ちひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 89%, 11%" },
	{ "question": "弾", "answers": [ "だん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%" },
	{ "question": "たい平", "answers": [ "たいへい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "重徳", "answers": [ "しげのり", "じゅうとく" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "三章", "answers": [ "さんしょう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "敬吾", "answers": [ "けいご" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "君枝", "answers": [ "きみえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "勝敏", "answers": [ "かつとし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "愛鈴", "answers": [ "えりん", "あいり", "あいりん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%, 2%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "江里子", "answers": [ "えりこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "朝子", "answers": [ "あさこ", "ともこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 88%, 12%" },
	{ "question": "当麻", "answers": [ "とうま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 17%" },
	{ "question": "上", "answers": [ "じょう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 3%" },
	{ "question": "嘉隆", "answers": [ "よしたか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "雄之助", "answers": [ "ゆうのすけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "雄策", "answers": [ "ゆうさく" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "安太郎", "answers": [ "やすたろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "三樹夫", "answers": [ "みきお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "昌久", "answers": [ "まさひさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "誠彦", "answers": [ "まさひこ", "せいげん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%, 7%" },
	{ "question": "宏史", "answers": [ "ひろし", "ひろふみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 59%, 41%" },
	{ "question": "初美", "answers": [ "はつみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 68%" },
	{ "question": "暢", "answers": [ "とおる", "のぼる", "みつる", "ちょう", "チャン" ], "comment": "Frequency: 44%, 40%, 6%, 6%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "小雪", "answers": [ "こゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "桂介", "answers": [ "けいすけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "国貞", "answers": [ "くにさだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 82%" },
	{ "question": "教生", "answers": [ "きょうせい", "のりお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "克明", "answers": [ "かつあき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "栄三郎", "answers": [ "えいざぶろう", "えいさぶろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "映子", "answers": [ "えいこ", "あきこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 70%, 30%" },
	{ "question": "敦司", "answers": [ "あつし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "宗方", "answers": [ "むねかた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 17%" },
	{ "question": "竜司", "answers": [ "りゅうじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%" },
	{ "question": "義堯", "answers": [ "よしたか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "良重", "answers": [ "よしえ", "よししげ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 88%, 12%" },
	{ "question": "幸弘", "answers": [ "ゆきひろ", "さちひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "雄太郎", "answers": [ "ゆうたろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "みよ子", "answers": [ "みよこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "未歩", "answers": [ "みほ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "正大", "answers": [ "まさひろ", "せいだい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "房之介", "answers": [ "ふさのすけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "爆", "answers": [ "ばく" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "知義", "answers": [ "ともよし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "智行", "answers": [ "ともゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "悌", "answers": [ "てい", "やすし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%, 6%" },
	{ "question": "忠行", "answers": [ "ただゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "忠宏", "answers": [ "ただひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "拓弥", "answers": [ "たくや", "ひろや", "たくみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 84%, 10%, 6%" },
	{ "question": "卓史", "answers": [ "たかし", "たかふみ", "たくし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 57%, 27%, 16%" },
	{ "question": "涼花", "answers": [ "すずか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 90%" },
	{ "question": "次郎長", "answers": [ "じろちょう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "少奇", "answers": [ "しょうき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "定頼", "answers": [ "さだより" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "健吉", "answers": [ "けんきち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "義丹", "answers": [ "ぎたん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "金造", "answers": [ "きんぞう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "梅次", "answers": [ "うめつぐ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "彩音", "answers": [ "あやね" ], "comment": "Frequency: 80%" },
	{ "question": "彩菜", "answers": [ "あやな" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "正名", "answers": [ "まさな" ], "comment": "Frequency: 30%" },
	{ "question": "ゆず季", "answers": [ "ゆずき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "保次郎", "answers": [ "やすじろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "峯一", "answers": [ "みねいち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "広家", "answers": [ "ひろいえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "英敏", "answers": [ "ひでとし", "えいびん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 92%, 8%" },
	{ "question": "晴敏", "answers": [ "はるとし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "伸顕", "answers": [ "のぶあき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "徳三郎", "answers": [ "とくさぶろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "悌二", "answers": [ "ていじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "鮮明", "answers": [ "せんめい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "秀徳", "answers": [ "しゅうとく", "ひでのり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 60%, 40%" },
	{ "question": "好位置", "answers": [ "こういち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "謙太郎", "answers": [ "けんたろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "邦弘", "answers": [ "くにひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "香奈子", "answers": [ "かなこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "雄仁", "answers": [ "かつひと", "ゆうじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 83%, 17%" },
	{ "question": "馬子", "answers": [ "うまこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "章雄", "answers": [ "あきお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "南風", "answers": [ "なんぷう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 35%" },
	{ "question": "東原", "answers": [ "とうげん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 5%" }
]
}
